Open the door now!
Being stubborn, are we?
You're the big boss, I assume?
Please. Don't.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Wait. You... You don't understand.
The Azurium here is still in its raw form.
It's unstable.
If it's disturbed,
it could cause a massive explosion.
Is that supposed to scare me?
The bigger, the better!
Let him go!
Pathetic. Toss him out!
Anyone else want to be a hero?
Sir.
If we want to make it out of here alive,
we should do as he says.
Get in!
You think you're so tough?
Let's see if you can swim.
Which way is the exit?
This way, bro!
Okay, thanks.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
How did these pirates get in here?
All done, let's go!
Wait.
What?
Did you pay attention to the brief?
We wait for IRIS.
What's taking so long?
Turn the burner off.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Attack!
Come here! Don't run away!
Move!
Biting off more than you can chew?
Don't drop them!
Are we done?
Put him here.
Where are we getting food later, doctor?
Be quiet.
Alicia, what's wrong?
- Are you seasick?
- Stop...
Stop him.
Stay back!
Or I'll toss this one.
Bakar, Bobby, don't let them escape!
Nothing's working!
Let me try.
Be careful, Bobby.
Watch the bag!
Stop moving around so much, bro!
See you!
Wait for me!
Everything's under control.
Way to go, Alicia!
Well done.
You're definitely a step up
from that sniveling kid.
Wait.
Is he talking about Ali?
Ali.
Ali, are you ready?
Yes.
SATRIA, status.
The current compatibility level
is approximately 60%.
We need to train more Pillar functions
to raise the overall percentage.
I know that.
I was asking about the mission.
Do you think he can handle it?
He must.
This is the only chance we've got.
He's here.
Dato'.
I believe you're acquainted
with my head of security,
Amir.
Dayang, Ganz, it's been a while
since we worked together.
Mission Batu Lesung, was it?
How's your arm?
Good as new.
Perhaps next time, it will be
my turn to rescue you?
And this is Elle.
My niece.
She has been my eyes and ears
for all operations in the city.
I've decided to appoint them
as the Pillar Leaders
for Neuro and Inviso.
That's great.
I hope that we can protect Cyberaya
more effectively.
So, what is it that you wanted to show me?
Oh no.
We're too exposed.
We can take them out from a distance.
Not again.
SATRIA is equipped with data
from all MATA agents
to enable it to carry out
the functions of all four Pillars.
We figured that
after Zain and Djin's passing,
the best way to continue operations
is to combine the Pillars.
This is to avoid an imbalance.
Why a young agent?
Is there no other suitable candidate?
He's the only one with experience
in the IRIS dimension.
It's similar to the system used
to control SATRIA.
SATRIA...
Use the gasing barrier.
Now.
Wouldn't it be more efficient to use AI?
SATRIA's AI will be there to assist,
but Ali will decide the course of action.
AI will never be able
to replace the human instinct
when evaluating complex decisions
during missions.
Device is in danger.
Ali, we need a more strategic defense.
What sort of strategy?
Calm down, Ali.
Your neural readings are off the charts.
Ali, the suit's integrity
is dropping below 50%.
I did it!
Ouch.
He still needs to get used to it.
But I believe the SATRIA project
will breathe new life into MATA.
It's clear he's not ready yet.
I need to see more developments
before this project can be approved.
That was a close one, Comot.
I really thought I was going to fail.
Do you think
I need more data to sync with?
Can I really be SATRIA?
Oh, come on. You just ate!
I'll feed you later.
I have to prepare for training tomorrow.
Here, play with this.
It's the IRIS agent!
Bulat, do you know where Ali is?
In there.
What's that?
Ouch.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
You never come over.
Why? Can't I?
Just taking a stroll, checking on Comot.
You're really not going
on missions anymore?
I thought you wanted to be a Super Agent.
You'll see once I'm done with training.
SATRIA training?
Mind your own business!
Just don't tell anyone.
Fine.
Ali.
Yeah?
Actually, I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
When you were using IRIS,
did you
get headaches?
No?
You never felt
like fainting?
And...
Of course, using IRIS does drain
a lot of your energy.
Now you see, you think
it's easy working with IRIS?
It's not that. I mean...
Hey, Ali. Are we on for this thing?
I'm about to head out!
Okay, we're on.
I forgot about
the study group with Viktor.
Don't worry about IRIS.
I think you just need more practice.
Got to go, bye!
Come on, Comot.
Look at me!
- Am I awesome or what?
- My turn!
Hey, come on, guys. I need to go home.
We're not done yet.
Didn't your folks teach you to share?
Hey, Ali!
He's really asking for it!
Okay then.
There he is!
When he comes out, we'll get him.
Run.
Don't look back!
What are you doing here, Agent Rizwan?
MATA has been looking for you.
We still have work to do, Ali.
All of the Numeros's threats,
Uno, Cinco.
They were never acting alone.
Someone has been orchestrating everything.
Who?
Cero.
I'm still trying to identify him.
You must help me get
the mission reports from MATA.
No way.
All intel from MATA is top secret.
I knew it. I told you he'd chicken out.
Ali, as long as they're around,
Cyberaya is in danger.
I'm sorry, Agent Rizwan.
I can't.
It's okay.
If you ever need me, I'll be there.
And Ali.
I'm not an agent anymore.
Viktor, you're early...
Sasi?
He said he wanted to study with us.
Yeah, it's almost the finals!
I can't lose to him again.
And you, you're getting smarter now too.
I want to see how you guys study.
What's your secret?
Come on, let's get started!
What are we waiting for?
If you want to know our secret,
before we study, we need to warm up first.
To increase our brainpower!
That's right, then we can focus better.
Wait, we can't be playing games.
It's the finals
and you're here wasting time?
Behind you!
Don't let him get away!
- Nice!
How much longer?
Wait, last round!
Do you want to try?
We'll study as soon as we're done, okay?
It won't take long.
How do I do this?
You just punch.
Like this?
I'm on your team.
Okay, one more round.
Don't you want to go home?
Oh no, it's so late!
Studying with you guys was awesome.
We should do this again sometime!
Oh man, it's going to rain.
What have we done?
We didn't even study.
Here, I took down some notes just now.
- Nice!
- See you.
The power supply disruption that occurred
early this morning in Wawasan Bay
and multiple technology centers
has been restored
without any complications.
The official report of the investigation
determined that
it was caused by an unusual
elemental change in the ocean currents.
The weather is really acting up.
Energy supply is now fully operational
- and stable.
- Comot.
- Get off the remote.
- No prolonged disruption is expected.
According to
the official statement from Cyber...
Civilians and establishments
that were affected
express their gratitude...
On a lighter note, let's tune in to...
Ali!
Remember me?
Neonimus!
What's up?
No more missions?
Are you suspended again?
How are you doing this--
Come on, like you're not used to this.
Let's play a game!
I've created a level.
Especially for you.
Yeah, let me try this.
Our intel states that
Neonimus will launch his greatest attack
at the following location tonight.
Your mission is to complete
the most thrilling level
before time runs out.
If you fail,
the entrance and exit will be sealed.
Act immediately!
So, how'd I do?
You... Why would I play your dirty game?
I knew you'd play hard to get.
That's fine,
but if you decide not to play,
I will reveal the identity
of all of MATA's agents!
You should come, I'll be waiting.
Don't be late.
- This is--
- Cyberaya Smart Tunnel.
That's a very strategic target,
especially with the weather lately.
This could spell disaster.
Maybe there's nothing
to worry about. Look.
Even though Neonimus is quite
the cunning hacker,
he's not as dangerous as he seems.
He threatened to blow up
the MATA base, but didn't.
He threatened to crash
the trains, but didn't.
In short, he's just all talk.
This is not a high-level threat.
I agree, send out the young agents, okay?
Act immediately.
Wait.
Since Ali has had some experience dealing
with Neonimus in the past,
this might be the right time
for us to test out SATRIA?
- SATRIA? What is--
- SATRIA has not yet been approved.
That is why we need results
from an actual mission.
Are you certain?
If anything happens,
you'll assume all responsibility?
In case you haven't noticed,
Dato's patience has been running thin
since you failed with IRIS NEO.
Fine.
We'll send a support team.
Ali!
It's been a while since
our last mission together.
Can't believe we get to do this again.
I can't believe
I still have to babysit you.
Why you...
Ali.
This is your chance to prove
your capabilities as the SATRIA Agent.
Good luck.
- Understood.
- Do your best.
And don't mess up!
Ganz.
Go ahead.
SATRIA. Rise.
Ready.
Cool.
I'm dead!
I've got to split before he...
Take this!
You think you can escape?
I'm not going anywhere, I'm right here.
I gave you a golden opportunity.
Not only did you fail,
but you're also trying to betray me!
Betray you?
No!
Pirate scum.
What did you tell them?
Nothing, I didn't say anything, I swear!
Fine.
But now,
it's time to erase all traces.
Have mercy, Cero...
I don't want to die single.
Cero. I knew it.
Too easy.
You...
You tricked me.
So noisy.
Your kid's got a mission.
CAUTION, SPEED TRAP
You brought backup, I see?
I'm going to have
to set up multiplayer then.
The game is simple.
If you can make it
to the end of the tunnel,
you guys win.
If not, you'll see.
Watch out!
Don't let him get away!
Let's go, SATRIA!
Are you okay, ma'am?
He's using this to hack
into the cars' systems.
SATRIA, can you trace
the source of the signal?
- Yes, hold on.
- Okay.
What's that?
Don't let them get to the others.
- Ali, Neonimus's location--
- Wait.
People are in danger here.
Show-off.
Too slow.
Ali, we need to find Neonimus quickly.
Now is not the time to play around.
I'm not playing, it's Alicia!
Too slow!
Seems like we'll wrap up in no time.
So, what shall we eat next, Comot?
Having fun?
Let's see if you can handle this.
Is everyone okay?
Get off.
Get off here.
Right here. Watch your step, ma'am.
Move.
SATRIA, dial it down a little.
There are civilians here.
No!
Help me!
Go, Ali!
We'll handle this.
One little spider
Got Ali in its web
Neonimus?
You're just a kid?
Why? Is that so hard to believe?
It's just like when people
find out you're an agent.
If it weren't for you,
I'd be a young agent too!
What do you mean?
You stole my spot!
They threw me out of the academy
to make space for you!
So, I need to show them that
they've chosen the wrong person.
Unfortunately,
I must scout for a new player.
Because now,
it's game over for you.
Hey!
You are all a bunch of cheaters!
Fine, two can play that game!
When the water crashes
The spider runs away
Yeah, you'd better run.
Agent Bakar, we need to move now!
Why?
Hurry!
Let's get out of here!
Darn.
Nice job, Alicia!
Alicia?
Don't run away!
Alicia, wake up!
Ali, focus on the objective.
Nice job, Ali.
Let's go.
All set.
Hurry. We've got to move
before MATA's cleanup crew arrives.
Wait.
Grab one of those things.
Just one?
Why not a knapsack full?
What year were you born?
Alicia, are you all right?
What happened?
The mission.
Everyone's safe.
But
Neonimus got away.
So,
it's not looking good for Project SATRIA.
Ali was supposed to pull it off.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
No.
I'm late.
- Alicia, you should be resting.
- General.
Well?
From my analysis of the recording,
she's proven to be more efficient
and performs far better than Ali.
It's just that I found
some glitches in IRIS's functions.
Stand up!
- Good morning, Mrs. Munah!
Morning.
All right.
I will now share the results
of your trial exam.
- First place.
- Please.
As usual,
Alicia!
Where is Alicia?
She... Alicia...
- She has...
- Present, Mrs. Munah.
I apologize.
I got caught up with prefect duties.
Just because you're the top student
doesn't mean you can skip classes.
It's not a good sign.
You might just fail your exam.
Second place.
Viktor!
No!
Thank you.
Ali, wait.
Do you want some?
How are you doing with SATRIA now?
I don't know.
I heard they were discussing
going fully automated.
Or they might change agents.
If that's true, then I really won't
be able to go on missions anymore.
I'm sorry, Ali.
If it weren't for me...
It's fine.
Are you okay?
Why did you pass out?
Actually,
that's what I've been trying to tell you.
When I'm using IRIS,
it's like I can see things...
that haven't happened yet.
That's IRIS's function, it gives you
the computer's perception.
I know that.
I mean like,
I can see the future.
And in the tunnel,
how did you think I knew
you were in danger?
You mean,
you're like a psychic?
That's so cool!
I thought so at first,
but after a while, it got worse.
Or maybe you're just too high-strung?
- Excuse me?
- I mean...
You're too serious all the time,
and your brain controls IRIS.
Maybe the computer's all scrambled
because you're using your brain too much.
You're the one
not using your brain enough.
Why you...
Oh man, I forgot again. Study group!
Ali!
Alicia, what are you doing here?
We are...
Studying, what else?
That's interesting.
What's interesting?
We're playing two v two, right?
No!
Wait, then.
She's really joining our study group?
You want to know our secret?
Before studying,
we need to warm up first.
To increase--
No need for that.
How about we skip the game today?
Why?
You guys think I can't chill out?
Right there!
Full charge, do the special attack!
Yes!
I beat Alicia at last.
It's just a game, man.
Oh man, Alicia.
- You should've used the special attack.
- Jeez.
Can you show me again, Ali. Please?
Do this to attack,
and this for the special attack.
You should loosen up a bit.
You're too stiff.
Okay, again.
Nice!
GG.
EZ.
I don't want to study
with you guys anymore.
Hey, Sasi!
You said you wanted a ride later?
So, are we studying or what?
HAPPY BURGER, CHICKEN SPECIAL
What's on your mind?
I'm beginning to see his game.
Look.
The people chosen by Cero
all have their own motives
to antagonize Cyberaya.
From there, he will seize the opportunity
and incite them to carry out his plans.
Now, we just have to find out
who his next target will be.
How is Ali?
Your kid's got a new toy.
Neonimus.
He has upped his game.
Rizwan!
You've got to see this.
I was tracking the signal to this thing.
Then it brought up all these locations.
This one. Does that look familiar?
Wait, isn't that...
Let's move.
See you.
Thanks, I had fun today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I think even my headache is easing up.
So, I was right, you are too high-strung.
No, I'm just kidding.
Are we studying again tomorrow?
No, I have training tomorrow.
I need to increase my sync levels
in order to keep going on with SATRIA.
How come your Neuro sync level is so low?
I don't know.
Follow me.
What are we playing chess for?
A Neuro Agent must be able to think ahead
while on a mission.
Playing chess can help train
your ability to predict.
Don't simply track the enemy's movements.
Anticipate where they're going.
Now that you no longer have IRIS,
you need to read
the fight patterns yourself.
A Neuro Agent must have a strong memory.
Order?
Fried noodles, hold the spice.
Two, but with an egg!
I'd like a spicy one, no veggies.
Ditto, but make mine rice noodles.
Also, an iced black tea,
make it less sweet!
Oh man!
Don't hesitate.
Good, again!
Boss, two special roti, please!
- Iced tea in a big glass!
- Done!
Now you've got it.
You've really never had these before?
No.
I don't eat junk food like you.
Talk about discipline,
no wonder you're awesome
even without IRIS.
You're not so bad yourself.
You've got instincts and spirit.
And you don't even train much.
It's so unfair.
Look at you two, having fun?
What?
Can't I go with them?
It is not my decision.
- But...
- You shouldn't be here!
Everyone's ready?
Entrance, clear.
Main stage, clear.
Control room, clear.
Jero mascot, clear.
Food plaza, clear.
Hello, are you open or not?
Right. Agents, stay vigilant.
Amir, what were you thinking?
Why did you send out so many agents?
We can't take any risks.
What's more, after the recent
smart tunnel incident.
From SATRIA's mission recording,
I've managed to uncover
Neonimus's identity.
What?
- When did you...
- I think you know him better than we do.
It can't be.
Who's the kid?
He was recruited as a young agent.
But he was expelled from the academy
due to behavioral issues.
Shouldn't he be following
MATA's procedures?
Yes, but he managed to sabotage the system
before disappearing.
Voilà!
Are you kidding?
This doesn't even look like the picture!
Just eat the picture then!
- Chill, bro.
- What's going on here?
Are you here to work or goof around?
We're undercover.
So we're supposed to play the part.
Are you for real, Alicia?
What?
Am I wrong?
If you like it so much,
go ahead and do it.
No way,
we were assigned to survey the area.
Yeah, let's go!
Hey, come back here!
I want to go too!
I bet Ali's not tall enough for this ride!
Touché!
The show's starting!
We'll reconvene here later.
Act immediately!
DETECTIVE JEBAT - WRATH OF EVIL
So, Agent Alicia has entered the game.
Looks like you've found my special level.
Let's go, Cadet!
We need to take out the Terrible Three
before they rise in power
and attack our town!
Get off now!
Zass, get him out!
Team, come in, I need backup!
You think you can skip ahead
without playing?
AGENT ALICIA
Alicia.
Send backup!
Pull out the agents from other missions.
We don't have enough intel!
Don't repeat the same mistake.
- So we'll use drones.
- And if they get hacked?
Let's send SATRIA.
Ali has shown improvements in training...
Now isn't the right time
to showcase your pet project.
But she's right!
I am getting better at handling SATRIA!
What is he doing here?
I commanded you to stay out!
Send me.
General, we need you here to...
Just try and stop me.
Formation!
Who's messing with our Icha?
Act immediately!
Alicia!
You finally made it!
Now we can have some fun!
Let her go!
Sure.
You just have to clear this level first!
Why are they still moving?
They were repaired by those spider robots.
SATRIA, increase attack power.
Got you now!
Icha!
Where do you think you're going?
You win!
You wanted to play so bad?
Ali. Don't.
Please don't kill me.
I'm just following orders!
Ali, enough!
Amir.
Amir!
It's time to step in.
Don't be hasty.
Fallen agents can be replaced.
But if we fall, it's the end for MATA!
And SATRIA?
Are we going to let it fall
into the enemy's hands?
That wouldn't have been a problem
if you'd gotten rid of the pilot
like we suggested.
You see.
If you're not capable of controlling
your own subordinates,
what's the point in being a Pillar Leader?
Watch your mouth.
Dato'.
My phone won't stop ringing.
The media's been chasing me
left and right.
Look!
The people out there are panicking!
What have you been doing?
We have...
We've lost five teams.
General Rama has gone rogue
with Ali and SATRIA.
What's their status?
We're still not able to reach them.
- Why are you all so use--
- General?
What?
Is that SATRIA, the secret project?
I heard he single-handedly
saved everybody.
Really? That's amazing!
Agent Dayang!
Congratulations, Ali.
You did it.
This is for your own good.
Can you believe it, Comot?
Me.
The SATRIA Agent.
Ali, can we talk?
Alicia!
You're okay?
- I guess.
- That was some mission!
Did you see me just now?
You didn't, huh?
Right. You were knocked out.
But if you had seen me in action...
- Wait, maybe IRIS recorded it.
- Ali!
I need to tell you something!
I saw
something with IRIS.
Rot in here for all we care!
Agent Dayang!
I...
I want to speak to Agent Dayang.
Are you sure about this?
I'm just following the signal.
Look around.
See if you can find a hidden space.
We were here with Uno for years.
I would've known if there were...
DETECTIVE JEBAT
What's wrong?
Are you in danger?
No.
MATA's the one in danger.
All this time, my revenge was
just child's play to you.
You have been underestimating me.
Because I was never good enough
to join your team.
But this time around,
I'm no longer playing alone.
I've found myself a powerful teammate!
You will regret the day you threw me out!
What have you done?
You'll see for yourself.
By the way, Cero sends his regards.
He knows we're here.
What?
SATRIA?
Causing destruction?
Are you serious?
I'm not so sure myself.
But it looks really bad, Ali.
Or maybe what you saw was
just me on a mission?
I don't think so
because everything was wrecked.
Nothing was left standing.
Except SATRIA.
When will this happen exactly?
I don't know.
But I've got a bad feeling about it.
Maybe we should just tell Agent Dayang.
We need confirmation first.
Can't you use IRIS to see again?
I don't have IRIS right now.
The General took it.
He's giving it back to Agent Dayang.
So that's it.
What?
You...
You're trying to take SATRIA away from me.
Because they took IRIS from you?
You think I'm making all this up?
It's not like you have any proof.
Am I supposed to just believe you?
Why not?
You believed me before!
I don't know.
Kind of strange that
you have all these visions
just when things are going great for me.
You seriously think I'm jealous of you?
You've always felt that way about me.
Ever since I got IRIS!
You sure are dense!
Whatever, at least I'm okay
with other agents being better than me.
I couldn't care less about IRIS!
I'm not like you.
I don't have to depend on some gadget.
Pathetic!
I knew you'd...
- Stop it, Comot!
- Quiet!
Agent Rizwan.
What?
Neonimus. Get him out of there.
Why?
We've been
played right into Cero's plan.
What do we do?
Find the General.
What now?
What's going on?
All comms are offline.
We need to switch the backup power on.
Ganz, find Dayang, and...
The HQ has been breached.
Initiate the Island Protocol.
You alert them about Neonimus.
I'll go get SATRIA.
Are you serious?
After everything I've told you,
don't you care at all?
I don't have time for all this!
Ali, wait!
SATRIA.
Rise.
Ali, something is interfering
with the system.
- Neonimus. He was able to insert--
- I know.
We need to move fast!
He should be in the holding area.
It seems Neonimus has taken over
the droids' control system.
We will take more time
if we use alternate routes.
Then we won't, just push through.
Since when did MATA droids
fight like this?
It is probably caused
by Neonimus's program.
Oh man.
There's more?
Why are you here all alone? Where's Ali?
He went to get SATRIA.
- You should take cover.
- I can help.
No excuses, you're still recovering.
- Go to the control room now!
- But Papa...
Dey!
Just this once.
Please listen to me.
Be careful.
Go already!
Stop him, Ali.
Stop SATRIA.
Alicia!
SATRIA.
How...
I never thought that she would
sacrifice herself for you.
You...
What have you done?
I didn't do anything.
You're the one responsible
for your actions.
Why are you doing this?
Why not?
You've had no problem being
used in all your missions.
Why would it be wrong for me
to give you a mission
that's more meaningful?
For Cyberaya
to truly drive human progress,
all those who betray that ideal
must be eradicated.
Those who rule,
those who lead,
and those who defend their injustice.
Your mission to awaken SATRIA
is done.
Now the time has come
for me to liberate Cyberaya.
Fascinating.
Alicia's body shows
a heightened level of compatibility.
Not only that, my analysis shows
a more rapid neural activity in her.
I understand now.
This is why she could predict the future
with IRIS.
How unfortunate
that you didn't heed her warning.
Careful now.
You wouldn't want to hurt
your friend again, do you?
Where are they?
You're too late.
Give it up, Ali!
That's not Ali.
Ali's a little shorter,
like you.
The Island Protocol?
That won't be a problem.
We won't let you leave from here!
Ali!
What kind of disaster happened here?
Did you do all this?
You don't know how long
I've waited for this moment.
The moment that
you would kneel at my feet.
But wait.
You're not even kneeling anymore.
You're groveling!
I've won, Ali.
I've won...
So noisy.
Ali, get up.
We still have work to do.
We must save Cyberaya from Cero.
I don't know what to do.
I did my best.
I did what MATA told me to do.
I did everything I'm supposed to.
So?
Just because you tried your best,
nothing bad can happen?
You've been through this before.
You've defeated a lot of MATA's enemies.
Yes, everything seems a little messy now.
But cloudy skies don't always mean
a storm is coming.
Don't let their sacrifice
go to waste, Ali.
It's no use just sulking here.
You're MATA too?
Did MATA have no one else to recruit?
Got you.
Alicia is an exceptional agent, Ali.
She has known MATA
since she was a little girl.
And her abilities now
are way beyond her age.
You could learn a thing or two from her.
You're not bad.
You're not so bad yourself.
You've got instincts
and spirit.
Alicia!
And you don't even train much.
You're okay?
Congratulations, Alicia.
I knew you were going to win!
Agent Zain had a lot of faith
in both of us.
In you!
I want you to become the Super Agent
that we've always hoped for
from the IRIS project.
He sacrificed himself
so that we can continue to live.
We can't give up now.
We have to continue his fight!
I never thought that she would
sacrifice herself for you.
Stop him, Ali.
Stop SATRIA.
So are you just going to admit defeat
to that brat?
Or are you going to get up and...
I understand.
We still have work to do.
If I'd listened to you sooner,
Agent Rizwan...
Uncle Rizwan?
I don't need your apology.
I just need your help in this fight.
Okay, are you done?
Uncle Rizwan, a word?
What exactly is your plan?
How are we taking down that hunk of metal?
What, how should I know?
He's been using
just this thing to hack every--
Wait!
Over here, Dato'.
The safety bunker is just up ahead.
Dato'!
Excuse me.
Dr. Ghazali.
What is going on?
Cyberaya is under a critical threat.
You've all been brought here
for protection.
- What threat?
- I'll explain later, doctor.
We need to move now.
But my son?
What about my son?
We will take care of everything,
don't worry.
Amir, Elle.
SATRIA's location.
You two go on ahead.
We'll protect Dato' here.
Yeah, right.
If you're afraid to get your hands dirty,
what's the point in being a Pillar Leader?
Did you call for backup?
Yeah, I hope they'll show up.
How is it going?
Just a little more.
I'm using IRIS to reverse-engineer
Neonimus's program
and create its counter,
like an antivirus.
If we can plant it in SATRIA,
we'll be able to reset it.
No defenses?
That's strange.
Ali, find out where he is.
Finally.
I was hoping you'd get here in time.
This is the only chance I will give you.
Join me.
Or your lives end here.
Not if I destroy you first!
Do you know what the Island Protocol is?
It is the last resort.
If there is a Cyberaya invention
that becomes an uncontrollable threat,
all individuals of significance are
taken away to a secret island.
Off-grid.
It is clear they knew well in advance
that they were playing with fire.
But have they ever thought about
the safety of the civilians?
They may be able to cover their tracks.
But they won't be able to escape
the explosive power of Azurium here.
But if you do that,
Cyberaya will be devastated!
Not entirely.
A small price to pay for the greater good.
There, hurry!
Now that you know,
do you not see
how futile all your efforts were?
No, Dos! Alicia is trapped in there.
How can I possibly be defeated
by my own moves?
There is no point in delaying it.
Let's finish this!
Stop!
You've all been used...
For Cyberaya
to truly drive human progress,
all those who betray that ideal
must be eradicated.
Ali, what happened?
Ali!
Get up, we need to get out of here!
No.
We must stand our ground.
If not, the whole place will collapse
and trigger an explosion!
Need a hand?
SATRIA.
Please. Don't do this.
There's no point in pleading.
He only takes orders from me now.
Cero.
SATRIA will never stray
from its objective.
Unlike Uno,
Cinco,
or you.
You've made a big mistake
by showing up here.
What have you done to Ali?
He fell into his own trap.
Even if IRIS invades the SATRIA dimension,
he won't gain control
as long as I'm still here.
Why won't you admit defeat?
SATRIA is equipped with data
on every one of your abilities.
What hope do you even have of winning?
You're wrong!
I still have instincts.
I still have spirit.
SATRIA will never be able
to imitate a true human soul!
It is human nature
not to know their own limitations.
He's using data
from all the Pillar Leaders.
I will show you
how fragile the human soul can be.
Alicia!
What are you all doing here?
This is all your fault!
I can create a magnetic field
to interfere with his orientation.
Find an opening.
Dayang!
Alicia!
I've won, Ali. I've won!
I've won!
What are you going to do about it?
- Why...
- Sorry, Alicia.
It was an accident.
It's okay, my dear. Don't be sad.
You can rest now, Ali.
Alicia?
Is that really you?
Seriously, do I have
to babysit you all the time?
Alicia...
I should've listened to you.
Never mind, it's like I told you before.
You don't use your brain enough.
How amusing.
Unfortunately, you'll both
be entombed here.
How does he keep doing all this?
You can too, you know.
You're in Override Mode, remember?
Ali!
You're right!
I haven't been using my brain enough.
Cero.
Have you finished your homework?
What homework?
What homework, you say?
Ouch!
SATRIA...
is the perfect agent.
It is impossible to defeat me!
No point in being perfect
if you don't know about
our special attack!
SATRIA, KELEMBAI, DETECTIVE JEBAT
- Nice!
Over here, hurry!
Over there!
Ali!
I will never let you win!
You won't get away with this!
Thank you, Ali.
You have saved me time and again.
Alicia?
Alicia!
No!
Alicia.
Wake up.
Wake up!
Do you want me to do it?
It's okay.
I can do it.
It's just...
I don't know where it went wrong.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
If it weren't for Cero
pulling the strings...
I don't need the pep talk, Ganz.
What was I supposed to say?
Zain would've known
what's the right thing to do.
Don't worry.
There's a reason for everything.
I'm starting to see
why Amir and Elle were chosen to join us.
I didn't think you'd warm up
to them so quickly.
We will be taking over the project now.
What?
You want to go on with the project?
I disagree.
Unfortunately, that decision
is no longer in your hands.
Agent Dayang.
You are hereby suspended
from your role as Tekno's Pillar Leader.
Effective immediately.
Dato', you can't do this!
Why not?
Your creations have repeatedly
put Cyberaya in mortal danger.
You didn't think there
would be consequences?
How dare you!
- After all she's done for this city?
- Ganz.
I understand.
I accept whatever sanction
you feel is appropriate.
MATA will continue to operate
under the leadership
of three Pillar Leaders
until you are eligible
to be promoted again.
Or until I find
a more suitable replacement.
What a joke!
Is there a problem, Agent Ganz?
They would never understand
the weight of protecting Cyberaya.
If you think that I would continue
to serve without Dayang,
you must be out of your mind.
Good.
You've just made things easier for me.
I don't need anyone
who's uncooperative on my team.
Please exit the facility immediately
before you are taken away by force.
All right, students. Time's up.
Eyes off the paper.
Put your pencils down and press send.
This is your last paper,
so I hereby declare that
the finals are over!
Freedom!
Don't be so dramatic.
Here are your results!
Hey, how come your score is
better than mine?
Didn't you just copy off me?
I have to re-sit?
No!
Viktor, look.
- That's amazing.
- Can I see yours?
How many A's did you get?
We're the same?
We studied together.
Of course we'll get the same results.
That's fine, at least you didn't beat me.
Ali, what about you?
You've got more A's?
But how? When did you...
I lost to Ali?
That's awesome, congratulations!
Thank you.
I'm so glad the exams are over at last.
- Let's grab a bite at Mamak Maju.
- Sounds great.
Then let's hang out and play games!
I'm good. I'm a bit tired.
You guys go ahead. I'll call later.
Gosh, someone thinks
he's better than us now.
So, the exams are over.
You would've totally aced it as usual.
As for Neonimus, MATA still hasn't
been able to track him down.
But it looks like
he's leaving me alone for now.
Here.
This belongs to you.
Please wake up, Alicia.
You...
don't want to go on missions anymore?
Agent Geetha!
Move!
- Move aside, move!
- Where's Icha?
Where's Icha!
Icha!
I was so worried about you!
Are you okay?
She's in stable condition.
But...
Glad you're okay, Alicia.
What?
Who are all of you?
So, what now?
Are we supposed to just let
those clowns take over MATA?
We have more important matters
to attend to right now.
What could be more important...
Wait, where are we going?
Keep it down. Just follow me.
Are you getting something from here?
You can come out now.
Go on.
What do you want to tell us about Cero?
I managed to get this from Neonimus.
Right before he escaped.
It's all in here.
Their plans, communication logs.
Did you track him down?
Not yet, everything's encrypted.
I was hoping you could help.
You're not seriously thinking
of working with him?
If we show her this,
do you think she'd remember?
Oh, her records are in here.
Why is her history file locked?
Comot.
We still have work to do.