Dude, you have to
pick up your phone!
Todd?
Oh, my...
Okay, Todd. Uh...
Uh, hi. Um, I need help.
I need an ambulance.
My brother isn't breathing.
Uh, no, no, he's not--
he's not responding.
He's unconscious. I...
I don't know. I don't know.
I just--
I just found him like this.
Something is really wrong.
Go get it. Go get it.
Yeah. Fetch it up.
What's up, man?
What are you looking at?
Who's my bestest friend?
You? Is it you?
You're so cute! I could die!
Silly boy!
Aww! You're so cute!
What? Too scary for you?
Indy! Come on!
There's nothing there!
Look who's here!
Aww. There's my bestest friend.
Look at him. Look at him.
Look at that big boy.
Is that Papa?
Who's that?
He's free!
Oh, the boys are back!
Okay.
Nope. Stay here, boy.
Stay. Sit.
Good boy. Stay.
Hey, sis. Question for you.
Todd, what the hell
is going on?
- Nothing.
- I'm standing in your
empty apartment right now.
Oh, yeah.
That's why I called.
Um, I decided to
get out of town for a bit.
Do you know where
Grandpa hid the gate key?
You're at Grandpa's?
Do you know where
he hid the key or not?
Are you out of your mind?!
There is no way that
the doctor said this was okay!
They discharged me,
didn't they?
To go home, idiot!
You can't just go wherever
the hell you want anymore!
They keys, Vera.
Where are the keys?
- Why Grandpa's?
- Why not?
Exactly. It's available.
I'm not bothering anybody.
I needed a break.
This could be good for me.
Found 'em!
Okay, I need you close
in case something goes wrong.
I gotta go.
Call me when you calm down.
Wait! Wait, wait!
Just tell me that you're oka--
Enough of that.
Let's go.
There'll be a lot
of cleaning up to do
because of the weather
over the next couple of days.
It should help out
that at least Thursday
and Friday will be dryer.
More rain comes in
on Friday night...
Come on, bud. Let's go.
Come on, scaredy pants.
It's not that bad.
Come on, buddy.
You coming out or not?
There we go! Okay.
This way. Come on.
Come on, bud.
Okay.
Welcome home.
I know!
But it beats the hospital, right?
Wait here.
Ohh! Man!
Okay.
Ohh! Yes.
Something smells awful
down here.
Glad I don't have your nose.
Come on, bud.
So, how long have you
been planning this?
Planning? No planning.
It wasn't some big thing, Vera.
- The red light's on.
- I just needed to go.
Hm. No. Yeah.
That totally makes sense.
The cursed family house
is a great place to relax.
It's not really
how I remember it.
Oh, yeah. Creepier?
Not exactly. It's just...
You think "house in the woods"
sounds so peaceful.
Wait. Is that Indy?
No. Old home movie.
Grandpa's playing fetch
with Bandit.
You remember that dog?
Uh, kinda.
But didn't Grandpa
just have a ton of dogs?
Yeah, but they all
just kept running away.
Indy, on the other hand,
never leaves my side.
I can't poop without a witness.
Eww! Don't tell me that.
I don't need to know that.
Grandpa had a ton
of these VHS tapes.
Mostly this
and shitty horror films.
I think he was taping over them.
What's the point
of making a home
movie if you live alone?
No idea.
Can you tell there's
something wrong with him?
Wrong with who?
With Grandpa. On the tape.
Not at all. He seems happy.
Well, that's how Grandpa's
generation did it, you know?
Put on a happy face,
even when you're rotting
from the inside out, right?
I guess living in a haunted
house takes your mind off it.
The house
isn't haunted, Vera.
Oh, yeah? No one has
lived there for more
than a few weeks.
- Grandpa did.
- Yeah, and it killed him.
Look, uh...
you just have to promise me
that at the first sign
of relapse,
you're gonna get in that car
and you are coming back.
Okay. Sure.
But the rehab promised me...
Okay.
God damn it!
Hey, man.
What's going on?
Alright. Let's go.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
What?
Yeah. I know. It's creepy.
It's all my family
buried under here.
Come on.
They all died pretty young, too.
Whoa. Stay here, boy.
Here, boy.
What the hell
are you doing out here?
Uh, excuse me?
You should be more careful.
It's fox huntin' season.
I've got traps and snares
all over these woods.
Is that Mr. Downs?
Good to see you all grown up.
How long will you be staying
with us out here in the boonies?
Well, indefinitely.
I gave up my old place.
Taking over Grandpa's.
You staying in that place?
- Yeah. What?
- Nothing.
I just pray for you
after everything,
the way your grandpa died.
Well, we're gonna
make it our own.
Just gotta clear it out,
get the electric going.
I got an old generator
if you need it.
I'm just down the hill.
Come by any time you need help.
Your grandpa was out here
with his dog, too.
After we found his body,
we never did find that dog.
Am I crazy?
It's nice here, right?
Right?
Indy? Right?
Yeah. You get it.
Alright.
You're sure you know
how to set this up?
Electric for old houses
is pretty tough.
Yeah. I got it.
Thank you, though.
Okay.
Just make sure
you get it running
before this weather rolls in.
Not really safe when it's wet.
Yeah. No problem.
Have a good night.
Take care!
Just out of curiosity,
have you noticed Indy
acting weird lately?
What do you mean?
Weird-weird.
Like staring at nothing
or sniffing for something
he can't find.
- One more time. Vera...
- This is serious. Okay?
You're the one
that keeps telling me
that he won't leave you alone,
so I went online and...
Does it seem like
he's searching for something
that you can't see or
something that doesn't exist?
Oh, you mean being a dog?
Trust me.
There's nothing wrong with Indy.
Todd, I'm not worried there's
something wrong with Indy.
I'm worried there's
something wrong with you.
Okay? They-- They use dogs to
detect all kinds of stuff now.
Oh, yeah. I'm aware.
Like bombs, cocaine.
Yeah, or, like,
medical problems.
Hey. Uh...
Okay. Seriously.
Dogs' noses are very sensitive.
- Ah. Jesus Christ.
- They can detect all kinds
of stuff that tests miss.
And doctors have
even been using dogs--
Fuck.
Hey!
Knock it off!
There's nothing out there.
None of that, please. Okay?
Come on.
You silly goose. Huh?
For countless centuries,
mankind dwelled in the dark.
But he wasn't alone.
In caves all over the Earth,
we see evidence of
the most successful partnership
between any two species
on the planet.
With keener senses
than their human partners,
dogs protected cave dwellers
from unseen dangers
and alerted them
to the presence of predators.
Mankind has left the caves,
but the darkness
haunts us still.
Oh. Can I help you?
You want some?
...companions yield
to this primordial doom.
Pretty good.
Hm...
Not so fast, boy.
Come around here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
How's my boy doing?
Big, strong guy.
Hey, buddy, buddy,
buddy, buddy, buddy.
Who's a handsome man?
A big, handsome man!
Come on. Ooh! Hey.
Good. Good boy.
What? What's your problem?
Hey. Bud. Leave that alone.
Come on, Indy.
Come on. It's breakfast time.
Indy! Breakfast!
Okay. Sit.
Good.
Alright, Indy. You good?
Guard the house.
Not now, buddy.
Can you just go
lay down somewhere?
I said not now.
I said not now, bud.
I said give me a minute.
I said get the fuck out of here!
Quiet!
Stay.
Go on. Back upstairs.
Okay. Where was I? Uh...
All the taxidermy
I leave to my daughter,
the vegan.
And, uh,
to my grandson, Todd...
Everything else.
Six generations...
of one family
have lived in this place.
Lived and died.
I guess I'm next.
I should never have come here.
Are you still up for me
coming out this weekend?
When did we decide on that?
Oh. Well, you know,
I just thought that
it could be really--
You thought what?
I thought
that it would be nice.
You want to check in on me.
Well, isn't that
what sisters do?
I just want to help.
Can you not?
I-I'm not trying to nag you.
I just...
I really just want to
make sure that you're okay.
- You are so full of it.
- What?
Can I have one day where
I don't have to be a patient?
Can you help me with that?
- I'm not trying to make you--
Because whenever you call--
and you call all the time--
I'm just sitting here
dreading and waiting
for you to feel like
we've chatted enough
that you can ask one
of your inane questions.
You know what?
Maybe this would be helpful.
Let me save you
the trouble of asking
on your next ten phone calls.
I'm fine. I'm feeling fine.
Nothing's wrong.
And I'm staying.
Well, alright...
No, you're not sorry. Shut up.
That's what I want. Shut up.
Let's make a new rule.
Until I come to you
with some kind of crisis,
you just lay off.
Think you can handle that?
Yeah.
Great...
Run!
Indy?
Where you at?
Come on.
Indy!
Indy? You down here, boy?
Hello?
Indy?
How did you...
What the hell?
Come on, Houdini.
Okay. Hold still, bud.
It's almost over.
Oh, you smell like death.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. It's just too late.
What do you mean?
Maybe if you had come in
earlier, before it progressed.
So you're rejecting me
because I'm too sick?
Clinical trials have
strict entry requirements.
That's bullshit.
You don't even treat half
the people you say you will.
And if it works on me,
it'll definitely work, right?
Why are you trying
to reject someone
that wants to be
your guinea pig?
I'm sorry.
It just doesn't work like that.
God damn it!
What are you
doing there, Todd?
Nothing! Nothing.
Uh, wait. Actually...
Do you know if any hyssop
grows around here?
Honeysuckle root.
I'm collecting those things.
No. Sorry.
Never heard of them.
All good. All good.
I'll figure it out.
Well, figure it out over there
'cause you're getting
pretty close to where
I placed those fox traps.
You take care of yourself, son!
Be careful out here, boy.
Okay.
Coming through. Okay.
Now we focus.
That's perfect.
To the northwest corner.
And that-- that's it.
What are you looking at, boy?
It's alright.
Just the wind outside.
Sleep.
Sorry, bud.
Not tonight.
Hello?!
Hello?
It's okay, boy.
Shh.
God damn it!
No! You stay there!
Fuck.
Stay.
I told you to stay.
No.
Stay here.
Who's there?
Indy.
Ohh. I'm so sorry, boy.
How did you get back here?
Come on.
Come here. Come here.
What's going on?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What happened?
How did you do this?
How did you get up here?
Huh?
You're a good dog.
No.
Boy, you can't save me.
You gotta stay here.
Oh, God.
Hey!
Okay. Come on., Indy. Let's go.
Come on, Indy.