It's the under
mouse story of the century!
This riveting young driver
has come out of nowhere
and turned the whole
Grand Prix upside down!
And here she is!
She's weaving through the race
like a kid dodging
broccoli at dinner time.
Oh, no!
Out of nowhere, as always,
Edda's nemesis appears,
the mysterious Nachtkraab.
The suspense is unbearable.
And the shooting star seizes
her moment
and shoots off the ramp!
Edda has driven her way
into the history books
with her famous signature move!
The rocket ramp spin flip
sky ride.
The crowd goes wild celebrating
a new world champion!
Edda!
What are you doing?
The rocket ramp spin flip
sky ride?
You're supposed
to let the customers win.
Oh, come on.
Oops.
Sorry, dad.
Won't happen again.
That was awesome!
Please, get your head
outta the clouds, Edda.
We're barely holding
the park together.
Sorry.
- Free voucher.
- Yeah!
Here you go.
Enjoy that.
Oh, Edda, no!
Not the big prizes.
Sorry. Good race.
I said sorry.
Guess we're closing early?
Dad, I...
Oh, I'll be right back!
Oof!
Hey!
Oh. Hey, Edda!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's the fire?
Today's the Grand Prix
qualifier.
I gotta get to the TV.
Ay yay yay, I nearly forgot.
You better get to Brain Freeze.
Hey, Edda!
Whoo!
Huh?
Your future looks lumpy.
Hi, Rosa.
Edda, I see all in the ball.
Angry hamsters
wanna take you down,
one of your legs is
plotting against the other,
or you're having waffles later.
Oh, I hope it's the waffles,
but I'll keep an eye
out for those hamsters!
Your fate takes a frosty turn.
Hmm?
Or you're gonna have
a milkshake tonight.
I hope I didn't miss it.
Heated competition
coming into the home stretch.
It's still anybody's race.
Is this tractor--
Uh, hi. Can I have a chocolate
milkshake but with no chocolate?
You mean vanilla?
No chocolate.
Just hold the chocolate.
Uh, sure.
Out of nowhere,
and here comes
four time
Grand Prix champion, Ed.
He's making his move.
- He's passed Louis.
- Ed!
And Olivia and everyone!
He's taken them
on the inside, on the outside!
On all the sides!
Yes, that's right. Come on!
Ooh-hoo! Going into fifth.
He's coming up.
He's past Olivia.
Whoo-hoo-hoo! Watch him go.
Come on, Ed!
Ed qualifies
in pole position for the Grand Prix!
There he goes!
I said no vanilla.
Why are you so obsessed
with this Ed guy anyway?
I don't know where you got
the idea that I'm obsessed.
I mean,
he's great and everything,
but I'm not obsessed.
Edda, sweetheart. I get it.
But if my racing days at the
Grand Prix taught me anything
is that this race is nothing
but a flashy cash grab.
Real racing is an art,
and the Grand Prix
isn't real racing.
I'd make it real if I was in it.
You know I've got what it takes.
I could race in the Grand Prix
and I could win if I wasn't stuck here.
Edda, I promise you.
We'll get back to your
pro training someday.
It's just since mom passed...
Sorry, I didn't mean.
I love this park. I do.
And I know how much
it meant to mom.
Well, at least
the ghosts are still working.
I miss you, mom.
It's a terribly sad situation.
Really, sir.
So many people borrow money
and they just can't afford to pay it back.
Isn't that right, mittens?
Painfully right, Fluffy.
I can pay you back.
Just not right now.
That's the thing though,
isn't it, sir?
The longer you take
to pay us back,
the more money you owe us.
It's a vicious circle,
isn't it, Mittens?
Ferociously vicious circle,
Fluffy.
One week.
Give me one more week
and I'll have your money.
One week.
You think this dump
is gonna bring in
that kind of money
in seven days?
I've been in this business
a long time.
I can do it.
All right then, prove me wrong.
But let me remind you
of our agreement, sir.
If you don't pay, uh,
what do we do
to his fair ground then,
Mittens?
The old rip and scrap, Fluffy.
Indeed.
We rip it up
and sell it for scrap.
You heard?
Why didn't you tell me?
Edda.
I'm just,
I couldn't lose the park.
Your mom,
it's all we have left of her.
- I had to...
- You're not gonna lose our home because we are gonna save it.
Edda, if there was a way
I'd have found it by now.
No one wants to come
to the fairground anymore.
Yes, they do.
They just don't know it yet.
If you've got an idea,
I'm all ears.
Okay, I don't have one just yet,
but when I do it,
it will be brilliant.
I look forward to hearing it.
Oh, this is all my fault.
If I hadn't been
so distracted by racing.
If I'd, if I'd
focused more on the park.
I won't let us
lose the park, mom.
Even, even if it means
letting go of my dream.
Wow.
Huh? Edda,
get over here quickly, mira.
The fireworks
have started already.
Oh, those Grand Prix folks
sure know
how to throw
a pre-race party, huh?
Well, it must be nice.
Edda, you'll get your
chance to race someday.
You don't know that.
Oh, yes, I do.
I'm the fortune teller.
I know that you will race
in the Grand Prix.
Just like I know that...
aquatic elves have been
stealing your junk mail.
That's it!
What's it? Aquatic elves?
What are they?
Fish or little guys?
Junk mail!
There are folks
from all across Europe at that party, right?
If I hand out park flyers
and get enough people to show up,
maybe my dad
can pay off his loan.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm gonna fix this.
Welcome to the Grand Prix
of Europe.
What a day. What a city.
What a tower. What a party.
What a race!
You can feel the air
sizzling with excitement.
Aye, Peri?
Well said, old boy.
And now, introducing
former Grand Prix winner
and Grand Prix League president,
Cindy!
Thank you Enzo,
and thank you, Paris.
Today we celebrate
the best drivers
all across the world
ahead of tomorrow's race.
The best race in the world.
The Grand Prix.
Why watch racing
when you can come to our park and race for real?
Our track makes the Grand Prix
look like a driving lesson with grandma.
So, are you ready to welcome
your Grand Prix stars?
They're gonna blow our minds
in France, Germany
and Switzerland,
Italy and England.
How about we meet the drivers?
First up the goat
who knows no fear.
It's Bockli!
Hello, Paris!
Cindy, I have a gift for you.
How wonderful!
A luxury box
of exquisite Swiss...
Cheese for everyone.
Cheese.
Give it up for Bockli!
Next up is the bear
who always comes in second,
but is always a great
sport about it, Magnus!
Naturally, Magnus
is starting position
in tomorrow's race
will be number two.
Yes, yes. Thank you!
I'm just happy to be here
and be part of the...
And finally, he is the
four time Grand Prix champion
and on his way
to becoming a living legend
if he makes it
to number five, it's Ed!
Yay.
Our youngest driver.
And fastest.
I love you, Ed!
I love you, Ed.
I love you too!
Ed, anything you want
to say to your fans?
Sure.
I'd like to compliment them
on their excellent taste.
I just died.
Ladies and gentlemen, Ed.
Have you ever seen
anyone else as cool?
I haven't.
And I hang out with racing
drivers in a literal zeppelin.
Oh, no!
No, no, no. Come back!
Let's have a look
at the other drivers.
Come back!
Oh, its Ed's car.
Well, there's no harm
in looking or touching.
Wow.
As long as I don't...
Ed! Ed!
Can I get a selfie, please?
Will you sign my face?
Hi. Hi there. Hi.
It's real pleasure.
Thank you so much.
- Hey.
- You are too kind.
This is-- My car?
- Huh?
- Excuse me. Sorry.
Ed! Ed, please!
Look somebody
more famous than me.
More famous?
Can I smell them?
No, no, no! Hey!
This is unbelievable!
Wait!
Stop that car!
Whoa, ah!
Whoo-hoo!
Who the high octane tank
are you?
Oh, my gosh.
You're my greatest fan!
I mean, I'm your biggest hero!
I mean, uh!
Get out of my car.
You're so different on TV.
Your real life voice
is so angry.
Stop this car and get out!
Okay. Okay.
Uh, where's the off switch?
Push that!
Uh, eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
I pick you!
I can't believe
I'm driving with the Ed!
I can't believe this either.
Drive back to the garage.
Okay!
How did you do that?
Oh, that's nothing compared
to that time in Madrid
when you were behind Nachtkraab
and you took that ramp.
Okay, I get it.
You know my work.
Can I show you
just one more thing?
No! back to the garage now.
Whoo!
I just saved Ed's life
with my driving skills.
I'm a hero.
Oh, you're a monster!
Cheese balls.
Do you see what you've done?
I can't drive like this!
Thanks to my biggest
fan, ah, I can't drive!
Then let's go to a hospital
and get you fixed up.
I'll drive.
No. No hospitals.
An injury is a disqualification.
Please, no one can know.
Okay, but you need help.
Oh, I have an idea.
Here we are. Home sweet home.
Wait, you live here?
Uh-huh.
On purpose?
Any fried food sludge gets
on these shoes, I'm sending you the bill.
Huh? This is the worst
breakage I've ever seen.
Your arms like a noodle.
I'm over here.
Ah, there's your arm.
You shouldn't tip your
limbs in such dark places.
Oh, congratulations.
It's not broken.
But un-congratulations.
It's badly sprained.
Quite painful, probably.
Oh, you think?
No driving for a few weeks.
Weeks?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have to drive.
I have to drive tomorrow.
Are you even a doctor?
Better than that?
I'm a fortune teller.
I foresee frustration
and annoyance in your future.
No, this isn't fair!
My prophecy is confirmed.
Hey, Edda.
It's tough
to save the park, aye?
Oh! Ow!
You're not Edda!
How dare you not recognize
the world's greatest racer!
Huh, we do kinda look alike.
Not our faces,
but same size, same build.
Same little piece of hair
that sticks up.
Ah, ow!
You, you, you weirdos!
You've ruined my life.
Okay, this guy
is coco like a loco. All right, Edda.
Why are we helping him again?
He's a tortured genius.
He can't be great and sweet.
Well, you are.
Actually, I'm great, sweet
and a genius.
I'll drive
in Ed's place tomorrow.
Do you really think that you...
Wait, if we look alike,
but you can't drive and I can.
No, no, no. No way.
I'm just saying
I could take your place.
Who would know?
I'd be wearing your helmet.
I am more than a helmet.
I am the world's
greatest racing driver.
No one would fall for it.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are right.
It was a stupid idea.
You should just drop out.
Give up
on that fifth championship.
I mean, who cares
if you become a living legend?
I care.
All right.
But I guide you through
with an earpiece.
You do exactly what I tell you.
Of course, of course.
Whatever you want.
Also, you give me
half your prize money.
Huh? What?
I'm saving your career.
You endangered my career.
I need that money. We need it.
If I don't save the park,
there's no deal.
Okay. Okay, fine.
As long as I never have to come
near any of you ever again.
I can't believe I'm gonna
drive in the Grand Prix.
No, neither can I.
Yeah!
Worst idea in history.
I'm gonna save the park, Mom.
My way.
Ooh, my muffins.
And now my sabotage.
When an undetectable
quick drying grease slick
hits the course that stuck up
Ed won't know what hit him.
Race fans,
only a few hours to go
until the start of their
biggest race of the year
with the 40 best drivers
on the planet!
But they don't just
have to beat each other.
They also have to survive
a gauntlet of traps,
each more fiendish
than the last.
Welcome to the Grand Prix
of Europe!
Let's see if we can grab
some of our drivers.
Magnus. Hey, Magnus!
Hello there, Cindy.
Lovely to see you as always.
So, Magnus, you haven't made it
to the top of the podium yet.
You know, for me, it's about
being part of the action,
not about winning, because...
is absolutely
not about the winning.
We're gonna try anything
different, Magnus?
And he tricks up
those furry sleeves?
Oh, oui, oui, oui, oui, oui.
Do tell us. How do you plan
to underwhelm us all today?
Ed, any thoughts
from our front runner?
Hi.
Oh, and who's this all cozied up
to the Grand Prix
diehard lone mouse.
Uh.
Uh, yeah.
This is my biggest super fan.
They won a contest for
the VIP meet and greet
lasting the entire
duration of the Grand Prix.
And you know
I'm all about my fans.
How did I not know
about this contest?
Oh, okay. Any thoughts
from Ed's luckiest fan?
- I...
- Nope.
Wow the zeppelin
is bigger than I thought.
Oh, there's Olivia.
Are she and Louie
really sworn enemies or is it all just an act?
I have no idea.
Bockli!
Oh, play it cool. Play it cool.
Is he as nice in real life?
I dunno.
Nachtkraab, the night raven.
Is it true he's a servant
of darkness
and sworn to destroy
all who's stand in his way?
How would I know?
Well, you've been racing
with these people for years.
Don't you know
anything about them?
No. And I plan on keeping it
that way.
I've been watching you, Edward.
You've lost your edge.
You've become too confident.
Cocky people make mistakes,
and people who make
mistakes have accidents.
That was totally a threat.
I still really want
his autograph though.
Eighteen hours
until the first race in Paris.
So where's next on the tour?
Hmm, graceful.
Just because you're dressed
like me,
doesn't mean you can be me.
I bet I can.
You're on.
♪ No, you won't ♪
♪ Until you try ♪
- ♪ You'll never feel happy ♪
♪ You'll never feel happy ♪
♪ Until you try ♪
- ♪ You'll never feel happy ♪
-
♪ Until you try ♪
♪ You'll never feel happy ♪
- ♪ Until you try ♪
- Easy.
♪ You'll never feel happy ♪
♪ Until you try ♪
♪ You'll never feel ♪
So, you really are obsessed
with me.
I think I've got everything.
Even down
to how you scratch your butt.
Were you born this annoying
or did you take classes?
Wait, was that a genuine smile?
Oh, is your face okay?
Right, yeah.
Anyway, I will direct
your every move
via this earpiece.
What for?
I know how to drive like you.
Hang back, but not too far.
Wait for inspiration,
then seize your moment
and zoom to the front.
Wrong! Inspiration?
You think I wait to feel
something so I can make a move?
No, I feel nothing.
Ow!
Well, you felt that.
And nothing I do in a race
is based on emotion.
Everything I do
is meticulously pre-planned
based on an in-depth
analysis of my opponents,
their vehicles, the course,
the weather conditions.
So complicated. Sheesh.
Why don't you just drive?
Because I am not a driver.
I am a winner.
Drivers, get ready!
It's time.
Oh, yes. This way.
The Grand Prix of Europe,
Race One.
Are you as excited
as I am, Peri?
Whoa. Settle down there,
old boy.
Give my ears a rest.
The racing
hasn't even started yet.
Now, let's break it down.
There'll be four races,
each one in a different country.
Forty drivers start today.
But in each race,
they last 10 drivers
to the finish line
will be eliminated,
which means
only 10 drivers will be left
to compete in the final race
in London next week.
But these aren't
your grandma's races.
Isn't that right, Cindy?
That's right, Enzo.
These action packed contests
come with pulse pounding,
over the top traps, tricks,
and treachery on the tracks.
Yes, indeedy.
And Cindy is the diabolical
wizard behind it all.
And you won't believe
the obstacles I've crafted for today's race.
So, let the pandemonium begin.
I can do this.
No, I can't.
No, no, no. I can't.
Why are you breathing
like that?
You better be okay.
I'm great.
I'm, I'm perfect.
Your voice is shaking.
Shaking with excitement.
Remember, all you've
got to do to move on
to the next race is
finish in the top 30 cars.
We just need to stay outta
the last 10.
Oh, boy,
this is really happening.
And last but never
least in pole position, Ed!
That's you. Oh, I mean me.
That's us.
Oh, mousetrap.
Drivers, are you ready
for the 50th Grand Prix
of Europe?
Then let's get
this party started!
So, the 40 drivers are lined up on the starting grid.
It's animal and machine
in perfect harmony.
Uh.
Um.
The red one.
A thousand
kilometers of high octane,
hyped up havoc on the highway.
These are the craziest
races Europe has ever seen.
Go!
Wa-hoo-hoo!
I must be dreaming.
I'm driving in the Grand Prix!
Hello, Ed.
You seem a bit nervous.
Be careful.
One mistake
can cost you a victory.
Winning is not the most
important thing. Right, Ed?
Well, in this case, it is.
What's up, folks?
Can you tell me one thing?
How do I look from behind?
Very nice, Olivia.
Ed's being passed
by Olivia, Magnus, Bockli,
and now every one else.
What a move
on the inside by Louie!
Great use of barriers.
And here's Richard.
That ain't Pond. Richard Pond.
Close behind the surprisingly
ever helpful Bockli
Your tires are smoking, Richard.
Probably because
I'm going so fast.
You sure
your hand brake isn't on?
I knew that.
Part of my strategy.
Back of the front,
Louie is being hounded by Wolf.
It's high speed and low cunning.
Ah.
A wolf in sheep's clothing.
Watch your line.
They're passing you.
It looks like Ed
might be suffering some sort of mechanical issue.
It's a masterclass in losing.
No more cars
are getting past me.
True. Seeing as you're
now in last place.
Oh.
How's it looking
up there, Cindy?
It's looking way
too easy, Enzo.
The atmosphere's electric.
Feel the crackle
of anticipation.
Wait, that's not anticipation.
It's lightning!
Actual lightning!
Did it get dark all of a sudden?
Ooh, shocking.
Forget the lightning.
Just focus on the road ahead.
There's an opening ahead.
Now's your chance.
To do what, get fried?
I can't see anything.
I'll guide you.
Get into the middle of the road,
you'll glide right through them.
Whoa.
Would you look at this?
Ed's powering on
fast as grease lighting,
like a bolt out the blue.
It worked!
You sound surprised.
And here comes Ed.
Can he pull it back after
that terrible start?
He's bearing down on Magnus.
Now all you have to do is,
Donuts?
Why are you doing donuts?
I don't know what's happening.
I do.
A sloppy driver is happening.
You're losing.
Which means I'm losing.
And I don't lose.
Is Magnus
about to take the lead?
Is this the moment
he finally wins, oh, of course he isn't!
Victory goes to Nachtkraab!
Oh!
And superstar Ed
will be all the way back.
Yeah!
In last position.
Let's have
a look at the highlights.
I see victory.
Oh, geez,.
I can't be sure.
Sorry, got distracted by Ed's
terrible uninspired driving.
So is this the secret TV
watching stand or the ice cream stand?
Um, both?
Turn it off.
Where is Edda, anyway?
There is no Edda at the moment.
Okay, very helpful. Thanks.
Ah, brain freeze!
As advertised.
This is all because you did
that stupid stunt and lost control.
There was something on the
course that made me spin out.
Yeah. A bad driver.
It, it wasn't on purpose.
It, it was...
Oh, spinning round
and round for no reason.
That doesn't make it okay.
Oh, oh, no. You were right.
I can't do this.
What is this? What's happening?
I'm not up to it.
I'm not good enough.
Hey.
That's not true.
Well, not completely true.
Well, no, no, no, no.
I didn't mean it.
You, you can do this.
I honestly, desperately
need you to believe that.
Maybe I am just
a fairground nobody.
Maybe my dream
should have stayed a dream.
There, there?
Uh.
Look, take some time.
Take as much time as you need.
I'll give you some space
while I go
and make excuses
for your terrible driving.
Oh, wow.
Roger, my magnificent
machine is crinkled.
Crinkled!
Are you sure it's not your
giant ego that's crinkled?
Guys, my car's leaking
a strange liquid.
That's
windscreen cleaner, honey.
A cleaning
team to Richard, please.
Hey, you. Super fan!
You star drove like day
old derriere out there!
Pourquoi?
I don't know maybe I,
uh,.
I, he just wasn't as good
as he thought he was.
No one's as good as
that chap thinks he is.
Well, I'm, I'm sure it was
just a mechanical problem.
The next race will go better.
I promise. He promises.
Your hero should be careful.
Very careful.
- Yes.
- You got that right.
He should.
So, you're the fan
who can't get enough of Ed?
Yeah, yeah. He's great.
You haven't spent much
time with him yet, have you?
There you are.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
I was just talking to...
And now you are finished.
Ed, if you ever need
to talk about anything.
Oh, I won't.
What were you doing
talking to the other drivers?
You'll blow our cover.
Stay away from them.
Why are you so mean to everyone?
The others hang out
and help each other.
Yeah, where's that got them?
Behind me.
Great drivers don't need help.
- Want me to get that?
- No.
See, I'm absolutely fine.
But don't you ever get lonely?
I have thousands of fans.
How could I possibly be lonely?
You better be ready for this.
I've studied the route,
the other drivers,
their bad habits,
Cindy's favorite obstacles
and Bockli's top three
flavors of ice cream.
Bockli?
I'm on the lookout
for a new role model.
Yeah, but Berkeley?
Welcome to the German
and Swiss Bliss
you don't wanna miss.
All through the Alps, forests,
mountains, alpine villages
and snow, snow,
and you guessed it,
even more snow.
It's so beautiful.
But things could get ugly
if our racers
can't handle today's obstacles.
Today I wanna be in the top 10.
Losing doesn't feel good,
does it?
Maybe you'll listen to me today.
I guess I should.
I mean, you're on my pajamas
for a reason.
I'm on your what?
Ten have fallen.
Thirty remain.
Who am I going
to knock out today?
As we wait for the signal, Peri,
do you think Ed will
be back in form today?
Or will his slump spell doom
for his hopes of a fifth win?
Absolutely.
Another controversial opinion
from Peri.
That's why he makes
the big bucks.
Now, just stay behind
the cars in front of you.
We'll make a move later.
For now, just drive.
Drivers, get ready.
It's race time!
And the drivers are off!
First, we race through
the beautiful forest.
Oh, we lost one already.
Oh, whoa.
You know what they say, folks,
when you're lost in the forest,
make sure you stick to the path.
Now we go through the mountain
tunnels into the Swiss Alps.
So Cindy, what's in store
for our drivers today?
They're about
to find out, Enzo. Haha.
Oh, pretty.
Ah, pretty dangerous!
Oh, Cindy, that is not cool!
That's cold.
Oh, I don't like this.
You're not supposed to like it.
You are supposed to avoid it.
Oh, great advice!
Richard, what are doing?
Ha ha. It's okay.
It's all a trick.
They're not real snow balls!
Chill out and enjoys
the ride, my friend.
Don't mind if cocka-doodle-doo!
It looks like
our favorite rooster
has activated his booster!
Oh, wait a second.
What is this?
It stopped!
What's happening now?
Out of the way road hog,
beep beep.
You got a new
trick up your sleeve, Cindy?
It's not me,
Enzo, but I like it.
Did you see that?
I think someone's
interfering with the race.
Maybe that's why I spun out
in Paris.
You're imagining things.
It seems like I've got a
very powerful imagination!
I gotta shake these things.
Ignore it. Just drive.
That's easy for you to say.
It's gaining on me!
That's it. I can fix this.
No, no. No stunts!
I call that move the
rocket spin flip sky ride!
Find a line on
the left. You'll make it!
And the ice cold stunt driving
has put Ed back
amongst the contenders.
Ha, dunno what's got
into this Ed clown
but he's driving better
than he has in years.
But there is no Ed
at the moment.
This is bananas.
I can't breathe.
Magnus and Nachtkraab
are neck and neck.
Could the bear
finally break his streak
and actually win a race?
Yes. Yes.
Yes!
Unbelievable!
No!
This is why
I love the Grand Prix.
Nobody could have seen that
coming.
Peri is losing it!
Yes. We made it!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, so nice to be back home.
With my favorite, cheese fondue.
Hmm.
I love fondue.
I just wish
it wasn't so painful to eat.
Did you see how amazing
I was out there today
with those snow boulders?
Sweetie, they're
called hashtag sno-lders.
Get with the time.
Whatever they're called,
they seem to have a mind
of their own.
What's that called?
When inanimate objects
suddenly come alive?
Starts with an S.
Sabotage.
Uh, I think he meant sentient,
Ed head, not sabotage.
You think there was foul play?
But who would do that?
I'll tell you who.
Please do.
Hmm?
I, uh, I don't want
to disturb your meal.
Are you sure
you don't want to join us?
Nachtkraab's sabotaging
the race. I know it.
Edda, take a breath. Sit down.
He's evil and he's got a
very threatening cheese fork.
Relax. It's just the
pressure of the Grand Prix.
It's completely normal to
be paranoid and delusional.
Is it?
No. I'm trying
to make you feel better.
You told me to be nice, right?
Yeah. Okay.
I mean, I guess it's a start.
Not a good start,
but you're trying.
I'm not paranoid though.
Hmm. Nachtkraab
is up to something.
I know it.
Oh, oh.
I said Rocky Road Ice cream,
not sockey road.
I'm terribly sorry.
Jorge! What did I say
about taking off your socks at work?
Nobody wants to see your hooves.
Rosa? Why are you doing this?
Where's Jorge?
Wow. Look at that
beautiful move.
Did you see that? Ha.
Why do you even bother
hiding the TV at this point?
Honestly, you're as bad as Edda.
Say, where is Edda?
Laundromat.
- Gym?
- Yeah.
She's, she's doing that, uh,
dirty laundry workout.
Hey, only one person
I know can pull off a hairpin back flip dash.
Oh, that wasn't
a hairpin back flip dash.
Uh-uh. No way.
It was a wheeze moth
undercarriage sachet.
- No.
- Hm-mm.
But even if it was,
I also only know one person can pull off
a wheeze moth
undercarriage sachet.
My daughter.
I need to go and polish
my nose ring collection. Yeah, I got one of them.
And I need to get my
crystal ball.
Freeze.
Ah, nice going in you
big mouth pot house.
Okay, out with it.
What's going on?
What are you up to?
And Erwin has taken the win.
Can anyone stop this mouse?
And today, Erwin,
the legendary driver...
Dad.
is leaving
the Grand Prix of Europe.
Talented racer. Friend of yours?
Actually, he's my, uh.
Uh, no. I don't know him.
Are you following me?
No, no, no, no.
I just happen to be walking in the same direction
and slightly behind you.
That's all.
Good.
People who don't stay in their
own lane tend to get hurt.
Wait, and my daughter
has actually been racing as Ed this whole time?
Hmm-mm. Yes.
And you saw everything
you just told me in your crystal ball?
Yes, I know all that
just as I know a peculiar
shade of blue
is going to ruin
your lunch late next week.
Impressive.
Especially since
that's a grapefruit, Rosa.
Jorge, just because
you are a bull
doesn't mean
you can give me any. - Hey.
As a bull, I find that
a little offensive. Okay?
But anyway, the truth,
Edda told us all of it
and wanted us to keep
it a secret from you.
Oh, please don't hate us.
We're about to lose the park
and she runs off the drive in the Grand Prix of Europe?
Hey, Rosa,
anything in that crystal ball of yours about us being fired?
And she didn't feel
like she could
even tell her own father
because who am I kidding?
I wouldn't listen anyway,
all I think about is the business.
We should start packing, right?
No one's getting fired.
We're her family.
We should be together,
shouldn't we?
Well, shouldn't we?
- Yes.
- Of course.
I thought
you were asking yourself.
Yes. Together is better.
We should. Then it's settled.
And more importantly,
I am not missing
my daughter driving in the Grand Prix of Europe.
- Would you?
- Of course not.
Hm-mm.
But how are we gonna get there?
It's really far.
My snow-lder plan failed.
But after this next trick,
I'm bound to win.
My career will be on fire.
Oh, no. Actual fire!
Everyone stay calm.
We have everything
under control.
There is no danger.
What the heck is going on?
We're all gonna die!
Um, your mic is still on.
Oh. Ha-ha!
We're all gonna die
trying to stop this so no one die dies.
Ha-ha-ha!
Magnus, what is going on here?
Oh, just a little baking mishap.
I accidentally
burned some muffins.
The worst part, I was
making them for all of you.
Aw.
Hmm.
What's this?
It's my muffin
icing caramalizer.
It's what accidentally
caused the fire.
I don't see any burnt muffins.
They disintegrated.
It's the settings on
this crazy caramelizer.
Must be faulty.
Ow. Faulty.
See?
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Okay, crisis over.
Back to your suites, everyone.
Thank you all.
Now I think I lie down
and take a good long nippy nap
to be ready for tomorrow.
Good call.
You'll need plenty of rest
to almost come in first again.
I'll show them.
No more Mr. Nice bear.
Ed and Nachtkraab
are going down hard.
And then I will
finally be victorious.
Ow.
It's him!
What are you talking about?
Nachtkraab is sabotaging
the race.
First he threatens me
and now he's trying to put
the blame on poor Magnus.
Where's your proof?
Well, I don't have
any actual evidence,
but what I do have
is better than that.
What?
A really strong feeling
I'm right.
So we have
to do something about it.
How about this?
Let's focus on this next race,
and if there's any hint
of sabotage this time,
I promise to help you find
whoever it is.
Really? You'd do that?
Whether I like it or not,
we're a team.
Thank you.
You really promise?
Hm-mm.
Okay, because if you don't,
I swear, when I get home,
I'll replace all your
posters with Bockli's.
Okay, that's going too far.
And I'll ask him
to sign all my pillow cases.
Buckle up folks,
with 20 racers
revving their engines, there's
no time to stop at admire
the gorgeous Italian coast.
Don't overtake yet.
He's right there.
Remember our deal.
Do as I say.
This is so frustrating.
How do you think I feel?
Hmm.
Vain? Big-headed?
Worried about
your receding hairline?
My hair is thick and lustrous.
Made you check though.
Is it true what they say, Peri?
Is Italy really
the land of romance?
Whoa. Easy there, Peri.
Children are watching.
So, Cindy, it's about
time for some obstacles.
What are we gonna see
from you on the tracks today?
How about some sea monsters?
Wow, they really need
to cut Cindy's budget.
Whoa!
Whoa.
Nice driving!
Ed, is that a compliment?
Enjoy it.
There won't be another one.
Now keep left into this hairpin.
Whatever you say, boss.
Ooh, I went left.
Left him in the dust.
Oh, nice try, fish breath!
That's off the scale.
You are kraken me up.
In the lead,
a thrilling clash unfolds
between Nachtkraab and Magnus.
Okay, team
captain, what's the play?
You know what, Edda?
Do your thing.
You've got this.
Seriously? You mean it?
Don't make me say it twice.
If I swallow any more pride,
I'll choke.
Okay, watch this.
And Ed suddenly enters
the scene
ready to shake things up!
Go, Ed!
Surely the race
belongs to one of these three.
Oh, what's that smell?
Smells familiar.
What are you doing?
It's, it's not me!
It's like I'm being blown back
by an invisible burst
of air or something!
What the.
Nachtkraab!
It's got to be you.
Is between Magnus
and Nachtkraab!
The bears slipping behind.
He's gotta be raving mad.
No!
Nachtkraab comes in first!
What are doing?
How did you come third?
That was the worst.
But, but where are you going?
Stop it.
This is against the rules.
So is sabotage.
There's gotta be some sort
of jet or air cannon or...
Didn't you promise you'd help me
if there was even a hint
of sabotage?
The only saboteur
I see right now is you.
You may want to stop
doing that to my car
because if Cindy sees you.
My office now!
Oops. Too late.
Magnificent job, Jorge.
This is the best thing
you've built
since the amusement park rides.
Gracia.
Of course it did help that I got
to build it using the amusement park rides.
And just in time
to make it to the final race.
Rosa, do you foresee any
disaster on the water for us?
None.
But it looked like the earth
got a few more equator lines. Hmm.
London. Here we come!
Whoo-hoo!
Ed, Ed, Ed, Ed, Ed, Ed, Ed!
Look, I get it's
a stressful time.
Though most people deal
with stress
by overeating or nail biting.
Not tearing apart
an opponent's race car
in front of 50,000 fans!
You are just lucky as the
biggest star of the racing world
that I need you
as much as you need me.
Give me your word this
will never happen again.
In the final race, you will have
to start in the penalty box.
Meaning you'll start one minute
later than everyone else.
Is that clear?
Well, well, well, if
it isn't the Ed head.
You must be super bummed.
Cindy's still chewing
him out in there, no?
Now that you've spent
time with him, sweetie,
you can tell us.
Ed's a real pain, right?
Yeah.
What's it like to work
for such a, how you say,
radioactive poo poo head.
Hey, hey. Come on, guys.
Don't put him
on a spot like that.
There's a rumor
the reason Ed doesn't talk
to anyone is because he's
embarrassed about his breath.
Supposedly, he smells
like foot cheese.
Is that true?
One minute behind. One minute!
And for what? Some crazy
hunch about Nachtkraab?
It wasn't a crazy hunch.
It was a a very strong feeling.
Feelings.
Feelings don't win races.
I told you that.
And now they're gonna
lose me the championship.
I know, I'm sorry,
but I'll find a way to fix it.
I know I can.
No, you won't.
I'm fed up
with you fixing things.
Give that back.
What's this?
Right now!
I'm your friend.
I don't have friends.
You're right. You don't.
That guy thinks
his exhaust doesn't stink!
So arrogant.
Has he always been this
weird and butt-headed?
And what's with that sketchbook?
The arrogance I can
only guess is a shield
to keep people
from getting close.
But the sketchbook
I know quite well.
Ed grew up in an orphanage.
It was actually
a pretty happy place
and all the kids became friends.
Who's the best road trip crew
by far?
♪ We are. We are! ♪
Who sticks together
just like glue?
♪ We do! We do! ♪
Ed and his fellow orphans
all dreamed
of becoming
a racing team together when they grew up.
We'll be
the best racing team ever.
But then, as each of his
friends found a new home,
Ed's dream team became
smaller and smaller until
it wasn't even a team at all.
Who's the best road trip crew
by far?
♪ We are. We are ♪
Ed decided from that day forward
to not depend on anybody
except himself.
How do you know all of this?
Because I was one of them.
When Ed and I met years
later on the circuit,
he wanted nothing to do with me.
And he still doesn't.
What?
Ha ha!
Healed.
Time to drive
Poor Ed.
That smell. I know that smell.
This is the smell
I smelled during the race.
And that means the smell
should lead me right to
Nachtkra!
Magnus' suite?
Whatever it is,
it's here somewhere.
You're number two.
You did fine.
So, so.
First place, just kidding.
Oh, who am I kidding? There's
no way it's Mag-.
A secret laboratory?
I knew it.
Invisible grease, Paris race.
Air blaster, Italy race.
The same smell.
I was so right
and I was so wrong.
Magnetic drone, London.
This must be the next
sabotage he's planning.
I need to get this to Cindy.
Oh!
I-- I must have lost my key.
Hey, it happens to everybody.
I must get in there.
No problem.
Just a second.
Thank you.
I could have sworn I had
my key with me when I left.
My pleasure.
What?
Everyone loves Magnus,
the good old bear
who always comes second.
But tomorrow
I'll be second to none!
Okay, I admit I was
wrong about Nachtkraab.
He's not a cheater.
That's very big of you.
And why did you decide that?
Because I now know Magnus is!
Magnus?
Even I like Magnus.
Oh, he is the last one
I'd suspect.
You've been hanging around
car exhaust too long.
Ed, Ed! I saw it. Something.
I don't know what Magnus'
final sabotage will be,
but now I know
he has one planned.
Hm-mm. You're fired.
You bet I'm fired! Fired up!
I feel so alive.
This time I saw proof
with my own eyes.
No, you are fired fired.
I don't need you
to drive as me anymore.
See?
So.
Oh, that's great.
But what about saving
the park, and...
Once I win, you'll be paid
accordingly for your time.
Now, if you'll excuse, I need
to focus on today's race.
It's not about the money.
Well, well, some of it's
about the money.
But how can you be like this
after all we've been through?
I thought we were getting close.
You are a good guy deep
down, very deep down.
But it's there.
I believed in you, Edda.
You just couldn't let go of
this whole conspiracy thing.
You could have been
one of the greats,
not off the charts once in
a lifetime great like me,
but, you know, regular great.
Don't do to me what all your
orphan friends did to you.
You don't wanna close
that door, Ed.
Maybe on my dream,
I can deal with that.
But not on our friendship
or any friendship
in your case, do you?
Welcome to London
and the thrilling final race
of the Grand Prix!
Outta 40 drivers,
there's only 10 left.
And I've gotta say, Peri,
it's been
an unusual one this year.
What do you think about it all?
Whoa! Chillax Peri!
I've never seen you so excited,
but who can blame you?
Let's go now to Cindy,
who'll take us through
today's thrilling route.
That's right, Enzo.
We've prepared a wild one.
Drivers will first encounter
Tower Bridge,
then onto Big Ben,
and beware drivers don't
let this bus catch you.
Oh, nein. They really
need to cut Cindy's budget.
The race is about to start.
Look, there she is.
Edda!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Edda. Huh?
Edda?
Dad, fancy seeing you here.
Jorge and Rosa told me
you are driving for Ed.
And you are not mad?
Of course I'm mad at myself.
I just wanted to keep you
at home a little longer.
You are a brilliant driver,
Edda.
I should have supported you.
And that's what I'm
going to do from now on.
Can you forgive me?
I got everything so wrong.
Maybe I'm not cut out
for racing.
Of course you are,
talking of which, why aren't you in your car?
I kind of got fired,
made some big mistakes
and now Ed's in danger.
They all are.
The cars ready and the
race is about to begin.
Just one more thing
to take care of.
It's the penalty box.
Ed has to stay in there
for one minute.
Now we can ready, set, go!
And they're off!
Ed. Ed!
It's me, Edda.
Ed, please believe me
about Magnus.
- Oh, I believe.
- Oh, you do?
You are the most annoying
individual I have ever met.
Ed. Ed, can you hear me?
Ed's penalty is over.
And there he goes, yeah!
Yeah!
This is unbelievable.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Mind me, coming through.
He's taken Louis
and he's coming up on Carlos.
Time to wrap this up.
Whoo-hoo!
Not quite.
Welcome to the bus stop.
Now that's what I call
a fair dodger.
Hm.
Need a lift?
Eric.
It's a brutal race folks.
Magnus has to be behind
that crash,
but I can't see how.
What's next?
Anyone got crystal ball?
Oh, I, I'm getting something.
Danger below
will threaten triumph above.
Look down. Look down.
Look down.
A drone.
That's it. Magnus must have
drones underneath the track.
Rosa was right.
I was?
I mean, aye, of course I was.
But what is he using them for?
And how do we stop them?
You're gonna need these.
You go Edda, save the day.
Now all I have to do is,
breathe through my mouth.
Ha ha.
Balloon gas tank.
Whoa. Okay.
Whoa, whoa!
Edda, are you there?
Drones? He's got drones.
I've got eyes on a whole swarm
of drones down here in the sewer.
You are in the sewer?
And what are you talking
about drones?
Right under you.
Magnus is using these things
to control the cars above.
Shockingly, I don't believe you.
I'll prove it.
There should be a car up
there spinning out of control.
Yes. Mine!
I believe you. I believe you!
Uh-oh, I don't think
they like to be punched.
Ah, they can shoot lasers.
Okay. I'll deal
with Magnus up here.
And I'll deal
with the drones down here.
That's a knockout.
Ed, you're all clear.
Ha-ha!
Hi.
What? What?
Let's pump things up.
This cheating
is getting very tiresome.
Would you like your ice cream
in a cone or in your face?
No! My drones!
What happened?
Computer, show me
what we have left.
I will take care of you,
whoever you are.
Ed's back in the action.
Okay, let's get this race
back on track.
Huh?
Come on.
Can't a bear just sit in peace?
This is a dream come true
for the best driver of all time.
Ed!
Edda?
Um, is that
an underground train
rising into the sky?
That's a change from
the scheduled service.
Edda, I'm coming. Hold on.
Wait, what is Ed doing?
I win. I'm first!
What is happening?
Edda, are you all right?
Uh, yeah.
No, not really.
Oh, no. The train's
heading for the stand.
Oh, I'll never make it in time.
Okay.
Thank goodness no one's
ever cut Cindy's budget.
Hmm, ah!
I said no vanilla!
How on earth
did you pull that move off?
You mean the pendulum
Whack River jump Surprise?
I just didn't think about
it like someone I know.
Hmm.
In all the
excitement, it's easy to forget
we've got
a first time winner, Magnus.
I won!
Finally.
Oh, Magnus, how could you?
Oh.
Look, Edda, they've got him.
You were so close.
Saving me cost you
becoming a legend.
I got something
far more valuable.
You gave me back my dream
to be part of a team.
You both did great.
That was a real race.
Bring it in, my old friend.
Bockli!
With Magnus disqualified,
the trophy goes
to second place, Nachtkraab!
Where is he? He was just...
I'm here.
I really need to know
how you do that.
Thank you, Cindy.
But there's someone here
who deserves this trophy more than I.
In a world full
of egoism and selfishness,
you can recognize true
heroes by their team spirit,
their courage
and their self-sacrifice
in standing up
for what is right.
Your daughter is an
excellent driver, Erwin.
Wait, you know?
I recognize a rocket
ramp spin flip sky ride when I see one.
Oh, I dunno what
to say other than, sorry.
I thought you were the bad guy.
Yes. I get that a lot.
I have no idea why.
Oh, thank you Nachtkraab.
And thank you Ed.
Thank you Grand Prix of Europe!
I have no idea
who this mouse is,
but I'm pretty sure we
will see much more of her.
In my whole career,
I have never seen
a Grand Prix like this.
What about you Peri?
Oh, my gosh. No. Never!
I mean, that was,
that was just, I mean,
that was incredible.
I mean, oh, Peri,
it was mind blowing.
I mean, you know,
Enzo, get away with me.
Okay, come on. Get away with me.
Oh, I've never felt so alive!
- And there you have it, folks.
- Come on.
Peri is a complete loss
for words.
Get away from me, Enzo!
Come on!
That prize money
changed everything, Edda.
Even if you did have
to give half of it to Ed...
He wouldn't take it.
Really? Why not?
Well, he said
the only thing he wanted
was for me
to be part of his racing team.
You said no?
Dad, I'm needed here.
Do you want to be here?
Of course, I don't wanna be
traveling all over the world
tag team racing with Ed
winning trophies all the time.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. Obviously I want that.
But look how happy
everyone is here.
This is my family.
But, you know,
we'll always be here.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that if you find
yourself with an opportunity
to do something
you've always dreamed of,
it's okay to go if you want to.
It's too late anyway.
I told him no
and he left for good.
And I told him to wait for me
to change your mind.
Wait, where?
So I was thinking we should
call ourselves Team Edda.
Absolutely not.
It's just two more letters.
- Nope.
- Hmm.
Well how about team Edda
and friend?
Stop it.
What about the Ed-dorables?
Whoo-hoo!
♪ It's always
Like the first time ♪
♪ See the magic
In the children's eyes ♪
♪ We ride them
Then we fly high ♪
♪ From here to the sky ♪
♪'Cause life can turn
Your world round ♪
♪ So leave behind
Your ups and downs ♪
♪ All you gotta do
Is come around ♪
♪ So join us now ♪
♪ 'Cause together now
We go from zero to hero ♪
♪ This place is for everyone ♪
♪ So let's celebrate
Under the stars ♪
♪ Let's dance
Our way through life ♪
♪ Oh, let's celebrate
Let love unite ♪
♪ 'Cause we light up the sky ♪
♪ Join us in the park ♪
♪ A joy for evert heart ♪
♪ 'Cause that's who we are ♪
♪ Celebrating under the stars ♪
♪ So let's celebrate
Under the stars ♪
♪ 'Cause we light up the sky ♪
♪ Light up the sky ♪
♪ So let's celebrate
Under the stars ♪
♪ Let's dance
Our way through life ♪
♪ Oh, let's celebrate
Let love unite ♪
♪ 'Cause we light up the sky ♪
♪ Join us in the park ♪
♪ A joy for every heart ♪
♪ 'Cause that's who we are ♪
♪ Celebrating under the stars ♪
Your future is full
of adventures and surprises.
Huh?
Or you have a long line
for the bathroom.
♪ Winning in love
Europe comes together ♪
We're shining lights forever ♪
♪ Oh, love ♪
♪ We can paint a rainbow
Across the sky ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ You and I celebrating
Under the stars ♪
♪ Some think
The world needs superheroes ♪
♪ Some want to live
Like famous stars ♪
♪ Some have it all
Most have zero ♪
♪ Some forget why we are
Here and who we are ♪
♪ We need a friend
When we're in trouble ♪
♪ Many ways
To help each other ♪
♪ Just a hand
Is all to be enough ♪
♪ Winning in love
Europe comes together ♪
We're shining lights forever ♪
♪ Oh, love ♪
♪ We can paint a rainbow
Across the sky ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ You and I celebrating
Under the stars ♪
♪ Celebrating under the stars ♪
♪ Together ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ Celebrating you and I ♪
♪ Celebrating under the stars ♪