♪ Blue tick
New money ♪
♪ Artificial sense
Of notoriety ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ha-ah ♪
♪ Slim thick, sign up now ♪
♪ Pay me
Don't pay the machine ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ha-ah ♪
♪ Big bites
Straight swallow ♪
♪ Come on
You know the rules ♪
♪ Ah-ah, ah-ah, ha-ah ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ You can be a star
Without star quality ♪
♪ Come on honey ♪
♪ Let's go get big
On tiny screens ♪
♪ We'll be like Marilyn Monroe ♪
♪ With turkey teeth ♪
♪ And no legacy ♪
♪ Love me please ♪
Welcome back home.
Thank you so much, sir.
- Have a good one.
- Have a good day.
♪ See, right now, I need you ♪
♪ I'll meet you somewhere now
You up now? I see you ♪
♪ I get you
Take care now ♪
♪ Slow down, be cool ♪
Okay. Who's she?
She's gonna have
a fun time tonight.
No.
♪ But I wish
you were right here ♪
♪ Oh, it's hard to leave you ♪
"Oh, Milo, what are you doing
at our best friend's
engagement party?"
He was your
high school boyfriend.
Why do you still care?
This dress sucks.
♪ All this time I'm thinkin'
I'm strong enough to sink it ♪
Bingo.
Hello, old friend.
No. No, no, no.
Hmm.
You're gonna have a great night.
Miss you, Mom.
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ It isn't my destiny ♪
♪ Waitin' around for
What heaven has planned for me ♪
- Hi!
♪ Sunset colors
Midnight lovers ♪
♪ All night long ♪
Hi.
♪ Sweet salvation or temptation
Take me home ♪
-  Hi!
-  Danica!
Thanks for coming.
Babe, I think you should
hook up with Milo tonight.
No.
What better way to
rekindle your romance
than at my engagement party?
So selfless.
With you looking so hot.
A cascade of fireworks, which
you know I find very erotic.
I wasn't gonna tell you this.
So, I had a session with Fleur--
Wait, I'm so sorry.
Is Fleur your life coach,
your energy healer,
or your psychic?
No, Fleur is new.
He's a claircognizant empath.
And he told me that
because Pluto's in Aquarius...
Mm-hmm.
...that means something
life-changing
is about to happen.
I don't believe in astrology.
It's not astrology,
it's empathy.
Hmm.
I see you looking at Ava.
- No. We're just--
- No.
- We're just friends.
- Right.
It's nice to see her.
You know bottling up your
feelings only makes you sick?
Have you read
The Body Keeps the Score?
Danica got it for me. It's fire.
You should check it out.
Okay. Yeah.
Uh, I'm gonna get a drink, so...
Hey.
You'll always be my number one.
And you'll be mine.
- All right, Daddy.
- All right.
I want to thank you all
for coming.
Teddy, to see
the person you've become,
with a strong conscience
and a...
...a big, big ol' heart.
I couldn't be more proud.
But let's talk about the real
star of the evening: Danica.
Your warmth and kindness
are a blessing
to everyone
whose path you cross.
Hear, hear!
To Danica and Teddy.
To us.
Can you believe our best friends
are getting married?
You know what?
I can.
You can stay, you know.
We could get a bestie compound
with a shared backyard.
I just... I don't think
moving back to Southport
is in the cards for me.
Like, Milo, would you give up
your fancy political job
to move back here?
No. No way. Never.
But I don't have a cushy family
nepo baby empire real estate
thing going on.
Oh, my God.
I'm just genuinely touched
that you called it an empire.
Thank you.
That said,
might be nice to take a trip
down memory lane.
It is Fourth of July.
Hey. Hey, you two.
Hello.
Over here.
Yes?
You up for a drive?
Oh, you dirty, dirty dog.
Milo! You know he can't say no.
- Yes. Yes, let's go.
- Yeah?
Let's go.
No, no. I'm driving.
- Wait, what?
- Yeah.
Girl, I'm sober. Alcohol bloats.
Okay.
Whoa. Is that Stevie?
- My God.
-  Mmm.
Now it feels like high school.
Who are they?
Friends from a past life.
We were close in high school.
But after all that shit
went down with my dad,
they went off to college
and I got stuck here.
What happened?
We grew apart.
- She looks really good.
- Mmm.
Wait, is it true
she went to rehab?
Yeah.
Can you blame her for spiraling
after her dad blew her entire
college fund and left?
-  We should invite her.
-  Yeah.
-  Right?
- I think it'd be really nice.
Aquarius is in Pluto.
Come on.
-  You want me to come?
-  Yeah, yeah.
- Come with me.
- Okay. All right. You good?
Stevie!
-  Hey.
-  Hey!
-  What's up?
- Hi.
How you doing?
-  What are you doing here?
- Yeah, I'm good. Uh...
My-- My boss is working the bar.
I'm just picking up the empties.
Well, this is great timing,
'cause we were gonna go watch
the fireworks where we used to.
You should come.
You got the whole gang
back together.
Yeah. Yeah, they're all here.
Yeah,
I'm-I'm just on the clock.
Oh.
I can do the run back alone.
You should go.
Mmm.
It is the best view
of the fireworks.
- No!
- Stevie's back!
Teddy, can I have some?
- It won't hurt you. Come on.
- No.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- I'm gonna kill you!
Stevie!
- So good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
Aww.
Look out!
What?
What? No!
- Oh, my God, you asshole!
- That was funny.
- No, it's not.
-  "No, it's not."
You hit those brakes
fast though.
And people say
women can't drive.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
It's jokes, jokes, jokes.
Rude.
-  Thank you, Daddy.
- You didn't kill us!
- Thank you, Mommy.
-  It's beautiful!
Whoa.
-  Wow.
-  Oh, my God.
What?
-  Here, I got it.
-  Wow.
-  Thank you.
-  That's okay.
- What do you want?
- Gimme the fucking blunt.
He wants the-- No!
Let's light her up.
Fuck!
Ahh! I miss this shit, I--
I miss
hanging out with everyone.
We even got Stevie back.
God, you feel that?
This energy
just makes my dick hard!
God! Yes, I love y'all! Whoo!
Oh, my God,
cannabis makes him so annoying.
I mean, look at the fireworks.
It's... It's poetry.
We come to this place for magic.
Oh, my God.
Because we need that. All of us.
Okay, Nicole Kidman,
but there's a car coming.
Fuck that car.
-  Why is he like this?
- I don't know.
Man versus machine.
-  Teddy, seriously.
- I'll show you how great I am.
-  Teddy, get out the road.
-  No, that's not funny.
-  Chill the fuck out.
-  Teddy.
- He's gonna stop!
-  Teddy, stop.
- Teddy, quit fucking around.
-  You're being annoying.
Teddy? Get--
Baby, please just move!
Teddy!
Oh, my God!
Babe, oh, my God!
What is wrong with you, man?
Jesus Christ, Teddy!
- My Superman.
- Stop.
- Get yourself killed.
- Teddy, what are you doing?
What the fuck, Teddy?
Get out the fucking road.
Get out of the road.
I wasn't gonna
let the car fucking hit me.
You owe me a blunt.
-  Fuck.
- Oh, my God.
Guys...
What do we do?
-  Are they okay?
- They are clearly not okay!
It's jammed! Fuck!
He's alive!
Hey! We're gonna get you out!
-  What do we do?
- Teddy. Teddy.
Teddy, get him out of there.
Hold on, we got you.
Whoa! Let me--
Hold it from the back
so it doesn't go over!
- Put your weight on it!
-  Try?
Don't let go!
It's slipping! Teddy! I can't!
-  Just hold it!
-  I can't! I can't!
Fuck!
What did you do?
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
I'm calling 911.
No. No, no, we--
we have to go down there.
That person was still alive.
Everyone just chill out!
Chill out. Just--
This is...
This...
Let's talk about it first.
Talk about what? That person
was alive. We have to help him!
Yeah, but we need to be careful
about what we say.
No, wait. Who gives a fuck
about what we say?
We have to do something.
How are we supposed to
get down there, Stevie?
It's not realistic.
- I think we need-- We need--
- Yeah. Yeah.
I'll call the police.
I'll call 'em. Gimme a second.
I'm such a--
Why did I come up here
with you guys? If-- If--
If this turns into,
like, a criminal thing,
you guys can all afford
fancy lawyers, I can't.
Why would it become
a criminal thing, Stevie?
We didn't do anything wrong.
It was an accident, right?
We were just messing around.
He was in the middle of
the road. It wasn't an accident.
It's manslaughter, Danica.
But this road is called
Reaper's Curve for a reason.
There are so many accidents
that happen up here.
And nobody knows that Teddy
was in the middle of the street.
We know!
All right, see? We're
fine, everything's fine, so...
The police and paramedics
are on their way.
- Now, let's get out of here.
- What? Wha--
Shouldn't we stay here
until they get here?
Don't we need to give them
a statement or something?
They-- They want us to give
the statement at the station.
No. No, no, Teddy, Teddy,
I don't like leaving.
I don't--
I don't think we should leave.
Like, I just got my life
back together,
- I can't screw it up...
- Stevie. Stevie, look at me.
Look at me, breathe. Breathe.
We'll be fine. I promise.
We just need to get out of here,
all right?
No! That guy was alive
in that car!
We need to go down there
and help him!
And do what, Ava?
Fuck this.
Stevie!
We should go.
Yeah.
We should get out of the road.
Come on.
Ava.
Ava, let's go.
See?
It'll be okay.
Aren't we going
to the police station?
Danica?
Danica!
My dad's gonna
take care of everything.
Okay, um...
It's really important
we don't tell anybody
what happened tonight.
You know,
I think we should all
agree on that
before we part ways.
Can we make that deal?
Stevie?
Yeah.
Milo?
Uh, yeah.
What about you, Ava?
Please say
you won't tell anyone.
This could ruin
our entire lives.
And Teddy didn't mean to.
It was just a big mistake.
Grant's gonna make it look like
we were never there.
Please.
I won't tell anyone.
Welcome to Wilmington
International Airport.
♪ Leave me alone, bitch
I wanna have fun ♪
♪ Got my hair tied up
Phone on "Don't disturb" ♪
♪ Leave me alone, bitch
I wanna have fun ♪
♪ My ex walked in
And my other ex with her ♪
♪ Leave me alone, bitch
I wanna have fun ♪
♪ Put the three of us together
That's a real tongue twister ♪
Harder.
♪ Leave me alone, bitch
I wanna have fun ♪
Milo, hey.
Hey, sorry,
I'm running a little late.
That's okay.
I can just Uber to Southport.
No. No, no, no, don't worry.
I'm almost there.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll be there in, like, 15.
Okay, I-I will see you soon.
Well, it was nice to meet you.
Well, hold--
hold on a second. You're, um...
You're going to Southport?
I'm going there, too.
Would you give me a ride?
Uh...
Ooh! Who died, you guys?
I'm feeling a little tension
in this car.
Hey. Miles, was it?
- Milo.
- Right, um...
Look, I haven't really
slept with a guy in years,
but you seem pretty beta,
and I'm really into whatever's
happening between you two.
Just putting it out there.
Okay.
How do you two know each other?
- Ava?
- We just met on the plane.
Yeah.
And Tyler,
what brings you to town?
Mmm. I'm so glad you asked.
Um--
I host a true crime podcast,
Live, Laugh, Slaughter.
It was one of Bloody
Disgusting's best pods of 2024.
I'm doing an episode
on the '97 massacre
that happened here in Southport.
I would love to give you guys
a little murder tour.
I'll keep that in mind.
My God! You guys actually came.
I know I kinda disappeared,
but I wouldn't miss
your bridal shower.
Hey.
- Hi.
- You look great.
Thank you.
Danica, the present table is
overflowing, where do you--?
Stevie.
Holy shit. Hi.
Milo, Ava,
- it's so good to see you.
- Hi. Yeah.
It's been so long.
Work got crazy,
and, you know.
Uh, okay, so where
do you want these?
Um...
I'm thinking maybe the--
- Credenza in the living room.
- Yeah.
Yeah, same.
Do you want me to take that?
Uh, sure, thanks.
Thanks, babe.
I didn't realize
you and Stevie got so close.
Yeah. She's been a really good
friend to me this past year.
Let's get a spritz.
I have a spritz bar.
Two fresh spritzes, please.
Wow!
Stevie.
It's beautiful!
I know how much
you love mermaids,
and then it reminded me
of that day.
Literally, I was thinking
the same thing.
- I know, I had to buy it.
-  Oh, my God!
You know me so well, diva.
Thank you.
Of course.
Okay. Let's do this one.
Oh. Uh, that's from me.
It's moonstone.
The lady at the store said
it symbolizes new beginnings.
It felt like you.
- I love it.
- Yeah.
I'm just feeling so loved today.
Okay. Let's go...
...this one next.
Okay, minimalist chic.
Could it be...
...cash?
A check, maybe?
Gift card.
Mmm.
Let's see.
No more pictures.
Who's this from?
No, really.
Who-- Who brought this?
- What does it say?
-  Nothing.
It doesn't say anything.
Obviously just like a...
...silly prank or something.
Sorry. I probably just took
too much Adderall this morning.
Hunter, babe, I'm sorry, you can
keep going with the pictures.
I know I'm supposed to wait
till the end,
but I couldn't wait for a kiss.
-  Aww.
- You don't say.
You're not supposed
to be here yet.
Hi.
Aww.
Get this. Get this.
Um, but now that you are,
why don't you show everybody
what you've done
with the pool house?
He calls it his "man cabana."
Stevie, Milo, Ava, will you
join me in the kitchen, please?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I can't believe
he would do this.
Who?
Teddy. He's obviously trying
to mess with my head.
This is why we broke up.
He's petty
and emotionally stunted.
And I know Wyatt's
kind of an alcoholic.
But he's taken
really good care of me
since Teddy went insane
this past year.
Sorry.
What makes you so confident
that this is from Teddy?
Are you an egg, Milo?
Outside of us,
no one knows what happened.
Besides Teddy's dad.
Unless it's somehow connected
to the person in the car.
Sam Cooper.
I know you all
looked him up, too.
Yeah, but he didn't have anyone.
No family.
None that I could find anyway.
Which honestly makes
the whole thing even sadder.
What if someone saw us?
What if someone
saw what happened?
Perfect.
So either
I'm being blackmailed,
or my ex is trying to
ruin my life.
- Jesus.
- Ew.
Teddy?
Visiting hours are over.
Hi.
Oh. Wow.
My long lost friends.
So nice of you
to make a house call.
So, how was Danica's party?
Was that fucking clown there?
Uh, yeah, Teddy, Wyatt was
at his fiancée's bridal shower.
Fuck do you three want?
Danica got a note today.
Ah. Queen Danica.
Is this a joke or something?
I don't... I don't get it.
Danica thinks you sent it
to mess with her.
This is real?
Yeah.
No. Fuck. Um...
Yeah, I... I don't want
anything to do with this.
Please, please just go.
I'm in enough trouble
with my dad as it is.
No, Teddy, Teddy,
we have to talk about this.
- Someone clearly knows.
- Danica got the fucking note.
It's a Danica problem, okay?
Can y'all please
get the fuck off my boat?
Can you just talk about--?
Go!
Oh, my God.
Goddamn.
Teddy, really?
Fuck.
Do you need help?
Hey.
Hi.
Didn't mean to scare you.
You okay?
Yeah, just thought
I heard something.
I know what this is about.
Wedding jitters.
- Mm-hmm.
- Baby.
- Mm-hmm?
- I'm not Teddy. Okay?
Not gonna spin out and bail
a month before the wedding.
-  I know.
- Remember what Dr. Emma said?
"Trust my actions and words.
You are safe."
I am safe.
Come here.
Mmm.
Welcome
to your meditation, Queen.
Let's begin.
Mmm.
Hello?
What the fuck, bro? Gah!
And in this moment
of absolute calm...
begin to feel the branches
within you emerging.
My branches are always emerging.
Fuck!
Oh! Fuck!
Now, exhale your fears.
You can take whatever you want!
Take the code
to my crypto wallet!
St-- Please.
Please. Stop. Please.
No. No. Please!
Please. Stop. No.
Please.
Please! Please! Stop!
Babe. I feel so much better.
Ooh! It's giving nuptials!
Wyatt?
Hi.
- Hi.
I was home.
I was in the bath,
and I didn't hear him.
How could I not hear it?
Does this make me a widow?
Yeah,
but you're like a hot widow.
Well, obviously
the hot part is implied, Ava.
Are we done?
-  Yeah.
- Oh, my God. No. I can't.
Teddy.
I-I think now isn't the time.
Danica.
Danica,
we're s-so sorry for your loss.
I've arranged
with Chief Roberts.
We'll have a patrol car outside,
keep an eye on you.
Theodore.
- Thank you.
- You all right?
Yeah.
Okay. What can we do?
What-- What do you need?
A ride home.
You know that meme that's like,
if someone you love dies, do you
still do your skincare routine?
Now I know the answer is yes.
How do you feel?
Numb.
That feels like forever ago.
Yeah.
Makes me really happy
that Stevie's been there
for you this past year.
'Cause I know I have not been.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
What? Why?
Because I did such a terrible
thing making you lie, Ava.
Like, I understood why
you didn't want to talk to me.
No. I couldn't talk to you
because I couldn't talk
to anyone.
What we did was so fucked up.
I just felt... so dark.
I felt like the guilt
was gonna swallow me, and...
I thought you were fine.
I am not fine.
I'm just better
at pretending like I am.
I've been having
horrible nightmares.
And now I have
stress induced alopecia.
I have a bald spot.
No one's noticing that.
I notice.
Do you think this is
some kind of
fucked up karma
for what we did?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I'm really sorry
this happened to you.
And I've missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
Can we cuddle?
Mm-hmm.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Are you sure?
No.
But whatever happens,
I'm gonna be here.
Do you promise?
Yes, I promise.
Mmm.
Okay, I'm just gonna
ask the question
that we're all thinking.
Is somebody after us?
I know it sounds crazy,
but what happened to Wyatt
can't be a coincidence, right?
I agree. It doesn't feel
like a coincidence,
but it also doesn't make sense.
Wyatt wasn't with us.
What if this was just
a random psycho?
Dani, there was a threatening
message written in blood.
I need to start drinking.
Okay.
Who else knows besides
the five of us? Teddy? Your dad?
You think my dad
would commit a violent murder
on the weekend
he's trying to prove to people
how perfect Southport is?
- Grant could have told someone.
- No way.
Besides, whatever he told
Chief Roberts
made this shit go away.
Great.
What about that girl you
were with that night, Stevie?
No way. I didn't tell her.
What about your new friend, Ava?
The girl from the plane?
Tyler?
- What girl? You met a girl?
-  Yeah.
And she has a whole podcast
about murder.
It's called
Live, Laugh, Slaughter.
Oh, wait, oh, wait. I found her.
She's so hot.
She's very hot.
She have a rat?
I don't know.
Wait, hold on. Listen.
What's up, Slaughter Gang?
Next week, I've got a story
that'll get you hooked.
In 1997, a killer
in a fisherman's slicker
terrorized a group of teens
who thought they could
get away with murder.
One by one,
he sliced and diced them
with his horrific hook.
And it all started
with an anonymous note.
I got an anonymous note.
Mm-hmm. Yup.
That's-- That's why we're here.
Okay. Let's kick the tires
on your little theory, Milo.
Tyler, a random girl I
introduced myself to on a plane,
came all the way to Southport
'cause she knows exactly
what we did last summer
so she can kill us all
for her podcast.
That makes no sense.
Well, I just... I don't think
we should rule it out.
Look, I'm with Ava.
I don't think
it's this podcast girl, but...
The notes. The hook.
There's a lot of similarities
to 1997.
Even if we wanted
to look into it, we couldn't.
My dad had all that shit
scrubbed off the internet.
What? It was
hurting investor interest.
I think it's time we start
digging into our local lore.
Local what?
This place is eerie as fuck.
When I first arrived,
I was shocked at the glow-up.
It's like a grisly killing spree
never even happened.
This place is so beautiful
it makes me wanna die.
But I learned
that was by design.
After real estate prices
plummeted
in the wake
of the '97 murders,
enterprising property developer,
Grant Spencer,
saw an opportunity
to turn this haunted
fishing town
into the Hamptons of the south.
But not everybody was happy
about the "gentrifi-slay-tion."
Fuck yeah.
Tyler. Hi.
Hey!
Thanks for meeting me.
Yeah. I was really happy
that you texted me.
I've been getting kind of lonely
walking around here by myself.
Well, show me
a new side of Southport.
Hmm.
Our journey begins with...
Bayside House?
Well, it's not about
Bayside House.
It's about what it used to be.
Come on.
♪ La-la-la
Loops inside my head ♪
Bingo.
♪ My, my, my,
My head ♪
♪ My head
Holy shit.
Well, they really
paved murder town
and put up a Soho House, huh?
I don't get it. What does '97
have to do with Bayside House?
Well, this was the site of
one of The Fisherman's
most gruesome attacks.
Oh, merch.
Did you make that?
Duh. I sell them
on my Etsy shop.
Oh, God. Wasn't she so hot?
Well, sucks she's dead. Hmm.
Okay. Picture this.
Nearly 30 years ago,
Julie James, Southport native,
comes home from college
to an anonymous note.
And then the bodies
just start droppin'.
Do you know what the note said?
Mm-hmm.
"I know
what you did last summer."
Look.
How shit is that handwriting?
If I were a murderer,
my handwriting
would be way scarier.
Did Julie James die?
No, actually.
She's one of two survivors.
She teaches at Hoffman now.
I tried to get her
for an interview for this,
but she sent me an email about,
like, boundaries or something.
Will you just...
wait here a second?
Yeah.
I wanna see if I can find
something cool upstairs.
Send a text to
"Don't Get Murdered."
Can someone come meet me at
Bayside House? Tyler is sketchy.
Send.
Tyler?
Cool costume,
but I'm not loving this.
Seriously, that's not funny.
Ava? Who is that?
Tyler.
Tyler, run!
No!
Ava? Where the fuck did he go?
Shh--
I don't know. I don't know.
Fuck.
- Try and pull it.
- Oh, God.
Pull it!
Just go! Go get help!
I fucking hate it here.
Come on!
Fuck.
Ava? It's Stevie.
Stevie, I'm in here!
Ava!
Stevie!
Come on!
You don't have to do this.
Please, man, I swear. I'm a fan.
Please. I'm a fan.
I'm a fan. I'm a fan.
- Ava!
- Stevie!
You.
- The door's stuck.
Hang on!
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- What happened?
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
No, no.
Ava!
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you hurt?
No. I'm fine.
I need you to handle this shit.
Yeah, sure. I-I-I'll pick it up.
Chief Roberts, do you have any
leads about who's doing this?
- Hey, Chief.
- Yeah?
We got the girl's parents
on the line.
I'll be right there.
Look. I know you all have
a lot of questions, okay?
We're gonna hold a town hall
at the community center tomorrow
to discuss
these recent events, okay?
I gotta go. I'm sorry.
Chief, I--
The cops are all
in Grant's pocket.
They're not gonna help us.
Then we'll find someone
who will.
It's happening again!
That is what
the nervous system says
when we are repeatedly
exposed to danger.
People living with complex PTSD,
they may not entirely
understand their own behaviors,
why they're making
these decisions.
Over time, if you don't deal
with your trauma,
your trauma will deal with you.
Because trauma changes the brain
in mysterious and complex ways.
Julie...
Julie!
Julie.
My name is Ava Brucks.
I'm from Southport.
And I-I was attacked by someone
in a fisherman's slicker.
- Very funny.
- No, I-I'm not joking.
They had a hook.
And I fought back,
but my friend is dead.
She's the second victim
in two days.
And another friend of mine
got an anonymous note
before all of this started.
Just like you did.
And what do you think
I'm gonna do about it?
I just need your help.
You survived this once.
And my friends and I,
we're really scared.
Someone is coming after us.
I just have one question.
What did you do last summer?
Shit, I'm so sorry.
I was just...
Going through my stuff?
I only had lemon ginger.
Hope that's okay.
Oh, yeah, that-- that's perfect.
Those people. Are-- are they--
Dead? Yeah.
But it's not about my friends.
It's about yours.
If history is any indication,
the killer's connected
to the boy that died.
What do you know about him?
Um...
Well, we couldn't find much.
Are you serious?
I mean, don't you people
put your entire lives online?
Not him.
I mean, we found an old address
to an apartment in Southport,
but nothing before that.
And the cops are downplaying it,
'cause they don't want
to scare away
the tourists who are in town.
Well, I'm glad to know
that the Southport PD
is still number one
in gaslighting.
Would you come back there
with me?
We're only 45 minutes away,
and there's a town hall today.
We could go there
and we could press them--
I made a promise to myself
a very long time ago
that I would never go back
to Southport.
They didn't listen to me then.
I'm...
sure they wouldn't listen
to me now.
Hey.
Whoever's doing this,
it's personal to them.
You can't run, you can't hide.
The only way out
is to find out who it is
and get them
before they get you.
We have
upped the police presence
for the remainder
of the holiday weekend.
How am I supposed to explain
that scene yesterday
to my children?
We sympathize with those
who witnessed what happened.
But this was
a disturbed young woman
- who acted only to harm herself.
- That is bullshit!
If-- If y'all could just
settle down, please?
Ava, we...
We are so sorry for what
you had to witness yesterday.
I can't imagine how distressing
that must've been.
But your friend
was deeply troubled.
We've learned
that she recently quit
her psychiatric medications.
That's a really convenient
narrative.
Can I offer an alternative,
Grant?
Two nights ago,
a man was murdered
in his fiancée's home.
And yesterday,
before Tyler was killed,
I was chased
through Bayside House
by someone
in a fisherman's slicker,
carrying a hook.
- Okay?
- What?
- And last Fourth of July--
- If you're referring
to the young man
had the accident,
he was a drug addict,
drove a stolen car off the road.
Now, that's tragic, of course,
but these
are completely unrelated events.
Are you really
just gonna sit there
and pretend
like nothing like this
has ever happened
in Southport before?
You should listen to her.
This isn't the first time
there's been violence
like this in Southport,
and you know it.
Hello, Ray.
-  Is that your boss?
- Yeah.
I assume you're referring
to what happened to you
back in 1997?
That's right.
Southport
is a very different town now
than it was then.
And I'm afraid
I just don't see a connection
between a home invasion,
a tourist's suicide,
and something
that happened to you
nearly three decades ago.
Gimme a break.
She said she was being chased
by someone wearing a slicker.
Now, you need to handle this.
It's not going to stop.
Listen...
I wanna reassure everyone here,
all of you,
we will have a healthy presence
from our friends
at the Southport PD.
So you can all feel safe.
And one last thing,
Pastor Judah's doors
will always be open
at the Southport Trinity Church,
should anyone need
a sympathetic ear
in the wake
of this tragic incident.
- Pastor?
- Thank you.
Each and every one of you
are welcome.
We've organized
a prayer group this evening,
which will start at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you, Pastor.
See you at the festival.
Why didn't you ever tell me
what happened to you?
It isn't something
I like talking about.
What's going on, Stevie?
What was all that about
back at the town hall?
You said I could
come to you with anything.
There's something
we need to tell you.
Who's we?
We have to figure out
who Sam Cooper knew.
Everybody has somebody,
and Julie said that's the key.
Wait...
you went to go see Julie?
Julie as in your... ex-wife?
Wait, I'm sorry.
You were married to Julie James?
Unfortunately.
Guys, I know what we have to do.
We have to involve Fleur.
Oh, my God.
- What's a Fleur?
- Don't ask.
My claircognizant empath.
All right,
if somebody is after us,
why don't we, I don't know,
fucking leave?
We could take the keys
to my boat
and fuck off
to the Bahamas for a while.
Simple.
For reasons I won't get into,
I wouldn't do that.
What about the car?
Grant said it was stolen.
- Did you guys know that?
- No. No, we didn't.
Okay, so, what, we need, like,
a police report?
Would there even be
a formal police report
after what Grant did
to cover it up?
Look, when they pulled
that truck out of the water,
they had to take it somewhere.
You need to find out
whose car he was driving.
Be safe.
You too. Love you.
Call us later.
Hello.
Can I help you?
We were hoping
you could help us get some
registration information
on a car that came through here.
You got a license plate number?
Um...
- We...
- Um...
I need a license plate.
Well, actually, that's--
that's part of the problem.
Um.
You see, my brother was
in a horrible car accident.
And I've misplaced that paper
with the registration number
and the license plate number
on it, and--
If you could just help me.
- Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
- It's still really raw.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- And I just would love it if--
It's okay.
They're gonna help us, okay?
- Please, sir, I mean, it's--
- Okay.
Yup.
Do you have anything?
What about a make and model?
- It was a...
- It was a Dodge.
It was a Dodge pickup truck.
Uh, late 1990s. It should've
come in around
- the last Fourth of July.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
1998 Dodge Ram.
Came in July fifth, last year.
Yes. Yes, that's exactly it.
Ugh...
It's really totaled.
This one's registered
to Judah Gillespie.
Is that your brother?
Yes.
Yeah, that... that's him.
Pastor Judah?
What are we even doing here?
This cemetery is
the only thing I could find
that connects
Sam Cooper to 1997.
So, there's gotta be
something here.
"Barry Cox."
Barry with the big ol' Cox.
Wait, wait, look. It says 1997.
He must be one of them.
And Max Neurick.
"Helen Shivers".
Oh, my God!
She was a Croaker Queen
just like me.
Oh, my God, diva.
That's so fucking creepy.
Are we done?
We've confirmed everyone
dead here is still dead,
and I'm not trying to join 'em.
You're such a grumpy tuna.
I'm sorry, Helen.
All right, come on,
let's get out of here.
It's getting dark.
Oh, my God.
Teddy.
Those are fresh flowers.
That means
someone visited this grave.
If he had no one,
then who's visiting?
- Hi! Yoo-hoo!
- What are you--
Um...
Did you happen to see
who came by and put these here?
- Nope.
- No.
People are in and out of here
all day, ma'am.
Um, what about those cameras?
- Please?
- Sure.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- I'll check that out.
Fuck this.
Let's just go.
He's not coming back, clearly.
Well, maybe there was
a lot of footage to go through.
Don't you think it's worth it
to find out
who left those flowers?
Fine, I'll go check,
but I guarantee you, he dipped.
Okay.
Hey, sorry for your loss.
Um, you have extra beer?
You know what,
all-- all good, I'm sorry.
Shit!
Hello?
Fuck.
No!
No! No!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Fuck away from her!
Oh, shit.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
Yeah!
Run away like a little bitch!
I'll fuck you up.
Hey, hey. Hey...
Hey, you're okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
-  I'm okay.
- Come on.
- Come here. Come here.
- Mm...
Motion detected. Back patio.
Motion detected. Front porch.
Fuck.
That's a warm welcome.
I thought someone
was coming to murder me.
This is worse.
Well, believe it or not,
I was worried about you.
May I come in?
I know
we're not exactly friends.
With everything
that's been going on,
it just felt sort of wrong
not to come in and check on you.
What is this really about, Ray?
'Cause I'm not buying the whole
"I'm worried about you"
nice guy act.
Fuck it. Look, what the hell
were you thinking
giving advice like that to Ava?
And there it is.
What-- You told her she should
track down the killer.
And then what, kill him?
Have you lost your fucking mind?
She asked for my help,
and I told her
- what I thought she should do.
- Oh, right, Yeah,
just give her advice from
the comfort of your own home,
then send her back to Southport
on a suicide mission.
Unlike you, I haven't
completely repressed everything
- that happened to us.
- Hey,
I deal with that every day.
Just like you.
But to project that shit
onto them...
It isn't right.
Look... one of her friends
that's involved works at my bar.
She's a good kid.
She clearly did something bad.
You know more than anyone,
that sometimes
you can just get mixed up
with the wrong people.
Yeah. I do know that.
Ava?
What's up, Stevie?
Did the cops find anything
that helps identify who it was?
Cops didn't find shit.
I think we should talk to Judah.
If Sam stole his car--
But what if Sam didn't steal
the car?
You think Sam and Judah
are connected?
So you think Judah's the one
that left the flowers?
Oh, my God! Enough with
the Scooby-Doo bullshit
for two fucking minutes.
Danica almost died tonight.
We can--
We can figure out
what to do tomorrow.
Fuck it.
Are you sure
you don't need anything else?
I'm okay. Jill gave me Xanax.
Shit. I have to...
I have to get back to the bar.
Bye.
Be careful, Stevie.
Oh, I also asked Jill to make up
a guest room for you guys.
No one sleeps alone.
Is that cool with you?
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Yeah. Um...
Seems like a good idea.
I love you.
We're gonna figure this out.
- Goodnight, kitten.
- Mm!
Do you wanna cuddle?
No one sleeps alone.
Big head.
It's just lumpy now.
I'm injured.
I don't know what
I would have done
if something had happened.
Yeah. But you don't have
to think about that, though.
'Cause you saved me.
Yeah.
I caught Teddy's mom
kissing her tennis instructor
in here once.
Hell, yeah. Good for Jill.
Yeah.
♪ Got you runnin' in circles,
I know ♪
♪ Touchin' me ♪
♪ Get your paws off
My Dolce cologne ♪
♪ Back it up ♪
♪ Off my throne 'cause you know
You wanna ♪
♪ Make me ♪
♪ Walk away
And forget about it ♪
Choke me. Punish me.
I deserve it.
Wait, what?
Never mind.
We don't have to do that.
Hold on. Hold on.
I think I need a minute.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You can punish her. It's fine.
She wants you to choke her.
So, choke her. It's okay.
Fuck is my charger?
Let me see...
Okay.
Ava?
Milo, I'm sorry.
I just don't really know how to
deal with all of this, you know?
Will you please call me back?
Have you heard from Milo?
Not yet.
Hello?
Can I help you?
Um...
Yeah, sorry.
We're looking for Pastor Judah.
Hey, I know you.
You're Stevie's friends.
So sorry about your loved ones.
Oh, thank you.
That's actually why we came.
We've been struggling a lot
with our grief.
Course you have.
Well, Pastor Judah's
not here right now,
but maybe I can help you?
Yes.
Can I use your restroom?
Of course.
It's just down the hall.
Thanks.
Ava?
Pastor. Hi.
I was-- I was hoping
to talk to you, actually.
This has all been so dark.
Of course. Such a terrible time.
There's been so much death.
Why don't you give her that book
that you had me read?
About grief.
We lost one
of our flock last year.
- He died in a car accident.
- Thank you, Hannah.
When did that happen?
I don't recall exactly.
I understand
why you're struggling.
It's hard to accept that death
is coming for us all.
Give me one moment, and I'll
be right back with that book.
That's okay,
I-I'd just rather talk.
It'll just take a minute.
I insist.
Okay.
May this book remind you
that death is part
of God's natural order.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
It's Judah.
He's hiding something.
You have to go talk to him.
These are extremely
concerning allegations.
I'm glad you came to me.
Give me a moment.
Let me talk
to one of my officers.
Thanks.
- Sit tight.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay. I guess he's
gonna help us.
Hey, you've reached
Milo Griffin.
Leave a message.
Hey. Ava told me what happened.
No need to be in your feelings.
Hitting the gym so
I'm ready for this motherfucker.
Just call me back.
Mr. Spencer, we have Miss Brucks
and Miss Richards here.
They're being hysterical.
So I was thinking
I could, uh, keep them here.
That's a fine idea.
Let them spend the night
enjoying the hospitality
of Southport's finest.
Where is he?
Can you text the group?
My phone's dead.
No, my phone's in the car.
He locked us in.
- Are you serious?
- Hey!
Hello?
- Someone let us out of here!
Let us out!
Danica,
I'm getting kinda freaked.
Where are you guys?
And... are you okay? Did--
Did it go okay with Judah?
Just call me back, okay?
You've reached Teddy.
Leave one.
Shit.
They're not answering.
Hey. Hey.
I made a promise to your dad
that I'd look after you.
And I have every intention
of keeping that promise.
Nothing bad is going to happen.
You hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
You're gonna make it
out of this, Stevie.
Hm.
No one deserves that
more than you.
Come on, let's go.
Whoo!
Ah! Ah!
Help! Help!
♪ Oh I'm crying
All night long ♪
Help!
Somebody help!
Mom.
Mom!
♪ That I love so ♪
Jill!
I'm getting ready!
♪ Oh why did I ever ♪
- Oh, my God!
- Dad.
Teddy! Teddy!
Oh, God.
Help! Somebody help!
Help us!
Teddy, it'll be okay.
Teddy. Teddy!
Danica...
Ava?
Danica?
No. No.
It's not my fault.
Of course it's your fault.
You're the girl
from the picture.
I mean, I do have a name.
H-Helen Shivers.
And don't you fucking forget it.
I was Southport's very own
Croaker Queen way back in--
I really shouldn't date myself.
Was it... 1996?
Careful, sweetheart.
I have the hook.
You're pretty.
Thank you.
Poor bastard.
Didn't deserve that at all.
I didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
You killed Sam Cooper.
Now, your fiancé is dead.
No, no, no. No. This isn't real.
I may not be real,
but that body is.
He died all by himself
while you were taking a bath.
I-- No-- I...
I-- I couldn't hear,
and I didn't know.
You're gonna die, Danica.
Please!
I just wanna wake up!
Stay in the dream
as long as you can.
Nothing good is waiting for you
on the other side.
I didn't wanna die either.
But we did a bad thing.
And when you do something bad...
No.
...you have to pay!
You okay?
Yeah.
Had a really fucked-up dream.
Something's happening.
- What do you mean?
- I have no idea.
You're free to go.
All units to the boardwalk.
- We should follow them.
- Okay.
What're you doing?
Get them down!
Get back.
I need you to get back.
Get them down! Ava! Stevie!
Danica, come on.
Come on, Danica, let's go.
Let's go.
All right, we're asking
this crowd to please disperse.
Hey. Look, I know it's a lot,
but you need to leave now
or you're gonna get stuck here.
Text Milo. Tell him
to meet us at the docks.
Okay. Okay.
Ray.
That's his car.
Thank God. Thank God.
We have to go.
Milo?
No. No!
- No!
- Wait.
- Oh, my God.
Milo!
No, Milo. No!
- It's gonna be okay. No!
- Ava, he's gone.
No, we can't leave him
like this!
You need to leave.
You need to leave
right now, Ava.
No!
- Ava! Ava, I'm sorry!
- No! No!
- Ava, come on!
- No, Milo!
He's gone. We have--
Ready, ready.
Put your hands up!
Judah, hands
where I can see 'em.
How you doing?
Bad.
How are you doing?
Did the anchor just drop?
I don't know.
- Chief.
- Yeah.
Take a look at this.
That's Sam Cooper.
Is that...?
Yeah.
Ava!
Ava, they're here! Ava!
What the fuck do you want?
I want you to die, Danica.
I thought that
was obvious by now.
Don't do anything stupid, diva.
You're a crazy, psycho bitch!
You shouldn't call
women crazy, Ava.
It's so reductive.
A strong, empowered woman
takes control of her destiny
and then suddenly
she's labeled as crazy?
Now, are you gonna keep
interrupting me,
or are you gonna
let me fucking finish?
After my family went broke,
and my dad left...
...things got
pretty dark for me.
But then I went to treatment,
got clean, and it was
like this new beginning.
I met Sam.
And I was finally ready to
forget how all my best friends
tossed me out
like fucking garbage.
Sam was afraid
I was gonna relapse.
That why he took Judah's car
to come get me.
I didn't know it was him
until his body washed up.
Judah was more than happy
to take Grant's money
in exchange for his silence.
I took care of him
before we got to the docks.
Can't have any loose ends.
So why are you
telling us this now?
Why don't you just kill us
like the rest of them?
You took the person that
I love the most away from me,
and I needed you to know
I did the same to you.
We should've stayed.
We could've helped him.
You left that night too, Stevie.
Remember?
Only because Teddy said we were
going to the police station!
So, what's your plan?
You're gonna kill us?
Steal Teddy's boat?
Is that gonna make you happy?
Yeah, yeah. Pretty much.
You know,
after I found out it was Sam...
...I thought about killing
myself a lot, honestly.
But then I thought,
why would I kill myself
when I could
just kill all of you?
Fuck!
This thing's so fucking hot.
Help! Help!
Help us!
We're over here!
You lying bitch!
That's for my fiancé!
Which one?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
She has Danica at the bow.
Ava!
Get away from my best friend,
you cunt!
Please, just fucking kill her.
- Now!
- Shut up!
Let her go, Stevie.
What are you doing here, Ray?
The police came looking for you.
I didn't give them anything.
Stevie, let her go!
Everyone's dead!
You got everything you wanted!
Just let Danica go!
Look, we still got time
to figure this out, Stevie.
You don't want to do this.
No!
Actually, I do.
Danica!
Why didn't you come to me? I--
It didn't have to be this way.
Yes, it did!
They took everything from me!
There needs to be accou--
No.
It's over.
Hey. I'm safe.
I'm coming back
on the boat with Ray.
Julie, it was Stevie
the whole time.
I just don't understand
how she did all of this alone.
Oh, my God.
She must have been
in so much pain to do this.
Julie said trauma changes you.
But I just didn't know it could
change someone like this.
You can't underestimate
the lengths someone will go
to avenge what's been taken
from them.
How did you move on
when this happened to you?
You never move on
from something like this.
It just changes you.
You learn to adapt.
Want a clean shirt?
I'm okay, thanks.
All right. Suit yourself.
Um...
I think I'm gonna head out,
but thank you
so much for everything.
Let me give you a ride home.
No, that's okay.
I think a walk would be nice.
There's just one problem.
You know it was me, don't you?
You know Stevie said
we should let you live?
That you were
the only one who wanted
to do the right thing
that night.
You killed your partner.
Did I?
Please don't kill me.
I don't think I have a choice.
Help!
Ah!
Ava?
Ava!
Julie?
Julie.
Oh, my God.
I think...
Okay. Okay. Hey. Hey.
- You know what?
- What?
- It's gonna be okay.
- Okay.
All right?
The police are on their way.
You are not gonna die today,
do you hear me?
Okay. Okay.
Yeah?
Happy Fourth of July, Julie.
Thought you were never
coming back to Southport.
So, how'd you figure it out?
That kid Stevie
asked for your help, didn't she?
They fucked her whole life up,
those friends of hers.
She wanted revenge, and I knew
how to help her get that.
Nothing holds people accountable
like a good old-fashioned
murder spree.
So you used what happened to us
as a playbook.
They tried to erase everything
about this place.
They tried to erase us.
They walk around here pretending
that what happened to us
never even happened.
I had to make people remember.
So here we are.
It's 1997 all over again.
Isn't that nostalgic?
Nostalgia's overrated.
Who cares if they tried
to erase us, Ray?
You have to let it go.
You know...
I think I'll say
it was you who killed everyone.
See, at first,
I thought it was a problem,
you getting involved.
But now I realize you're
the perfect fall girl.
Crazy-ass Julie James,
who couldn't quite move on.
Recreates her past,
only this time...
she's in control.
What are you waiting for, huh?
This is gonna hurt, sweetheart.
What are you waiting for?
Gotcha.
Fuck the Fourth of July.
Couldn't agree more.
♪ I was living in a devil town ♪
♪ I didn't know
It was a devil town ♪
♪ Oh lord ♪
♪ It brings me down ♪
♪ In the devil town ♪
♪ The devil town ♪
♪ All my friends were vampires ♪
♪ I didn't know
They were vampires ♪
♪ Turns out
I was a vampire myself ♪
♪ In the devil town ♪
♪ The devil town ♪
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Hospital.
Hospital, hospital, okay. Uh...
I am so Isabel Atraumatismo.
You know, you're kinda
like a real-life mermaid.
Right?
- I am.
- You are, you actually are.
Did you call a car?
- Yeah, I got one.
- Okay, good.
Can I say something?
Uh-huh.
I'm fucking starving.
- Oh, my God. Me too.
- Yeah.
When's the last time we ate
literally anything?
I don't know.
How you feel?
Better.
How about you?
I'm also still really bad.
I think some of my digestive
system is in the ocean now.
Yeah, this whole experience
has been... zero out of ten.
- Like, no stars. None.
- No stars.
None at all.
It's pretty crazy
that all of this
could have
probably been avoided,
if men just went to therapy.
- Well...
- You know...
I love you.
I love you so much.
I think you're my soulmate.
You're my soulmate.
Yeah, I think
it's fair to say...
the divas are up.
Oh, my God,
I forgot to tell you.
What?
Stevie's alive.
What the fuck?
Should we kill her?
That feels extreme,
but yeah, probably.
Fuck yeah.
♪ Sometimes when I
Zone out at night ♪
♪ I forget you're out of sight ♪
♪ Like living
Before you were gone ♪
♪ So I read up
On the afterlife ♪
♪ I don't believe
In Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Just somewhere
We can all belong ♪
♪ And days move slow ♪
♪ I'm living in
The same black hole ♪
♪ But there's flowers
On your grave that grow ♪
♪ Something's gotta change
I know ♪
♪ And I'm stuck
Somewhere in between ♪
♪ Your death
And my lucid dream ♪
♪ I'm no help lately I know ♪
♪ But I'm tired of trying
To prove my worth ♪
♪ To be accepted on this earth ♪
♪ Baby I'm ready to go ♪
♪ And days move slow ♪
♪ I'm living in
The same black hole ♪
♪ But there's flowers
On your grave that grow ♪
♪ Something's gotta change
I know ♪
Tonight, we're
tracking a developing story.
A string of brutal killings
took place
over the Fourth of July Holiday
in Southport, North Carolina.
While law enforcement
first believed
a local pastor
was Miss Ward's accomplice,
it came to light
that she was actually working
with Southport native,
Ray Bronson...
Holy shit.
...once married to
Hoffman University professor,
Julie James,
both survivors
of the deadly killings...
Here you go.
...that rocked Southport
nearly 25 years ago.
Bronson and James survived...
Isn't that your
college roommate?
...on two separate occasions.
Yes.
James was attacked by Bronson
after returning to Southport
in the wake
of the recent killings.
People are always
trying to kill that woman.
Ray Bronson is now deceased.
I hope she's in therapy.
All right,
I'm gonna go get some sleep.
But it is believed
his accomplice,
Miss Ward, is still at large.
Julie! Oh, my God.
It's been years.
Can I come in?
Of course, come in.
I was watching
the news and, girl,
you can't catch a damn break.
Ray?
Yeah. It's been a weird month.
Come here.
I missed you.
Me, too.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want
to do this to you again.
What's going on?
I need your help.
Who are we fucking up this time?
I was really hoping
you were gonna say that.