[Sound of a loud bang]
♪ ♪
Dad, in this same place.
disappear in this very place?
This is our original son.
All our elders were here.
That's a big legend.
[Officer] One share of the land
Please send me a share of the land quickly.
Lotus...
How are you?
Stay away.
- Hey Rampa,
- Beversi
What do you see?
Grandpa's gun.
There are frequent fires.
You continue the story.
Her wound is very serious.
What a legend?
About years ago,
This is the place where the gods settled
What are the numbers?
The God we believe in!
A power merged in nature.
Whenever a man turns towards unrighteousness,
From the world of magic, the gods,
It's like sending armies to protect the religion.
One of those who came like this,
we believe, Panjurli.
The blood of those who go towards iniquity
Another will come after him to drink
A fierce-looking scoundrel!
[Primal cry]
All these clans have come and settled,
in this sacred soil.
This is the original name thousands of years ago...
Kantara
is a legend.
The time when the Kadambas ruled Banavasi,
The Kadambas, the rulers of Paduvana
.
With a bloody sword,
He who became king over his subjects by force,
A demon in human form,
Vijayendra of Bangra.
Without any awareness of the outside world,
Among our elders who lived happily
Baidi is a dreamy little girl.
Look here, Jabbana.
How beautiful!
Is it the stone of Karnika?
We who worship nature,
see the divinity in that stone...
Blood flowed in that clear water.
Someone was watching all this from a distance.
Wizard!
[Baidi is crying]
Jabbana… (crying)
Our elders of Gatti Ratte
became slaves to the Bangra people.
[Sound of whipping]
[Sound of a hand gesture]
[The man screams in pain]
Hey.. Hey… Hey… Jabba!
One day, while the king was bathing in the sea,
The magician was sitting at a distance, fishing.
[Sound of sword]
Hmm, his blood shouldn't touch the water!
The king's eyes sparkle at the sight of the spices.
Even though silver doesn't shine like gold
it was the foundation of their trade.
Where did you get this?
God's flower garden.
Kantara.
The king had everything,
Kantara left one.
Is the way right?
[Sounds in the forest]
- Hey! Where did this grandfather go?
- It's not here now.
The king was caught in the illusion of the magician.
[Scary sound]
[The horse squeals in fear]
Everything was filled with that light.
God's flower garden!
But it's not just light,
[The wild boars rush in angrily]
[Tree branches break and fall]
Dad, dad… fire.. that…
Dad, fire!
- Dad!
- Stay here,
[Scary sound]
Dad!
[Primal cry]
[A tree burns and grows in fire]
[Scary sound]
What kind of tree is that?
King of Bangra (laughing)
That?!
[Everyone gasps]
[Divine Incarnation]
[Primal cry]
Swami Panjurli.
Whoever sets foot within this land of Karnika with destructive thoughts
Their blood fell on this ground, pure.
[Primal cry]
As long as this voice of mine reaches
Until then, this idea is in the air.
Let it hum in everyone's ears.
[Primal cry]
Rajashekhara, who had fled without direction or destination,
only managed to reach Kadapa.
On the one hand, those who find peace through worship,
On the other hand, they would accumulate energy through invocation.
From the story of Karnika told by Rajashekar...
The people of Kadapa were fascinated by Kantara's powers.
Rajashekhara joins the court with the help of those from Kadapa .
From there, darkness and gloom merged.
Decades passed, but the fear of Kantara
remained intact in Rajashekhar's chest.
It is as if rain pours down whenever the abode of religion is disturbed.
Divinity is born again and again in this soil.
[Baby crying]
Ika Jabbana, there is a child inside the well.
She kidnapped a child no one wanted and made it her own.
She gave him a name that she found in the original.
Berme.
Meanwhile, Rajashekar becomes the father of two children.
[Emotional music]
But when I found out that the girl
had no strength in her arms and legs...
[Baby crying]
Why is this called God's flower garden?
When our Ullaya comes here for penance, he feels at ease.
This is the garden that Goddess Parvati gave me , telling me to meditate .
Berme is talking to someone?
What's wrong with him?
When they brought the child they found in the well and
asked who they were going to talk to now...
What should I do?
Come on, let's go..
Belita Belita
was amazed by the beauty of this place,
Never go into the wilderness, children.
Why?
There is a demon Brahma there.
[Boy is laughing]
Hey, why are you laughing?
Don't laugh.
Brahmarakshasa.
As time passed,
our elders, who used to make a living by utilizing the produce of the forest,
They gave a share of that production
to God and kept the other share for themselves,
They were holding the third ball on the border.
They believed that a demon named Brahma would come
and take it away.
For the next generation of Kantara and Bangra,
the fear of the Brahma demon was a boundary.
[Scary sound]
As he was getting older, Rajashekara
crowned his son.
[Traditional music]
King of kings…
King Marthanda,
The people are sovereign,
The chief of Bangra,
Sri Rajashekar, the heir apparent,
The new ruler of the Bengali throne,
To Sri Sri Sri Kulasekara Rajas
Very good! Very good! Very good!
[Ceremonial orchestra playing]
Come, Kanakavati.
Salutations to Kulasekara Rajaguru.
Oh priests,
Hello.
Oh! God bless you!
Which God?
My blessings be upon you, Aitu.
Go ahead.
A gift from the Kadambas to the king.
Mahaprabhu!
- Give it here once. Oh.
- That's beautiful!
- It's shining, Mara.
- Look how it looks.
The state prospered under your rule.
Was it necessary to give a title to your son while you were there?
Didn't my father see me rise to power?
What I had to do for my father.
I believe my son will do it.
Did you get it from them?
Aren't I behind him?
You became a king and
made me a minister, Kulasekara.
This is what Khushili needs to do now.
What are you doing, Maraya?
The war was over by the time my father was alive.
But should I take over the government? (Laughing)
Hmm. That's right.
Starting with a hunt?
Those.
Where to go?
Kantara.
Not a scary forest!
Is there a Brahma demon in this forest?
Didn't you see your father's eyes, Mara?
Hmm! I'm not here anymore.
Will they get there before us? (Laughing)
[Bhogendra laughs]
Whoever gets caught, it's enough if I can't be found.
- Hey Bhogendra,
- That...?
Drive a little slower, Mara!
Everything drunk is coming out.
It's impossible to go any further than this.
If you want, you can walk with the soldiers.
Hmm?!
Who is the king here?
I don't know who the minister is, Mara.
- Hey, give me an arrow...
- Ik.
- Hmm, give me the bow.
- Oh!
I didn't bring a bow.
Who is this Mara?
The monkey, who came to hunt, did not bring a bow,
I don't know where to leave this now.
Ikkali, who are these?
Tell the kings not to make a fuss,
Give the bow Bikanasi!
Brother, there's someone there.
Oh! How much is that?
That's all.
He has no sense of touch, Mara.
Hey, look around...
- Bukka bukka bukka..
- Oh! Where?
- Aha!
- Yes.
Ah! Madhukara… just a good blow.
- I showed it to you.
- Yes?
- Hey, bring it.
- Hey, those in front, go.
If there's something inside, let's shout.
- Why are you going inside?
- Are you crazy? I'll run.
- Lord... not here.
- Oh!
Hey, is it broken?
Oh my god, it's broken.
King... I don't want to continue.
- Are you going?
- Oh.. are you going, are you going...
Let's go ahead!
Hey Turra…
- Only a good horse.
I'll listen to what you say.
Crown him,
and our coronation will be complete!
Hey, Kadave!
[Releasing and hitting an arrow]
Ran, ran, ran... ran..
- Hey Nilsira.
- Hey… What a blow, King,
Good luck!
I know,
Hey, come on.
Annu Bara, come quickly and go home!
Kulasekara, to our chariot
we are going to put it in our chariot.
Again the kings are empty-handed.
that the kings come empty-handed.
Brahma the demon! (with fear)
[Ominous atmosphere]
Mahaswami, others
It's good to go. Oh!
[Sound of horses running]
They also took the bow and left.
Soldiers
[Soldiers gasping for breath in fear]
Don't be afraid, keep your eyes on all four sides...
Brother!
Run!
[Soldier crashes into tree]
Whose?
Hey Nagendra Sumne, don't be mad.
He had courage,
he too went.
If everyone dies, who will tell the story?
Oh my…(crying)
[Soldiers' horrified screams]
[Arrow piercing]
the! Brahmarakshas's ball.
It's over. (Crying)
What do you see? What do you do?
I didn't hear you say that, go away...
Ayyappa!
[Soldiers fight with forest people]
[Screams angrily]
Oh!
Oh... oh, I'm alive,
I have someone above me.
[Heroic music]
Berme!
Did you arrive a little late?
[Berme lets go of the rope]
♪ ♪
♪ Forest forest ♪
♪ Isara Deyere Poo Bittal ♪
♪ Bemmere stared ♪
♪ The land of truth where the gods live ♪
♪ Kantara! ♪
[The Kantaras continue to sing]
Oh, Jabbana has arrived.
You continue.
What are the children doing? What?
Pump...
How was my hunt?
Is that possible?
What is your hunting like?
If he comes after us again, I'll stone him.
What do you mean by border? Oh!
Did you run away in fear?
Was that a tiger in front of you? A mullet.
It got scared when I screamed.
Oh, Grandpa, when you screamed, the thorns stood out,
It's the same even after death. Ika.
Don't doubt my abilities.
Give it here. That…!
That!
No matter what,
You shouldn't have shown your power to me
at this age.
[Women laughing]
Nochi! Ika.
Take it.
Good hunting. That?
[Men shouting]
Hey, Kora… How many times have you been here?
Abba, the hunt is big.
[Indistinct speech]
Huh?
[Alert calls]
Hey! This is breathtaking..!
[Hunters shout]
Oh.. I've been dead for a while.
- Hey!
- Stop being a jerk,
He turned his head away just by seeing us.
Whose Darbesi did you bring?
They came.
- How many people were there?
- About.
We broke everything we could get our hands on.
The people on the horse ran away.
King.
The Bangla people have crossed the border,
They will take us away again and do the work.
Sleep with a weapon under your head.
How many people are there?
They ran away in fear without seeing us.
They are afraid of them.
I'm saying... the Bangla people have somehow made it happen.
It's better for us to cross the border ourselves before they come back
.
Shall I say once to Jabba the Hut for courage?
Hmm,
He left all of us behind just because he cut off a toe ,
How much courage can he give us?
I'm just saying what I saw.
Everything I saw came running.
I know what they are like.
From now on, all border guards should be careful.
- Berme!
- Oh...?
Take the bodies and throw them across the border.
I don't want more people coming in looking for him .
Ha ha.
Oh, look,
That's what Jabba says. Go beyond the border.
Oh my God, has the demon Brahma crossed the line?
- Is that all just a fabrication?
- Yes?
Oh my God,
shouldn't you know which direction to go?
That's a ghost to us.
Give a big coin.
It's hard to live anymore if you miss so much.
- Allah is the one who kills and takes away.
- Hmm.
- Hey…
- Hey!
I'm crazy. Tell me.
Do you want to sit and talk at the top of this waterfall
?
My legs are shaking.
What kind of stone is this, that it's so sharp?
This is not stone. Iron,
We have to make sacrifices.
These are the ones who do not eat the eye. They do not hold the tongue.
- These are..
- Oh.?
How far is it from here to you?
That is, on foot.
That would take a day to reach
- You're not taking us away.
- You're going, no,
Why do you come there?
We don't want to see how much you've grown up compared to us,
do we?
See?
Look, you're not coming back.
If you knew I was the one who brought you there
,
It's hard to live there again.
Hey,
how much do you think you're going to take us?
We will not come to Bidli.
Yes, you say,
They don't have to understand.
Oh my God!
Come on. Let's go and pray.
- Huh?
- Hmm.
We are going out across the border for the first time.
My dear.
Swami Panjurli.
- What happens?
- That's the God we believe in.
Your oath is not even visible.
It can only be seen if there is devotion,
Don't worry. Just think about it and then do it.
Oh. I can see that now too.
Forgot to say,
Except for the soldiers at the border,
no one else is allowed in!
Now they're letting me in.
Good arrangement.
Oh, life and honor remained,
I don't even have the habit of scolding myself.
Hey guys.. what's the story with this Brahma demon?
That's not true,
- Once…
- Hey, Sumne Iro. I'll tell you.
There was a wicked king in a town.
Hey, we have one too.
Ha…! Avne.
[Together]
People are getting sick of him working.
He then performed a severe penance.
No, no, why do penance?
It's not worth it if you get a higher salary.
- Just listen, Marre,
- that was a mistake.
As the sages and sages, in person,
told a group of people...
He should be given so much work that he can't even get a salary
.
Why is that?
If you give a man a gift, he will eat people like a
snake.
- Yup!
- Ha!
There's more. I'll tell you later. Come on.
I can't stay here,
I don't have much hope,
How could it be so quickly?
- Come on, just listen to me.
- Is that enough?
- My heart is beating fast.
- We'll stop it completely, Dad.
Listen here.. He didn't do what he said,
When they get rich after finishing their work,
they will eat humans.
It's not like he once came to eat the king himself,
The queen grabbed Rappa, gave him a lock of hair, and went away.
It's like I was sent to do everything and come.
- Is it Sarta?
- No,
Even now, I'm getting my hair done.
I feel like I'm somewhere in this forest.
Who is Maraya the Monkey? (Laughing)
He is the demon Brahma.
- Is that him?
- Hmm.
Oh God!
If only he would stand in front of me with his hair all disheveled.
What is my fate?
Anyway, if you get one for your birthday, it's enough.
- Whose?
- A beautiful piece of mama's.
Those.
How much is this?
Bangra border.
Was this also built by Sankappa?
Ha. That king Rajashekara
did.
Open the door!
If only we had come in our own clothes.
we wouldn't have been caught here, Berme.
Hey hey, shut up and be polite.
Oh my goodness, the kings arrived yesterday,
Why are you so late?
There was so much to see inside that… forest.
- Where is the hunt again?
- It's not here.
How many deaths? Just come.
Why are the kings so late?
They wake up early in the morning , meditate for a while , and then light a lamp for the gods.
It's a little late.
You are the only one who makes me happy, King.
He ascended the throne,
You alone have not changed,
It's the same old Kulasekara.
Bhogendra chose the afternoon,
People are waiting, come quickly.
- Are you coming...
- Is it noon?
Kulasekara!
This is your first meeting after becoming king.
Hmm, hey, I don't want to know what I've been drinking.
Whoa!
No way, (laughing)
[The crown rolls down]
Slowly, slowly.
Don't you know?
Didn't you know you were drunk?
No, Dad.
Let the meeting begin..
Oh my! What a mess this is!
It's good, don't worry.
- Hey!
- Huh?
Princess Kanakavati has arrived.
Don't let anything fall into their eyes.
Yes? They will see us when they see us.
- Hey, come on, there's someone here.
- Hey, stop, you killer, you've only survived half your life so far.
You've arrived. Don't touch the whole thing.
Pliers, these people,
Truth. Listen to what I say,
How many people are there!
- Ikoli
- How long is it?
Ikkali, this one, this one is long.
I won't say.
This is it.. hey,
Where to see Maraya's death.
[Chief's orders]
Hmm, pick it up!
If your hand touches the water while you are unloading, I will kill you.
[Slave screaming in pain]
Rhino!
How much?
- Lunch!
- I was starving.
Stay here, don't go anywhere.
Who to catch? Who
to let go? I don't even know.
- Oh, my life was lost in hunger.
- Brother, brother.. give it to me.
Karma Kanda said that he had to feed them a lot .
- What a shame, you all are acting like wild men.
- Oh, good.
That!
- Veera Mahabala Anna.
- How long has it been, Maray, I haven't seen you.
The king has put it in my intelligence department.
No one has seen it like that.
- Huh?
- Very secret.
You eat. Don't let your hands dry out.
Eat it once and die quickly!
Shooter!
Take stock of the work done so far.
The king's enemies said that they wanted more.
I will get permission and
get it as soon as possible.
The stone is visible in the Karnika,
Do you need carving?
The Kadambas have built such a beautiful temple,
Doesn't the God in the sanctum sanctorum look beautiful?
- Start.
- Okay.
Oh God, protect me!
Is that a bit ominous?
[Screaming in fear]
Hey! You're here, it's okay, Kootkoli,
This is the death of a female bee.
Hey! Come here.
- How much?
- A soldier?
Do you need soldiers to protect you?
What a shame! You are my burden.
.
Hey, she's a big person, but she's not the one who comes to her,
No way.
[The Kantaras are screaming]
Oh! What kind of a joke is this?!
Hey Chinkra, shut up, Mara, it's getting cold.
From here, your path is yours, mine is mine.
Don't tell anyone that I brought you here .
No, that's all I'll say if anyone asks.
That!
I wonder if I'll be at the butcher shop tomorrow.
Shh! Shh!
Oh! Good!
I have now found happiness for the hardships I endured.
Hey!
Look here... Sankappa's place is not available.
How they have done everything. Alas!
- How much did you need?
- That...?
Oh, give me some of that.
- Hey, give me some of this. I need it for the hunt.
- It's like asking for supplies at the store...
Idonderedu kodi not,
..keltiddane
- How much is this?
- Bring back the hunting game.
- Give me the king's order?
- Will you give it only if I give it?
How long ago did you join the army?
- Hey, no, this morning.
- What?
Hey!
Is the uniform dirty?
That..
That...
didn't you just come back from combat training?
Hmmm! Hmmm!
If Sankappa was there, Rappa would have sent him away,
I am grateful for what I have become.
- Where is this Sankappa?
- He's in prison.
Whose house is this?
Anniversary!
Where have you been all these days?
Leave it.
Your wife knows everything about us.
- Which dog said that?
- That brave Mahabala Anna.
Hmm, there's been so much war,
but he didn't die!
Oh, grandma, drink it!
Why hide anymore?
Come on, open your mind and talk.
Hmm! You looked over there!
I'm going to talk a little bit here.
Hmm.
Is this all ours?
Ah! The crust is good.
How did this get here?
- Go, go….
- Take it, take it..
Jeeta did it,
wouldn't a fistful of purchases be enough?
- Did you steal this?
- Oh! Peppercorns!. It was all ours.
Hey, we should catch all of you and hang you.
Hey soldiers, let go of that, hold on to this...
Hn! You take them yourself, this belongs to us,
We are waiting for this.
Hey, is that you?
Don't they look like soldiers?
Even with all this, they don't look like soldiers,
so why all this?
- Hey, why don't you take it?
- They're all thieves too!
Come here, soldiers.
Catch him. Come on, Rappa!
- Search all the clothes.
- Hey, hurry up, Maray!
- Are we dead?
- Go, go!
- How can we recognize each other?
- We are Marra, can't you recognize us?
[The Kantaras are shouting]
- Did it start again?
- Who?
Mari, step aside!
Where is Maraaya hiding?
God must show the way.
Hmm.. Should I climb there?
The entire Rajbidi is occupied by these people...
Go..
[Berme is giggling]
I came to a certain place, and
the boats made it look like I was climbing it!
It won't be okay up there.
It's not like I'm coming down,
Who called you?
Go and do business.
Alas!
- Berme, is it okay to leave here?
- Just stay.
[Sound of spear]
Hey, hold on tight!
[Sound of chariot wheels]
♪ ♪
Woohoo!
Whoo! Whoo whoo whoo!
Is the boat leaving?
Who is running away?
Swami!
[Chenna keeps screaming]
How did you get here?
Did you bring it yourself?
[The Kantaras are screaming]
[Overlapping scream]
Hey Beversy!
Can't you see, this is me...
You will be welcomed there by Darbesi.
[Berme keeps screaming]
Who is the woman?
Hey! He's here, come on!
Ah!
Are you coming from here? Come on!
Big!
Hey hey hey, you bastard. Hey. Where now?
Oh!
- Is it yours?
- Hey, hold on tight,
I'll stop wherever I go and see.
How many monkeys are you standing like?
Fly away!
Hey, what's that sound?
Daru!
Ha! There's a twist ahead, alas...
Go and stop the chariot.
Alas, there is an abyss ahead...
God, God, God, God, God
, give me life..
I will give you a Brahmakalasa fruit. Oh my..
[Men scream together]
Give it some time.
We'll come ourselves!
You don't need soldiers to come to protect you.
Come on.
- Young queen!
- Hey, Chenna?
What do you do with them?
Hmm... I came to pay my debt of life.
Jai Bhangra!
How much is this?
- Gangasara.
- We did it ourselves.
Ha!
There is a terrible wound, Mara!
Hmm.
Put this in.
Are we thirsty?
I've given it. Didn't come.
Chief soldiers!
Kings...
they sold our goods in the market.
They made a fuss over what they heard and
caused losses to their business.
What is the name.. Nindu?
Berme.
Where did it come from?
[Tense music]
Kantara.
[Sound of weapons being drawn]
The demon Brahma didn't come, did he?
[Chain noise]
[Sound of whipping]
I can't do it, Mara.
This is the buffalo.
Kantara?!
[Sound of whipping]
Brahmarakshasa!
Hnu. My grandfather was killed by cunning while he was hunting.
Hypocrites!
They can't handle it!
Hey Bhogendra, there's not even a bit of soil in their
forest,
It's all just a story.
If your father had given birth to you, would you have stayed there?!
You were watching the story come true.
As the little one ran, Maraya saw the fire in the pot.
[Men laughing together]
Don't laugh like that, Marre,
you're really going to die!
Oh, what a sight!
Give it to him.
[Grunting]
How many times can you break a tie?
Let go of your hand and look.
How much?!
Come on.
Don't laugh, Maraya, you're right!
Kulasekara!
Come here.
Come on!
We were just staring blankly.
Who brought you to Bangra?
How high is your bangle in the sky?
It takes four steps to get there.
We came.
Oh my God, you saved me!
- Hey!
- Oh, good.
Where is your uniform?
That's my fever.
The commander-in-chief has come to ask for leave.
- What?
- Ha!
Permanent leave. Will it come?
Intelligence department again?
I have put other people in charge of it,
These people don't leave their wives.
Why did you come here?
You have come to see us,
Shouldn't we come to see you?
[Mourning music]
Have you been to Kantara?
Didn't go inside,
That's all I saw from the side.
[The men of Kantara laugh in unison]
Even though I know I won't go back.
Have you set foot on this soil?
[Mourning music]
Hmm! We once
left you behind,
Today, we have invaded your space,
broken into your own, and stood before you.
Do you still
think we can't go back?
[Heavy percussion music]
Come here.
Come on!
Did you add salt? Or did you pour it? Hey,
Hey!
How are you?
I just asked for salt.
They have come as if they had come to the fair, waving their hands.
Didn't you just cut off that hand?
He doesn't look like an ordinary person, does he?
Looking at his actions and words,
he seems like the leader of Kantara.
That's why I said that.
I won't get a chance like this again.
He is in our custody, we will kill him.
Hmm!
The king's responsibility was understood only when the company was good.
Take responsibility and hang yourself,
How are you now?
Hmm. Don't confront the Kantara people.
Not everything is yours, King.
So can I wash my hands too?
Hey!
Hot water is a good idea,
[Servant screaming in pain]
Hey...
Baby!
Sleep, child...
Get up.
The children went out for a few days.
Make sure nothing happens to their lives.
Swami!
We have brought prisoners,
Sell ​​it to the Arabs for a good price.
That won't happen to Marley, Maraya.
Do you want to change yourself now?
I'll do it if you make a monkey.
Bring those who have a chest cavity and sell them.
Bhogendra is having a hard time.
Hey, don't call me Hesrella, booba.
- Now I am a minister.
- Aisa!
When I was the king's personal soldier, you
weren't in your father's mind, Mara.
Now you're boobing me too?
Where is Booba?
[In Portuguese]
- Hey, excuse me...
- What's going on?
There is no proper place for my boat, Hockley,
This port will remain for another death.
- What do you mean?
- Portuguese,
There is no place to dock the boat,
I ask you how many deaths you have, my friend.
[Slapping]
Hmm. I don't know if there's a place to park the boat,
Come swim next time you come.
If you...
Son of a whore
Hey hey hey.. what are you saying?
- He's your mother...
- Oh, nothing, nothing,
You just said that people are a bit aggressive.
Hey,
You know,
Son of a whore
I'll kill you one day, you fool...
- Ministers!
- That?
You should not lay hands on foreigners,
We are having a hard time doing business.
Everyone should say what they want to say to someone, right?
This time, the people who came are very stubborn,
I bought it and sold it.
- Oh!
- Lunch.
Take a look at the strong people of Hodsala,
I saw that there was no life, no life,
Go to bed.
I thought dinner had arrived.
The people who brought it today are ordinary people,
They came to Kadili and destroyed the entire Royal Street.
Our royal street?
How arrogant is Mara?
My son Pepe is right for these thieving officials.
[Intense background music]
Give me a spanking!
Swamiji has arrived.
[Sound of metal key]
[Sound of iron door slamming]
No matter how much anyone inside is shouting
, you should be inaudible.
- Do you know?
- Hmm.
Put on a helmet.
Lord?
Put the Chilka on!
Hmm.
You may have difficulty seeing.
Go outside.
Okay. Hey, ha ha.
[Sound of whipping]
The thief is under my supervision.
Beversy?
Where did it come from?
Kantara.
[Ominous music]
That… that.. that..?
Kantara…
Hey, hey, take it quickly, Mari...
The Beversi people just locked up and left when they told me to put a Chilka in
.
What can you say?
Hey.. Can someone
come here and unlock it for a moment...
- Who is there?
- Swami Karitiddara?
The Lord himself has said that no matter how much one rants, one
should remain unheard.
Oh my gosh, I'm calling you Pepe.
Don't be afraid, sir, we won't do anything.
Hey!
Come quickly, you beavers, and open the door.
Take it off. My life is going to end now.
Oh, my God, O mortals, breathe here.
It's getting cold, come quickly, my dear...
Hey Kuntkol.
Come on. Dad came..
- Abba Bandru, hey, you are there to protect me, Nerepintu Allah..
- Swamiji said.
Don't be afraid to ask for what you don't want, or you won't listen.
What a bunch of death bodyguards you are to these people,
Where did you go to sleep? You are dead.
- This is the side of the field.
- Hey, are you going to go all together?
Swami said,
we should stay together wherever we go.
Tell him that you don't want to be together,
you want to be with me.
Hey, aimless karma, where
did you get this magic from?
You are welcome.
Leave the way, give me a card,
Where are you...
Did you cut off the dogs' heads?
- Lock it now.
- Ha.
Called for a fine.
Don't come here!
I only hold the saw in my hand. Huh.
We don't do anything.
We are also human beings like you.
Why are you gathered here?
Is there anything our family
has done for Bangrak?
King Vijayendra
asked me to build him a palace,
We gave.
His son asked me to build a prison,
We tied that up too.
But in the same palace, I am alone.
I never even dreamed that they would put it together.
Oh my, what a pity!
Whose father?
Hmm.
I am that poor person.
Oh my God...
Didn't you ever dream that your leg would be completely numb ?
The Bangla people also said the same thing earlier.
That's it, Irli, why did they put you here?
The king asked me to build a boat,
- Did you give it to me?
- We gave it to you.
To test it,
they put a close soldier in a boat and sent him out into the middle of the river.
Look, look, look... The soldier and the boat
were drowning right before my eyes, and Marai was the one who went into the water...
How is that?
All it took was a small hole in the bottom of the boat to let the rainwater out
.
But I never imagined that water would even come in through that same hole .
Hey!
Don't tell him, don't work together,
After work, drink as much as you want, don't worry,
That's good for the soldier.
But doesn't that dream need a memory?
Hey,
What is that? Is there a town by the river?
Hmm. A place for trading on the seashore.
Port
[Background music]
[Pepe enters]
Have you arrived?
[Door opens]
[Men gasp]
How long has it been since I saw the light?
This bastard is right here.
Ha… maybe come..I'm holding on tight.
Oh..
How many doors do you see, Beavers?
Don't worry, brother. We caught him from the inside.
Did you say you wanted to talk to me about something?
What's the matter?
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
This is what we have,
Let's go outside and get ready.
I will give you half of what I brought,
We trade the rest.
Oh? How quickly did Maray learn the trade?
Hey, it's not happening, Mara.
You have been sold to the Arabs for a thousand baht .
How much do you smoke?
The smoky greens are from abroad.
Bad smell.
Can I give you one, please?
How much?
I found a green leaf in our forest.
lettuce?!
Look at the Sedi.
- [Igniting fire]
- Gammatthaghtade
[Intoxicating music]
[Sound of metal chains]
What a bunch of greens!
The ceremony is open.
Swami, the cemetery remains open.
Same.
- Pepe,
- enough, give it up.
Business…?
Allah is great,
What if you just say business, business, in empty words
?
Do you know what business is?
Sayli,
Have you ever seen a place like this where you can do business?
Can I see?
There is nothing ahead of this.
You should kiss the hand of the saint who gave you this.
How much do you do?
Whoa!
My father, you never break your word.
Look, Ayatollah.
It's getting dark. Go out.
[Booba snores loudly]
Are you asleep?
Your father is crazy.
[Sound of metal clanking]
Is that right?
Okay.
You can't take it off, can you?
No matter how much trouble you have to endure, you won't be able to get out.
Malko,
Talking in the morning.
Sankappa, come.
Ha...! Here we go..
It's not like I'm leaving without telling you again.
Tell him when Buba wakes up, okay?
How many greens..
Don't you look like Kantara?
Oh, my God, I'm an Arab.
I was born here when my father went into business.
The man may be caught in the middle of the trade!
Bermege who came to see the outside world,
He knew that if he wanted to succeed,
he needed a leader.
Farming.
So what kind of son?
No matter what, we will grow and eat whatever we want.
♪ Polly Poly Poove Pondullaya ♪
♪ New coral grows.. ♪
♪ Golden shimmering light drops ♪
♪ Is Kantara included? ♪
♪ Palm gooseberry ♪
Hmm.
♪ Learn the technique, practice the technique ♪
Wow, it turned around..
♪ It's easy.. ♪
♪ The sky is also above the roof.. ♪
♪ I saw a colorful dream.. ♪
♪ Kanna is a very new light.. ♪
♪ Aha ohhhh.. ♪
Wow! The work is done!
♪ There's a new commodity in the soil.. ♪
♪ Walk with new energy.. ♪
♪ Aha ohhhh ♪
♪ The forest is very new.. ♪
♪ Aha ohhhh.. ♪
♪ Polly Polly ♪
♪ Poove Pondullaya ♪
♪ New coral grows.. ♪
Swami, Panjurli.
- Berme Gandu Magu.
- Maybe.
It's a joy to see your hope at this age.
Hey! (Laughs)
When this one grows up and becomes an adult,
everything is in the balance.
♪ ♪
♪ Look at the seed.. ♪
- Why all this, son?
- Oh, for heaven's sake.
What is Yapara?
Giving this, we get what we want.
♪ Oh, the forest.. Oh, the sweet song.. ♪
♪ Look at the seed.. ♪
♪ Work hard.. ♪
♪ Oh, the forest.. Oh, the sweet song.. ♪
♪ Give and take.. Ethics are the best.. ♪
♪ Be strong, believe and live.. ♪
♪ Kanna is a very new light.. ♪
♪ Aha ohhhh.. ♪
♪ There's a new commodity in the soil.. ♪
From now on, a third of what we have grown will be sold at the border.
If you leave the forest and go outside
How long will you live in fear of losing your life ?
If they were to excel so much in the strength of mere soldiers
,
If we, who have divine power, call upon their land...
Dad, don't drink too much.
The gallbladder is gone.
After Kantara's escape,
My life is gone.
What else can a son do with a gallbladder?
Dad, you don't have to do anything to get them.
I did it.
If they find my son,
I have vowed to go to the same forest for eighteen years of exile .
Isn't that a line, son?
- Boo...
- Huh?
Do you take your father's name?
Beversi!
I called everyone.
- Boo! [All together]
- Oh!
- Berme?
- Hello.
I'm not going to the forest, Dad.
Arresting the officials,
- Are you going...
- Why is it all blue?
Tell them that we sold you to the Arabs, and
that we gave you a thousand boars.
That's the achievement of our lifetime, that.
Oh, hey hey hey hey…
Boobanna, I will do business here and pay off your debt.
Yeah? Haha. Haha.
Must pay..
- I swear on you.
- Go ahead.
Only good people.
- Dad,
- Huh?
Did you give them permission to do business ?
Yes, son.
Our debt doesn't have to be paid off.
- Again, the Queen's permission?
- Oh?
Badda…
Boobanna. You never break your word.
We are coming.
Oh.. I wonder if I should stop talking for a while
.
All the women are white, Mara!
You don't need to show off all your abilities here.
- Hey Sumnira. !
- That's right, .
Do you know how to trade?
I don't know, Dad.
He doesn't know.
Hmm…!
- What is that?
- It looks like clothes. .
How about clothes?
Do business without anyone knowing.
How to do business without anyone knowing? !
Hmm, don't be silly,
Everyone knows it.
What a great man this is!
Hey pepper, cloves, turmeric, cardamom, cardamom…!
Come, come, come. Come… !
[People shouting]
Hey, Avr,
Look, we didn't know the value of our things.
Seeing that the people under the feet have grown up to the scalp,
The Bangra people couldn't get a saddle.
The Kantara people have landed at our port to trade.
I'm going to tell the king about this matter...
I understand. Go away.
Come to the office with Kantara's help.
Yuvarani..?
It's a little difficult to climb the stairs.
Can I send my son...?
Hmm.!
Did you escape from the mansion and go into business?
You are not trading in humans like me.
Don't forget that you are standing in our shoes and talking.
You can see the place.
You are the only one in charge.
Oh, Pepe..?
They were given responsibility based on their ability.
If the Kadambas knew that there were people more capable than you...
Did you know?
Hey hey…
Don't go there, hey...
Where do you lean forward?
We have given you what was in Kantara.
You have done business up to this point,
From now on, we will do our own business.
Permission was granted.
What is permission for?
Must be for business.
There should be a cut in revenue.
How much?
A merchant who lives in a canal.
Tie it up,
I don't have the strength to borrow money yet.
- You see.
- The young queen said it all.
Permission letter?
You have given permission for business,
But it shouldn't be like we did business without permission.
Will you come...?
Those people are a bit like that,
I will hide their arrogance.
He takes a pomegranate and leaves.
[Traders' conversation]
Where is Dalal?
- They're downstairs
- Ha.
Going for business, not for a big event, huh,
Look.
Be careful.
That's it, Dad.
Oh... they get all these things from here..!
Broker..!
Hey! Pepe…
- Where is Boo??
- Hello.
They don't have a sore leg, they're just out.
- Give it!
- Show me that...
How much did you bring?
How much do you need?
Bow and arrow.
[Dalal sneezes]
Take it.
You should know how to use it.
Don't you know our goal yet?
Ha ha?
- Oh, let's show it to Chinkara for once.
- Ha.
Hey…!
Listen to me, Berme!
If we step on it, they will kill us and take us away!
Ha!
Hey, are you here?
Monkeys from the forest!
[Speaking Arabic]
Do you know the price of this?!
Karma.
How much is this?
Brewery. Twelve years old.
Hey, baby, if you hit me with a hammer,
Who drinks at such an old age? Come on..
Hey, that's the special Marayya. !
Hey, there's no access to this place, Marre!
That is the horse brought to the king.
What are you doing, Boobanna?
Just came to Nodli.
Oh... what beautiful horses...!
What if we pay more than the kings?
Hey! Berme!
The one who held the line,
The hand is finished..
Please don't touch.
That's it, Marry!
Don't touch it with your hand. I'll touch it here.
- Chinkra!
- Beversi Rhyenda… !
Dad, be careful!
Oh, if I put my hand where it shouldn't be, wouldn't you just scold me without stepping on it?
Hold on... don't let go..!
[Tense music]
- This horse is breathing!
- Swami, horses...
- Run, Swami..!!
- Are you coming from here?
[Shop collapses]
Does this horse have too much heat?!
That... crazy horse...
That!
Oh! Is your leg okay?
The queen is a male horse.!?
[Confusion occurs]
Whose horse did it touch? Who?
I decided to cut off its head because of you.
Hey.
I'm here about Janrud alladtavuntu on the street.
Go and warn your king. Go..!
If you don't agree with everything we've touched on
, you'll almost have to give up.
♪ ♪
Business is all about getting better quickly.
There is something for everyone.
Am I there?
♪ Oh, my beloved.... ♪
♪ Who are you? ♪
♪ I saw a charming magic weed ♪
Hey! Did you come here with your hands tied?
♪ The brave Shakuntala, overcome by emotion ♪
♪ The love poem of my heart has blossomed for Melua.... ♪
♪ Oh, something seems to have changed ♪
♪ A rainbow is forming ♪
♪ As the war is won ♪
♪ The mist of illusion has come and gone ♪
♪ A beautiful poem opens its page amidst history. ♪
♪ Oh, my beloved.... ♪
♪ Who are you ♪
♪ I saw a charming magic weed ♪
Berme.
♪ Sweet, sweet, sweet ♪
♪ That's a crime beyond the limit ♪
♪ Start with a spark inside your chest, a beautiful light ♪
♪ Again and again and again ♪
♪ Eye for eye, you gave me pearls ♪
♪ Hands
told stories of new marriages without waving swords ♪
♪ Oh, something seems to have changed ♪
♪ A rainbow is forming ♪
♪ As the war is won ♪
♪ The mist of illusion has come and gone ♪
♪ The river of happiness is flowing ♪
♪ Like a friend's heart is broken ♪
If you knew all this, you
should have come and stayed with us.
That's what happened.
I too want to see your garden of God.
Don't chase after lightning just because you've found the light.
You are lost.
♪ ♪
- Oh...?
- That..?
Look
how much respect our things have outside.
Hey, what's all this...!?
- Next time I go
- I'll have to buy more.
Hey,
Everything we had is gone.
If you say you still need it, where will you go?
- Still inside.
- Pumpy,?
Have I brought powder for your white dress?
Don't go too deep, even if it's a mistake, son. ?
Dibba, there's no going back.
- Oh… yes!
- Hey, you take all this and go back.
- We'll see..
- Oh, I asked God. !
Sankappa!
Where to?
Will you come with us?
Oh my God, I have a good reputation in Bangla.
Now, it shouldn't happen that Sankappa died while he was out in the forest, gathering greens.
We'll see to it that you don't even touch a blade of grass.
We are behind you. Come on.
Haha. You have no respect at all. Come on!
- Do you know how much these wild men eat?
- Listen, listen.
Hey Chinkra, what are the arrangements for dinner?
Next, they beat and eat what they find.
Even if you make a mistake, you shouldn't go in front of him.
[Birds chirping]
[Surprise sound]
Like a cuckoo? ?
[Berme whistles loudly] Whoo whoo…. (whistling sound)
[Dramatic music]
[Tiger's roar]
Oh tiger!!
Hey.. Odira...that too
came here to eat what it found in front of it...
Did you know that the tiger is hungry for meat?
Dibba, it's swallowing you in one
piece, don't come back...
[Tiger's roar]
Hey!
[The Kantara people are screaming]
[Tiger's roar]
[Tense music]
Is it the stone of Karnika?
Allah Berme, leave us alone.
When we go, should we go after it?
Where is the tiger taking us?
Its home for dinner. Be quiet..!
Hey, come on.
Let's see where it goes. !
Sankappa, be careful.
I slipped as soon as I set foot on Kantara . How much more will it slip?
There are only a few camels in this forest. .
- Don't scare me, Marre. !
- You all stay here,
I'll see.
Oh, that's good.
Our elders said that there was a terrible forest in the distance .
[Ominous music]
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid.
[Strange noise]
- How did the Berme fire go out?
- How did you get here?
- Why did you go? ?
- Hold on. You guys come.
There are so many things to see in this forest.
[Ominous echoes]
[Strange noise]
Don't stop, run...
I knew you were coming from Bandi.
I didn't say that. Hmm. ?
[Wild Sins Scream]
Come on.
Will I fall victim to your rebellious courage?
- Me too.
- It's okay, come on.
[Scary music]
Stop buying what you find in this forest,
Can't you take our bodies back?
Is it good that you came this far?
Aissa! Berme...!
Got it!
In this darkness, you are seen in the light of lightning,
I am not responsible if anyone
shouts pepper.
I'll tell you first. Take it.
Let's see what arrangements can be made for dinner.
Can it be a joke?
Oh! Generous.
I'm not sure if I'll get to the top of the mountain or not.
[Men laughing together]
Whose name is this?
[Deba shouting]
Deba?!
[Tense music]
[Sound of knife being taken]
[Berme whistles loudly]
[laughing]
[Men are attacking, shouting]
[Men's shouts]
[Berme screams]
[Refreshing music]
[Tribal music]
[Strange noise]
[Men screaming in pain]
[Footsteps and screams]
[Wild Sins Screaming]
Berme!
[Tiger's roar]
[Horrible scream]
[Folk music]
Our son,
Dead...
Hey..
Go!
Go... go beyond.
Are you irresponsible...!!
You went out and got half-baked.
Now you have entered that place and
destroyed everything.
- Oh my god, how much do you know?
- Hey,
Hey, you are a self-sufficient old man,
Did the boys get together and have sex?
Is there no strength in you, and theirs has gone to the net, Darabesi?
We just went, we went.
Hey,!
Whose fault is it? ?!
Tiger.
Is it the stone of Karnika?
N Ullaya!
If we live by believing in the gods
They tried to gain power by taking control of the same gods.
People from Kadapa direction.
They lied by saying that their village was once
washed away by the flood.
Can we also find a place to live in God's flower garden
? ?
Give it.
We should have known as soon as they said, "God's flower garden ."
Someone told them the story of Karnika here.
But there is only one truth...
They came here
because they wanted a flower in the garden,
[Primal cry]
When will they realize that there is unimaginable power here ?...
Those scoundrels attempted to reach the source of our divine powers .
[Amazing music]
[Wild Sin screams in pain]
They used it to arrest him.
The forest is a place of tears of sin.
[Musiya (monkey) falls down]
We began to see the impact of their experiments on nature .
[Jabba screams angrily]
[Riot occurs]
At that moment,
Goddess Parvati sent someone to stand up to them.
Tiger God!
It comes and walks into Kantara.
It did what its owner told it to do.
Those who ran away that day,
Even today, they are sitting in a forest
and trying to become powerful.
Berme, now that tiger god, go back to that forest,
I have removed the barrier from your hand.
[Sound of metal object and falling sound]
[Traditional music]
Ramadas?
Stop for a moment.
[Music stops]
Kulasekara, !
If this is accompanied by a scolding,
Stay! Aha! ..
- Friend..
- Huh?
- For you.
- Ha, Burley, Burley.
Ramadas..?
- Give me the tune.?
- Ha!
Rappa Kodi.
[Traditional music continues]
[Sings hoarsely] That….
King!
What happened?
Are you kidding?
How are you?
Your Majesty, the port security officers
are waiting to meet you.
Your Majesty, the people of Kantara
have landed at our port to trade.
I'll see what happens.
- Ramadas..?
- Ha.
[Music continues]
Seeing him and our young queen together,
It looks like you are sitting on your throne.
- That?
- Hmm. Hmm.
[Sword hits the neck]
Hey Bhogendra,
Come and see what they are like.
Don’t give too much time. Rappa came with his head.
Hey,
Are you walking...
- Honey!
- Come on.
Hey, look there…!
Honey, what do you want?
[in Arabic]
Huh?
How much do you need?
Have you lost the will to live?
- Just give it back..
- Who are you?
Oh my goodness…
Don't be silly, Marre.
I found out you were here, and
I came here with great difficulty, hiding my face.
Take me to Kantara too.
Even if they die, they will still be there.
- Wife?
- No, dad.
That's a thief.
This is..
It's not too early to start a new life anyway.
Oh, I'm early.
Hey, Nangirl.
Is that true?
How did you know we were here?
Only for me,
Everyone knows about Bhangra, Ghingra, and Raja Giza. Hmm.
[Trumpet sounds]
- Gunananda…?
- Huh?
Should the praise begin as soon as the chariot stops?
You can watch it if you want.
Stop.
Hnuhn. I don't mind.
- King of Kings,
- Hey!
- Bangra's clan crest, !
- Hey Bhogendra,
- The power of King Kulasekara,
- Wow!
Mahamantri Bhogendra has arrived.
I don't need to say all this, do I?
Don't you hear a word?
Beaversey.
What will I do to him?
Where is that traitorous Booba?
- Ministers?
- Bhogendra Eche.
Cunning,
Isn't your kingdom in the port of Bangra?
[Sound of whipping]
Everyone is watching.
Go inside and talk.
Ah, it should be here.
[Sound of whipping]
Give respect to the elderly, Bhogendra. ?
Is it polite? Hmm.
Ika.
[Heroic music]
Bhogendra, is it okay to let go of the whip now?
- What if I don't leave? ?
- Hey. !
- Ramadas..?
- Ha, ha…
[Traditional music continues]
[Sound of whipping]
[Music increases]
Hey, Karira, the navy!
It's sinking, ministers...
Doesn't the one who built the boat know how to sink it? Hnu, ?!
Dad, from now on I will be with Kantara.
I have to go, son. I've pressed the button.
That?
Do you want to defeat us all, sink our navy, and
establish your rule in the port of Bangra?
Hmm, this wasn't in their heads.
- What you said was good.
- Bhogendra...?
From this moment on, the bonds are ours.
You don't even need permission to do business here
. You don't need a tax.
The Bangla people won't accept what we have touched.
From now on, we will make the whole world agree...
[Trumpet shells]
Clear the space until the noise stops,
If not, you will have to put an end to the trade in humans
yourself.
[Traditional music continues]
The chariot overturned. Hmm.
Hmm.
Huhu huhu!
Son of a whore
I wonder if the Porchins sang.
What kind of face do you see, Kulasekara?
Cut off his head...
You said it yourself,
Don't bite.
This Bikanasi has come here by auctioning off the Bangra mariyade,
Will you leave him alone?
You left behind the Kantaras, these are ours.
Saying that they are ours, why did they send those who were not in their power?
The bondsmen left our hands today.
I have placed you on the throne, ...
Okay, Kursidralla...
For what purpose?
A king in name, but
no control over the army
You gave the treasure to the one who left with the sweat of that Kantara
.
- It's the same dogs' breast milk--
- Kulasekara! !
I was talking beyond the limit. ...
I can't be bothered by the limits you set anymore
.
Furthermore, the army and treasury
are all under my control.
Whatever decision is made,
it is not without your consent.
I'll take it myself.
Keep this in your head.
I'm ready to leave everything in your hands and take to the streets,
Kulasekara.
Whatever you want to do next, I'll do it myself.
Just sit back and watch with respect.
You said you wanted to talk...
What's the matter?
You shouldn't have insulted him , forgetting about him in a crowded meeting .
In the same meeting, they also insulted me , forgetting that I am the king .
If you do what you have to do as a king
, you will receive respect.
Everything was available!
Hey, do you want to get rid of all your nonsense now?
What responsibility are you talking about?
Shut up quietly and watch your work.
They have defeated the naval forces and
captured the prisoners.
We should do something ourselves before the Kadambas get involved.
What do you want to do now, King?
We negotiate ourselves.
Are they Opatara?
They should give what they asked for and accept it.
I made a mistake.
- Did you just say it was a mistake?...
- Did you say it from the heart?
I know you are very embarrassed by me.
Give me another chance, I'll make everything right.
Wait.
How do you think it should be fixed?
Until now,
I have done what was out of your control.
You don't even ask for an army.
You just did it once and showed it.
Do you think you should do it again?
How big is it?
They will not lay hands on our prisoners,
I will walk into their divine flower garden.
Rajalakshmi,
Get Kanakavati married soon.
I don't trust him either.
You are the only one who has elevated me to the top,
it is up to me to descend.
To these hands that have done the coronation...
They even come to throw me out by the neck.
Don't make your hand so long, Dad.
If I have a bill in my hand, it will be difficult for you again.
Hey, come on…
Bara dog…
Can you show me which hand has the letter?
What happened?
Caution.
Alas,
Kings...
How did it go? (Laughing)
Mom…
Don't worry, I didn't poison you.
Let's relax and sleep for a day or two .
[Music]
I will wash away the stain attached to the clan
with the blood of Kantara.
Soldiers... put this one in prison.
It wakes up your sleeping grandfather and just
fills his head with all the unnecessary things. That's it.
When we all suffer, it's good for Bangra
.
Are you still thinking of destroying it, brother?
Hmm.
The wild man is strong,
Come back after getting married...
How are you, old man?
Kulasekara is not worthy,
He was also placed on the throne, and Bangra was
You mean you rule? Ahaha…
Go, put them to sleep.
I wonder if I could bring a blue one.
If he knew it was a boat I built,
he wouldn't be able to sit on it even if he died.
[Sound of horse steps]
God's flower garden. (Laughing)
[Kulashekar laughs]
The place where my grandfather set foot.
It's beautiful.
I followed in their footsteps. Isn't that right?
Huh?
Ha... ha.
This forest, this dark, silent,
How peacefully they are sleeping.
The only royal dharma is to kill those who are sleeping.
Soldiers..!
[Drumming sound]
[Jabbajja's warning cry]
Whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo….
Burned and burned...!
[Sound of arrows]
Hey… come on…
Friends… Kantara is ours now…
Have fun.
[Warrior shout]
Sin.
For so many years, you have lived in darkness,
I had to come to the light.
Ullaya, Ullaya…
What a mistake we have made, Ullaya…
Hey, don't touch it like that, go away...
Oh my god.. he's dead.
Hey Ika, what's wrong? Drink some water,
Drink water.
[Children are crying]
[Kulashekar laughs]
Hey... whose pot is the fire burning now?!
Hey go, go…
Wild chickens!
God of knowledge.
- Is it beautiful?
- Oh, yes.
[Soldier falls to the ground]
[Women screaming in pain]
- Grandpa,… Grandpa…
- Oh!
Grandpa…
Hey, where is my horse?
Oh.. irrigation.
[Cheenkra's tired voice]
Hurry up!
Oh, come on. (Laughing)
The medicine is half-finished, bring it quickly,
Did you put water in your stomach...
Oh baby….
A little bit...
[Sound of a sword being stabbed]
♪ God came from above to meditate on earth below ♪
♪ Parvati built a flower bed ♪
♪ They set fire to the flower of God ♪
♪ Gods, where are you now? The voice is ringing ♪
♪ Even God and Parvati would have come ♪
♪ Even you gods won't come ♪
[Song melody]
♪ ♪
[Music]
This Kantara is as sacred as Mount Kailash, the highest place of your God .
Today, the eyes of sinners have fallen on this place.
The living things here were eclipsed.
It is time for us, who have been born in the womb and brought death on our backs,
to be unable to save this soil.
Manichil!
Don't talk without us!
[Scream of pain]
On which rock are you sitting?
You sat on that rock.
Religion for religion, truth for truth.
♪ Religion to religion ♪
♪ Truth to truth ♪
♪ The path you walk is poison, O Lord ♪
♪ About Mother Earth ♪
♪ My heart is torn and torn ♪
♪ Who has forgotten the axe of sorrow ♪
[Manichilla continues]
Oh! Here is your God
♪ Oh my God, the womb is broken ♪
Beggarly
- ♪ Who's that? ♪
- Where are you?
Hey…
Artists.
Will you not relieve the suffering that has come to your sinful family
?
♪ Our waiting God ♪
♪ Where are you? ♪
Who else should I call?
I came, didn't I?
♪ The soil of truth is full of poison ♪
♪ The laughter of unrighteousness ♪
♪ Oh my God! ♪
Happiness is chosen.
Come, I will give you a boon.
Hey Karkondu Bannira...
With respect.
Oh… Ullaya….
Oh my God!
Ullai. ...
"Oh, the god who guards the border!
Bring together all the forces here,
Leave the sky and step onto the earth.
Erase the footprints of sinners.
Let their hearts break at the sight you set.
Let a single blow from you
cause the blood of demons to flow.
Your Brahma demon ran away in fear, didn't he?
Hey
Where did you go, leaving all of your people behind?
- Abbey?
- Bermey... (crying)
Mom?
Just a good voice.
Hey!
Oh my….
Come, Guliga , break their arrogance and pride and save the religion.
Abbey…
[Berme trembling]
[screaming in disgust]
Baby..come to my lap baby.
Lord.. you fool!
[When the darkness covers my body,
Baidi?
[When the darkness covers my body]
Play (instruments)
[Loud instruments]
[When the darkness covers my body]
[Primal cry]
[Loud instruments]
Oh, dance performance.
[Primal cry]
Before disrespecting the soil where Swami Varahamurthy was
Hey!
The dogs that came to the Dombarata Nodli?
Hold on…
Rudra Guliga…
Hey!
The border guards on this holy soil are there to punish those who have strayed from the religion.
Did you forget the field manager?
Rahu is a fool!
Trickster!
[Sound of bodies falling]
[Scary sound]
Dark-eyed fool
[Primal cry]
Huh?
Bloody eyes...
[Primal cry]
Fireball
As a reward for your deeds,
give your blood to this soil in the form of a flower.
You protect religion, oh...
Swami Raja Guliga...
[Kulashekar screams for his life]
[Berme calms down]
[Berme pales]
♪♪
♪ The stone of mercy is the stumbling block of man ♪
♪ The finger wound won't heal ♪
♪ Dharmava Darpake Balikodo Durulara ♪
♪ Even God cannot be defeated by crying ♪
♪ A fierce thunderbolt struck and shook the earth ♪
♪ Have you heard the hiccuping lap of Mother Earth? ♪
♪♪
♪ A wound in the womb is destiny ♪
♪ I will wander my whole life looking for a cure ♪
♪ You're fighting with someone you don't know ♪
♪ You will lose yourself in search of yourself.. ♪
♪ Even if you swallow all the sins, the Ganges will swallow them ♪
♪ Leave me alone, I'll regret it ♪
♪ Totta flower garland when Darpadali merevaga ♪
♪ Will the flower fall tomorrow and become a noose? ♪
♪ ♪
Oh!
♪ This life is a curse worse than death ♪
♪ The medicine that removes all sorrow is in the pyre.. ♪
♪ Everything has an end in the beginning ♪
♪ I can't find a clue about you.. ♪
♪ The mother's breast milk flowed like blood ♪
♪ Tell me, who has what share in this sin? ♪
♪ The bridge crossed to conquer fate ♪
♪ That fate has become a game of dice! ♪
♪♪
Oh my God?
O king,
the linga of God, which was to be installed in the sanctum sanctorum, has cracked.
[Emotional music]
- Whose is it?
- Pepe, from the port of Bangra.
It's not like there are good people there too.
When you have insulted the gods of God,
Did he agree to live inside the temple you built?
What's broken here isn't the stone, it's his mind.
How do I fix this?
Brahma will not let the Kalash become a vessel until he is satisfied .
No matter what, there is a peace in this place.
Build from the outside.
It should be there.
How can you be so lazy if you skip meals like this?
Ika.
I
can't live like this, Berme. (Crying)
What a joke,
Are you the one talking?
What else?
Do we, the animals in the forest , come and play and go hunting when they feel like it ?
It's like we don't even have the right to scare them
.
It's not to scare.
We have the right to stand above them.
It's always been said that if a tree wants to grow tall, its roots
must be strong.
[Sound of drum]
[Soldiers screaming in pain]
We are not used to women killing children, are we?
If we go one step further
, we have to do that too.
Please give me a chance to talk.
Haha.
If our people touch it, they will cut off our heads, Jabba.
We know you are very hurt by us.
But we are just as lost as you.
I should have thought that the fire that set our place on fire
would burn you too.
Before you cross the line in greed and hurt our people,
You too could have thought about it for once.
Who drew the border?
Did they run away in fear? Did they hide inside in fear?
If you cross the power,
It's greed if we cross it. Isn't it?
What other authority?
The respect that existed among the surrounding feudal lords has now come to the streets.
The crown that was supposed to be on the throne has fallen to the ground.
Go and atone for the sin you committed earlier.
That's what I came here for.
Which powers have we wronged?
We are told that we must give it a place of worship in the courtyard of God and
atone for our sins.
Who are you to give space to our God?
We are in the place God has given us.
Don't be selfish,
This is a good opportunity for us all to live equally
.
Enslave our own people and
build a kingdom with their blood,
Fill your treasury with the wealth of our forest,
Are you talking about equality now?
To right all our wrongs,
this is the only way left,
Please allow me.
We agreed, but our god
doesn't agree to come to you.
Are you saying this yourself?
Is this what your God is saying?
[Traditional folk music]
[Primal cry]
Ala, the child I bore,
It's hard, don't think about it.
[Primal cry]
My heart is filled with joy there, my children,
It is my duty to guard Ullay's house with my head bowed as if waiting for you .
There are some truths that appear in my mind.
Only I and my beloved know that,
This is not what they did,
I am being used by my own pleasure,
Don't be confused within yourself...
Go and see it for yourself!
[Primal cry]
[Emotional melody]
♪♪
♪ I don't know, the path of devotion to Lord Shiva.. ♪
♪ All I know is that God is the one who saves ♪
♪ Cheers to your stay.. ♪
♪ The presence of a tormented Maya.. ♪
♪ This is Kapoo.. ♪
♪ Know that devotion to Shiva is also the path. ♪
- Whose?
- The Kadamba side.
♪ ♪
♪ Om ♪
♪ Gananamtva Ganapatigam Havamahey ♪
♪ The poet is the poet of the poem. ♪
♪ Jyeshtharajam Brahmanam Brahmanaspata aa nah ♪
♪ I am the one who is blessed with the divine power ♪
♪ Kiss me ♪
♪ Come and finish it.. ♪
It is a tradition for those who come from the forest to build chariots.
- Here...
- We'll walk you through it from now on.
♪ Survey Janahitam ♪
♪ Pranam Sthapita.. ♪
♪ May the power of Shiva unite.. ♪
♪ Chanting mantras, devotion.. ♪
♪ I am a pure-hearted person ♪
♪ Peace of mind, what a journey ♪
♪ The body is the temple ♪
♪ The world's grace is also the grace of God.. ♪
♪ Love is radiant in its form.. ♪
♪ The accumulation of virtue is the ultimate happiness.. ♪
♪ Yatra Shraddhacha Bhaktim ♪
♪ May you be blessed with happiness.. ♪
♪ I wish.. ♪
♪ Know that Shiva is the path of devotion ♪
♪ ♪
[Vedic mantras]
[Nagare, the sound of instruments]
In this soil created by Parashurama,
the Brahma Kalash of the temple of God,
You have fulfilled it as a song,
Praying that God will be pleased and grant us all long life, health, and prosperity,
The Kadambas
gave a golden idol as a memorial offering.
Everyone should accept it with devotion.
Chicken.
- Can we touch this?
- Hmm.
Despite all the differences between us , the Bangla people
You have done what you asked for in a good way,
This is a historic decision.
I congratulate you on this move
on behalf of all Bangla people.
If you ask for something good, we will do everything we can to give it.
I know.
I don't know.
If you knew, your son would have been sitting on the throne.
[Music]
Huh. Okay,
We heard something good today.
Will you give it?
Hmm, I know what you're asking.
We only needed the bonds for trade,
Not for power.
We gave it back.
But I have one condition.
Tell me.
Those who have been forcibly enslaved must be freed.
The divine is established in this soil.
Otherwise, walk on the path of religion.
This is a historic decision.
On behalf of all Kantara
, I congratulate you on this move.
Hmm. It might work for you.
You can be brave.
Why did you stop?
If you heat it too much, it won't melt, Sankappa.
What is your father's name for Karali?
Blow air...
You were once a prisoner in my prison.
Times change, Pepe.
- We just have to change.
- I understand.
When to put air in?
[Pig making noise]
When the cup of sin overflows,
the king's steps lead to iniquity,
Will you correct your actions and prevent Bangra's peace
from burning and becoming ashes?
Alas, will you listen to the sound of the gnat and
step on the pile of ashes?
The decision is up to you.
Do you need God to commit immorality in the name of devotion ?
Do you need God...?
[Primal cry]
[Festival atmosphere]
Having experienced hell all his life,
he is breathing peacefully today.
Seeing their happiness brings me a sense of relief.
Why don't you just go to sleep and stop watching all this
?
I am watching.
You still have about 10 minutes to eat.
Come.
Berme!
When you lose your way,
you don't need anyone to show you the way, son!
I just came to see you.
Those who desire the flower garden of God
Never trust anyone, son.
Oh, my God?
[Man crying]
[Ominous music]
[The magician is crying]
[Men and women wailing]
Berme!
[People continue to cry]
Lord God,
diseases that are invisible to human eyes
Today, it has come to children.
Our generation is falling victim to these diseases that are like plague.
You are the one who saved me, you are the one who killed me.
You left the sky
and came to earth, killed this poison and drank nectar.
We need to get rid of this disease. Lord God."
Someone has imprisoned the gods.
[The magician is humming]
People from Kadapa direction.
Why is this called a flower garden?
Those who desire the flower garden of God..
God's flower garden!
[Baidi screams in pain]
Drink our breast milk..
We'll be babysitting for a while.
Everything is going well.
Our son
Dead (crying)
Never trust anyone, son.
Brother,
You can't do it, leave me alone.
Don't burn your hands with it.
Someone has imprisoned the gods.
We agreed, but our God
doesn't agree to let you come together.
Is this what you are saying?
Is this what your God is saying?
God's flower garden.
Fearing the forces of the forest,
I had been sitting there for so many years, hoping there would be no war.
Kanakavathi!
Kantara should be ours,
Their divine stone
should become the stepping stone to our palace.
It's not that easy,
They did not come just to establish a god.
To establish religion.
Don't be afraid,
To fulfill your wish, there is one more task left.
[Ominous music]
Kanakavati doesn't have the patience to wait any longer.
My sword is thirsty for blood.
Neither of us has the strength to scare him.
Is it a renunciation?
The child who didn't move her arms and legs back then,
is now sitting on the throne,
I have conquered death without any intention,
The blood of the Bangra, the breast milk of the Kadapas.
Both are poison.
The king of Bangra stood before the daughter,
Let's not have a war, let's not have one.
Take up your weapon,
I give you the right.
When they all grew up,
I wished they would all be in Kantara.
We can't see these children today.
You have nurtured and protected us for so many years.
The gods' eyes may be watering.
The fire that ignited their faith in us,
It should become a forest fire and be burned to ashes.
- Oh my God.
- I can't stand the thought of you anymore, Jabba.
This is not a war we are fighting for our own selfish interests.
This war is for the divine stone in their possession.
As if sending hordes of demons to stop the spread of evil
,
But today,
everyone in this garden of God is God's flock.
[The Kantaras prepare for war]
[Somber music]
[Sound of eagle flying]
Did you come to Hokke to see how many people there were?
[Everyone looks on in surprise]
[Footsteps]
[Somber music]
[Mourning music]
We have put a stop to the gangs in Kantara.
Even beyond that, if any forces come,
I see and say.
But
only to stand in front of the pride who came from the original place...
[Evil music]
The power of three generations must unite.
[Berme screams in anger]
[space noise]
[Sound of arrows]
[Berme screams in anger]
[War cry]
[Arrow strikes against shields]
[Wheel noise]
[Explosion sound]
Hold the shield...
Ha! Ha!
Give me the dogs.
[Conch sound]
[Sound of burning wood chips]
[Sound of door being smashed, men screaming in fear]
Ya Ali, Sankappa. The border of Bangra is powdery powdery.
Doesn't the one who built the wall know how to break it?
Jai Kantara…
♪ When will the bed be tied ♪
♪ The bed is the source of all suffering ♪
♪ When did Kantara arrive ♪
♪ The entire village was destroyed and the forest was dark ♪
[War cry]
[Scary music]
♪ It was in the beginning, Banu, ♪
♪ Hill, land, blue sea ♪
♪ Everyone's property, whose ♪
♪ It's not my father's to give! ♪
[Berme screams angrily]
♪♪
[Kantara's warriors scream in anger]
Tell the king something.
♪ ♪
Do you see our strength?
I never imagined that such a big
war would erupt from just one of our hunts.
♪ ♪
♪ We are calling you with the permission of God and Goddess Parvati ♪
♪ Hey! Build a fortress.. and become the ruler of the city ♪
♪ The forest said, wake up! ♪
♪ The forest fire.. has come to the town.. ♪
♪ Who can stop it? The flame is so high ♪
♪ Shout out loud, wake up!!! ♪
[Song melody]
♪ ♪
Alas,
Go to the doctor. Go to the doctor, quickly...
- Where is the dog running?
- Oh!
Lord, we are with you.
♪ Hey! Build a fortress.. and become the ruler of the city ♪
♪ The forest said, wake up! ♪
♪ The forest fire.. has come to the town.. ♪
♪ Who's stopping you?.. Wash your feet and welcome ♪
♪ While doing the ocean♪
Go.
What are you looking for here in this dust?
♪ With the permission of God and Parvati ♪
♪ We are calling you ♪
♪ The forest fire.. has come to the town.. ♪
♪ Who can stop it? The flame is so high ♪
♪ Shout out loud, wake up! ♪
[Song melody]
They crossed the border.
Hold them back until the sun sets.
[Sound of warriors fighting]
[Jnanadeva screams]
♪ We are calling you with the permission of God and Goddess Parvati ♪
♪ Hey! The fortress.. ♪
Ha! Anniversary?
- You!
- Hmm.
Did you come for the war
? Did you come for the long haul?
Damn it!
♪ Courage is a weapon for pride.. ♪
♪ Religion is the medicine for hatred.. ♪
♪ No one swears.. ♪
♪ When we stand up and say "Peace!" ♪
♪ No one is as sharp as an arrow today ♪
♪ The elephant roared when it heard that its feet were warm ♪
O
Good?
What are you looking at here? Look ahead, your death is coming.
[Soldier's scream and attack]
[Sound of sword piercing]
Huh? He's not dead, is he? Come on...
♪ Hey! Build a fortress.. and become the ruler of the city ♪
♪ The forest said, wake up! ♪
♪ The forest fire.. has come to the town.. ♪
♪ Who can stop the flame that rises so high? ♪
♪ Shout out loud, wake up!!! ♪
[War cry]
[Scary music]
The power of Vijayendra was prevalent in Rajashekara.
The sound made when the power of Vijayendra is infused in Rajashekara.
Kings.
Grandpa?
I want the flower garden of God that you desire.
[Fire is burning]
[Horses are galloping; the ground is shaking]
[Horse neighing]
[Warriors screaming in anger]
Nochi!
[Chinkra suffocates to death]
Grandpa?
The guardian of Kantara.
[Song melody]
The blockade must be lifted.
What to do?
When you were found in the well, who left you?
No one even knew who left you.
Today is the time to show why you came
,
Go.
The Ganges shows the way.
The king of Bangra.
Go away!
Has God come here?
It's not just what came here,
They settled here.
Are you still there?
They are inside.
Would you go and see?
[Berme falls to the ground]
Today is the time to show why you came
,
Go.
The Ganges shows the way.
[Burmey takes a deep breath]
[Wall collapsing]
[Rajashekar gasps]
[Sound of magical breathing]
How many more people will come to guard the waiting room?
You will shed a stream of blood on the stone of your god.
Ullaya!
[Refreshing music]
[Heavy breathing]
[Breathing sound continues]
[The sound of breathing gets closer]
[Brahma-Rakshasa's roar]
[Berme groans in pain]
Ah!
[Exciting music]
[Primal cry]
[Sound of approaching flames]
♪♪
[Tiger's roar]
This is my hunt!
♪ ♪
[Primal cry]
[Tiger's roar]
With my body covered in ink,
I held a rusty trident.
You will not immediately become a member of God's family.
Standing before you is the source of creation,
Female.
If you dare, touch it.
Come.
I am not the one who will touch you, who has done a disservice to the birth of a girl
.
Needed for your destruction,
With God's permission, Mother
Sankebare, daughter of Galibhadra Kumara,
My older sister.
My sister is coming...
[Sound of a loud bang approaching]
Are you listening?
[The sound of the meter intensifies]
[Primal cry]
I have come and stood before you in the form of Chavundi, the creator of the origin you mentioned .
Break your head,
"I will make Ullaya's broken
mind one."
Chavundi
[Kanakawati screams angrily]
Chicken.
[Breaking neck]
[Rajashekar screams in sorrow]
Light!
In light, everything that is before the eyes is visible..
But this is not light.
Vision.
The light that shows everything , both what happened in the past and
what will happen in the future.
What do you see?
[Primal cry]
♪ ♪
♪ The form of a boar is divine ♪
♪ Varasmita Vadanam. ♪
♪ Diamond tooth ♪
♪ Raksha Kavacham. ♪
♪♪
♪ Shiva Sambhuta ♪
♪ Born on Earth ♪
♪ The one who believes is the one who gives ♪
♪ A thousand gods' hearts are happy ♪
♪ The begging and the slandering are worshipped... ♪
♪♪
- Did they disappear here too?
- Hmm.
Where did the well that was here go again?
That's another legend...