The soul is here.
But speaking
the truth in love,
let us grow into Him
who is the head, Christ.
From him the whole body,
joined together
by every supporting ligament,
growth of the body...
Take off
your former way of life,
the old self
corrupted by deceitful desires,
to be renewed
in the spirit of your minds,
and to put on the new self,
created according
to God’s likeness
in righteousness
and purity of the truth.
Thank you.
You can return to your place.
As you've noticed,
there are new girls among us.
Welcome.
I hope we'll have fun
and create something
beautiful together.
Now, please take your places.
The new girls too.
Stand in your voice groups.
Okay, I'll help you.
You can go here.
And you, come here
and stand next to Ana-Maria.
Move closer, so I can see you.
That's fine. Please remember
your new positions.
Remember who's on your left
and who's on your right.
Let's start with some warm-up.
Put your sheets down.
Let's do the support exercise.
Relax and...
Continue.
That's it.
Your diaphragm must work.
Split it.
Now triplets.
Breathe in every time.
Every time, okay?
Up.
A bit more.
Grab it on high. That's it.
Fine, thanks.
Let's do a breathing exercise.
Bend over towards the floor.
Your head is dangling,
your neck is relaxed.
Arms beside your body.
Breathe in through your nose
as if you wanted
to smell something.
So the lumbar part expands.
That's the point.
When you smell it,
I want to hear your breath,
a short breath,
but expand the lumbar part.
Again.
You have to feel
the lumbar part expanding.
Hello, girls. Don't mind me.
Hey.
The head-mistress wants me
to change a bulb in her office.
Again?
- I need the ladder.
- You know where it is. Take it.
We'll sing "Igraj kolce".
It says forte. Don't scream.
Lower your chin and open.
And...
More.
Grab it.
And...
That's it.
Listen to each other.
Forte.
Altos, something's wrong.
The 'igraj kolo' part.
It must be prominent.
Otherwise...
...the song falls apart.
I have to hear you.
Hana, can you do it?
And...
A bit more strongly. Again.
A bit better.
Lucia, right?
Now you, please.
Good, a bit more
fullness please.
And...
Much better. Again. Grab it.
Come on.
Yes, nice.
Okay, let's...
The forte at the beginning
must be clearer, stronger.
We must be one.
Lucia.
Stop daydreaming and join us.
Girls,
the rehearsal isn't over yet.
So concentrate please.
All together now.
We have a lot of work to do.
It's a good thing
we're going... - Where?
To Cividale.
For intensive rehearsals
at the Ursuline convent.
- We'll rehearse, eat...
- Apricot dumplings.
Apricot intensive dumplings.
- And stuff ourselves with...
- Gelato.
Have your parents sign it.
See you on Tuesday.
Here.
Thanks.
By the way...
The conductor always wears
really funny shorts
at those rehearsals.
Really?
You'll see.
I'm Ana-Maria, by the way.
- Lucia.
- Nice to meet you.
Cool lipstick.
Thanks.
I can put it on you if you like.
Oh, no, no need.
My aunt from Paris gave me this.
Wow.
Your aunt from Paris?
Look at this.
A gift from her aunt from Paris.
- Really?
- It's awesome.
So pretty.
Can I put it on please?
- Me first.
- Okay.
Okay.
- What?
- Nice one.
- Spread it.
- Is there too much of it?
No, there's never too much.
You'll have to
finish it yourself.
- I will.
- Okay.
Now you.
Awesome.
That's pretty too.
- Yeah?
- So pretty.
- It's your turn.
- It's really nice. - Yeah?
This colour really suits you.
- It really does.
- Let's take a photo.
Come on.
Let's take a look
in the mirror.
It really suits you. Here.
Lucia.
I have to go.
- How did the rehearsal go?
- Well.
- The conductor praised me.
- Is that so?
He gave us forms
for you to sign.
What forms?
For traditional intensive
rehearsals in Cividale.
How long do they last?
- Three days.
- Oh.
Did you plan
on wearing lipstick there too?
Well?
No.
I thought
we'd agreed about lipstick.
- Yes.
- Yes? So?
But all girls wear it.
You have to be like them?
You can't think for yourself?
Lucia, you're 16 years old.
Lipstick isn't appropriate
for school.
I wore it only
at the rehearsal.
- You're too young.
- Why? - What do you mean?
Do you think
you can do anything you like?
- That nobody's watching you?
- You're exaggerating.
Give me the lipstick.
I told you to give it to me!
You can't sleep either?
No.
Me neither.
But he sure can.
He sleeps on the couch
every afternoon
and then in front of
the TV at night.
Do you know what helps?
What?
Ice-cream.
What is that?
- I don't know, a film.
- Turn it down a bit.
Turn it up.
He won't wake up. You'll see.
An earthquake wouldn't wake him.
- Ana-Maria, come on.
- I'm sorry, Klara-Maria.
You're such a Mary.
I am Mary.
- Saint Mary.
- Not anymore.
- For a while now.
- Shush.
Hey.
Uršula.
- Uršu...
- What do you want?
- Good morning, Uršula.
- You keep sleeping.
- So what?
- Good for you.
A deer. Look!
Look! A deer, girls.
A deer, look!
- Did you see it?
- Yeah. - Another one!
Oh, I need to show
you something.
- What?
- Lucia, look.
OMG.
Look at those boobs.
What is it?
3,000 years ago they
worshiped a goddess
instead of a god.
Because they had
such big vulvas.
Yeah.
What was it like
when they got their period?
- They had pads, didn't they?
- But not the same as now.
My grandma said
they were made from cloth.
- Cloth? - Yeah.
- It must've all leaked through.
Yuck!
When did you first get
your period, Klara?
- When I was 13.
- What about you?
I don't have it yet.
Really? You're 16
and still don't have it?
Some get it later.
It's totally normal.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
you're a woman.
You're a woman
when you have your period.
So you're a full-on woman?
Yeah, I am.
She isn't.
Look, Lucia,
this is the Devil's Bridge.
When they built it,
they had a pact with the devil,
so they had to
sacrifice a virgin
and push her off it.
Do you think she already had
her period? - What?
The fertile ones
were worth more.
- What? It's true.
- Uršula, the historian.
It's general knowledge.
- God bless you.
- Hello. - Welcome, Bojan.
- Nice of you to come.
- Thank you.
Hello, girls. Welcome.
Please come in. Follow me.
How nice to see young people.
Let's go. Was it
a long journey?
Not at all.
- What's that?
- We're renovating.
I hope our workers
won't bother you.
- No, we're used to it.
- They're very nice.
But they don't speak
any Slovenian.
There's just been an accident.
As the workers were carrying
the big ladder,
they accidentally hit our Mary.
Her hand fell off.
Lord help us.
Now, we'll have to call
the restorers again.
They're quite expensive,
right?
Yes.
That worries me, you know.
Come on. Where are you?
Four to a room as we agreed.
We meet downstairs
for rehearsals in 15 minutes.
15:25.
I'm going to bed.
- Good night, Uršula.
- Good night.
Show me your swimming suit.
Frog for lunch.
Frog in the clouds.
Hey.
What are you looking at?
The olive tree.
You're looking at
the olive tree?
A beautiful olive tree.
Are the rooms nice?
He's wearing those pants.
We're practically all here,
right?
Don't wander around the convent.
Where are the rehearsals?
Always here
unless we agree otherwise. Okay?
Okay.
Any questions?
- No.
- No? Okay, let's start then.
Let's open
"Something’s in the air".
It says mezzo piano.
Altos, do what we've agreed.
Slowly, drop by drop.
Intonation.
Here comes the phrase.
You've done the triplet better.
Hold it.
The triplet could be better.
And...
That's it.
Crescendo and...
Don't stop.
That's right.
Attention. Forte.
Soprano,
I'm looking at you. Attention.
Good, let's continue.
Attention.
Altos, where are you?
It's crescendo.
That's it. I have to hear you.
Jesus! What is that?
We can't work like this.
I can't work.
Excuse me!
Hey!
They can't hear you.
Use your diaphragm.
Let's go back in.
Close the windows please.
And the doors too.
Nothing.
The concert clothes
are back there. Try them on.
Let's make use of this time.
Klara, it's like
you picked the colours.
- Do you really think so?
- Yeah.
Lucia.
Thanks.
- Look.
- Wait.
Sound is light.
Aren't you coming?
What? Oh, yeah...
I need to change
and I'll be right there.
Beautiful. Nice materials.
It falls nicely.
If any of the dresses
are too long,
we'll shorten them.
- They're a bit impractical.
- Costumes are never practical.
It’s the appearence
that counts.
We look like virgins
for sacrifice.
Girls, come on.
What are you saying?
You look beautiful.
Forest fairies.
They suit you. Really.
What are you doing?
Can you lower your skirt
below the knees like the others?
Please, girls.
A choir is a joint formation,
if one of you doesn’t conform,
it'll fall apart.
Stop fussing, you look nice.
The dresses suit you.
You're great.
Let's get to work.
And...
Should we take a closer look?
Which one would be right
for sister Magda?
The one on the right.
Wow.
Hello.
- Come on, let's go.
- Wait a minute.
- They're looking at us.
- Let them.
Lucia.
Are you up for something?
Yeah?
Watch out! Let's go!
- Wait!
- Run!
What's with you?
You're totally crazy.
Does it smell nice?
That means you like
his pheromones
and you two would be
good together.
Here.
It's yours now.
But you stole it.
I did it for you.
I didn't ask you to.
You didn't need to.
You're welcome.
- But we have to return it.
- No, it doesn't matter.
Isn't...
Isn't it like...
Isn't it a sin?
Yeah.
Then it's sour grapes for us.
Don't you know that?
If you sin,
you have to eat some sour
grapes to atone for it.
Seriously. Cross my heart.
I'm not kidding. I swear.
It's our grandmas'
ancient knowledge.
I've had to eat heaps of them.
You don't believe me?
I believe you.
Okay, here you go.
- Are you afraid?
- No.
Okay. Ready,
steady, go.
You mustn't spit it out.
If you don't suffer,
it won't work.
With confidence.
No, come on!
Truth or dare?
Dare... No, truth.
Okay.
Who from school
have you slept with?
- Did you have to?
- Of course she did.
Do I have to tell
you when too?
Tell us everything.
Once after school,
I went to a schoolmate's house
to get homework.
It started to rain,
but I didn't have my umbrella,
so I was soaking wet,
I couldn't walk.
- Then I came...
- Oh, come on, just tell us.
Wait.
Which boy was it?
Luka.
- Luka!?
- Yeah.
Yuck. His hair is always greasy.
No, he was so cute.
- Oh, come off it.
- How romantic.
I just knew he was a pussy.
Does he at least
have a big one?
That's another question.
I won't tell you just like that.
What about you, Lucia?
It's not my turn yet.
- You're cheating.
- No, it's your first time.
Those are the rules
and you have to follow them.
Truth or dare?
Okay, dare.
No.
- Pick truth, it's much easier.
- Much easier.
- Fine, truth then.
- Okay.
Have you ever seen a naked man?
- Tell us.
- No.
But you know
what a penis looks like?
Yeah.
Describe it.
Do you find it beautiful?
- No.
- Does it attract you?
Not really.
Does the vagina attract you?
Vulvas of goddesses.
No.
So nothing attracts you?
How do you know if something
attracts you? - You feel it.
You feel warm
down there
and it tingles and just...
...feels good.
Do you ever masturbate?
Play with yourself?
That's...
- That's not fair.
- Yeah, it is.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Oh, come on.
We've just warmed up.
Pick truth.
Come on.
No, dare.
We have to come up
with something
really hard for her.
Wait.
Yeah.
Okay.
Dear Lucia,
your dare is
to passionately,
really passionately,
kiss the most beautiful girl
in the convent.
That's... Whatever.
Want to switch to truth now?
Turn off your flashlights.
Plunk.
Put out your hand like this.
Close your eyes.
Concentrate only
on what you feel.
Do you like it?
What is it?
The workers are down in the bay.
Should we go and take a look?
Otherwise they'll hear us.
- Isn't it great?
- OMG, Klara.
That one is so tanned.
Oh my God.
What a teddy bear.
He really is one.
Look at the one in boxer shorts.
Fuck, I forgot my phone.
Klara, can you go get it so
we can take photos?
It's in my bag.
Why me?
- Go before they leave.
- No, I want to watch them.
Don't be a pain!
Lucia.
Look at him for a bit longer.
Have you ever kissed anyone?
Where did that come from?
We're just talking.
That's what friends talk about.
I have and it was great.
And what if I haven't?
No big deal.
You can try with your hand.
First.
You hold your hand like this.
No, no.
Come on, don't be lame.
I did it and now
I'm a great kisser.
- Come, like this.
- Okay.
You've mastered that.
Now do it with your tongue.
Want to try?
What a creeper.
I'm sure he'll wank off
the whole night.
Come, let's go.
What are you doing?
I don't know. She snored.
Hey.
The workers are off today
because our
conductor complained.
Really?
Ana-Maria, please help me
with something.
Come, quickly.
I have to hang the curtains,
so the workers can't see inside.
Hold this.
And you, hold the ladder.
- Be careful, sister.
- I'm used to it.
It's always me doing
such things.
Is it because
you don't have a man?
What?
We're used to doing everything.
Sister Patricia
drives the tractor.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
We're completely independent.
We're used to doing everything.
Sometimes a bulb needs changing
or a shelf has to be put up.
Is it hard to be celibate?
Well...
In celibacy,
you have to redirect
your energy into work
and creativity.
It's marriage with God.
You gift your body to Christ
and God's word fills you.
And then it isn't hard
to remain faithful
to your vows.
- Can I ask you one more thing?
- Go ahead.
Don't you miss
someone hugging you?
Or running his hand
through your hair?
Of course.
There are such moments.
You are tempted.
But that's because humans are
instinctive by nature.
But when you decide
to devote your life
to something higher,
then God's word, God,
gives you all the satisfaction.
It's God's touch.
It's different from human touch.
Human touch is transient.
Someone comes,
touches you and leaves.
God's touch lasts.
God's touch touches your heart
and spills over your body.
- Do you two go to church?
- Yeah.
Take care of your body.
A woman's body is sacred.
Did you hear that, Lucia?
God's touch
spills over the body.
I can't imagine what it's like
when that woman gets horny.
Holding it in for so long
must drive you crazy.
I don't know...
But what if energy really can
be transformed like that?
I don't believe it.
We're animals, it's our drive.
Sex is healthy.
It's been proven.
She said it was a drive.
- Yeah, but...
- You can't say
that God's touch
is the same as human touch.
God's touch. Come on.
I just know
that kissing is healthy.
When you kiss,
happy hormones are released
and you feel better.
Pure chemistry,
the body doesn't lie.
Remember?
Will you call it a sin again?
If you want to suffer, go ahead,
but don't expect it from us.
Can you listen to me?
Stop acting like
Virgin Mary. It's boring.
Hey.
You play beautifully.
You can't sleep either?
Me neither.
It's too humid. Come here.
Sit down.
It's Bach.
But I'm playing it wrong.
I should play more dryly.
Sostenuto.
But I like using the pedal.
It makes the harmonies softer.
Really beautiful.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you okay?
You can confide in me.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Just tell me.
What is it?
I think that Ana-Maria
is in love with me.
Why?
- I don't know.
- Did something happen? - No.
I've known Ana-Maria
a long time.
She's not like that.
We're here to work.
The focus is
on the choir and singing.
Let's stick to that.
Okay.
- I'll go change.
- Yeah.
Don't drag it. Follow me.
"Heart". I have to hear that.
And now the canon.
Float, open up.
Listen to each other.
That's it,
I want to hear you. Open.
Come on.
Where are the phrases,
the emphases?
Your heart hurts?
I have to hear it.
Altos, it's your turn.
Altos, come on.
More. Mind the dynamics.
Mind the expression. Emphases.
Crescendo.
Mind the dynamics!
"It weighs..."
Lean on it!
That's it.
Attention, girls. No, stop!
I said dynamics. Don't scream.
You squeeze your neck and peep.
We said
that dynamics isn't screaming.
Let's go back. 16, canon.
"What's wrong?"
Just the middle.
No, just you, Maruša.
And...
Make it a bit fuller,
otherwise it's fine.
Lucia. The same.
And...
Lucia, please,
I gave you the intonation.
Stop daydreaming.
And...
Why are you so timid?
Make it fuller.
Don't be so scared.
I can't hear you over here.
And...
More dynamics, Lucia.
Where are the emphases?
Can you remember?
Continue.
Wake up, Lucia.
You're sleeping.
I'm sorry, just stop.
That's rubbish.
Girls, if you're going
to sing like that,
we might as well go home.
You're stiff
and that affects
the entire choir.
Please pull yourself together.
Hey, where were you?
Look at this.
OMG. He's completely naked.
Where did you get it?
Lucia sent it to me.
What?
I just wanted to
return his T-shirt.
My God, Lucia, way to go.
- You're so naughty.
- Isn't she?
He's hot.
Can we send it to others too?
- Please don't.
- The conductor, for example.
Klara, no!
We won't, relax.
Are you okay, Lucia?
You're totally red.
Yeah.
I just feel a bit sick.
I think we have to go.
Louder.
Mind the phrase. And...
Lucia, where are you?
Don't drag it.
Girls, you know this.
And open.
Lucia, I can see you.
By drops.
Open!
Stop! Lucia,
what's going on with you?
Where are you?
Who am I conducting for?
Again, just you.
And...
Well?
Again.
And...
Go on, sing.
Rubbish, Lucia.
Come on, sing!
Go on, sing.
Oh, come on, Lucia.
What are you doing?
Who am I counting for?
Again. And...
Come on!
I told you to sing!
Come on, let's do it.
Come on.
Where are you?
Let's do it. Sing.
And...
Parlando then, fine.
Come on.
And...
That! That! And...
Lift your chin.
Keep singing. And...
That's not how we sing.
Lift your chin. Keep singing.
And...
What's with your posture?
Stand upright.
Like this. Steadily.
Come on.
I'll help you.
Shoulders back.
Come on!
That's it!
Keep singing.
We haven't finished yet. And...
Sing, I can't hear you.
You aren't using
your diaphragm. And...
I told you to sing, Lucia.
Sing!
And...
One, two, three and...
I can't hear you. At all.
That's rubbish.
I didn't tell you to scream.
Let's go.
One, two, three and...
Go on.
And...
That's unacceptable!
That's unacceptable.
This won't get you anywhere.
It's disrespectful
to me and my work.
It's rubbish.
I'm wasting my time here.
Why did we even come here?
From the top.
Get ready.
One, two, three and...
Sing!
Open.
More.
That's it.
Continue.
And...
Lucia, get out.
I told you to get out.
Continue singing!
Thanks. That was enough.
Lucia!