232 BCE.
Ashoka, the great emperor,
slaughtered thousands
to conquer Kalinga,
yet one thought conquered him.
And that is his repentance!
He couldn't tell whether what he had
achieved was a victory or a defeat.
He reached a conclusion
after dwelling on that thought.
He realised
the hidden divine power he held
within was extremely dangerous,
so he dispersed it into
the nine scriptures.
He decided to give those
scriptures to nine worthy warriors.
He gave the eight scriptures
with the eight siddhis
to capable warriors,
and the ninth scripture, with
the elixir of immortality,
to the great sages who possess
the ability to see the future.
He ordered them to use it covertly
to protect humankind.
For eons, those nine warriors
have bestowed this duty
to the next in line.
The scriptures grant
immortality and world domination.
from the Greek and Portuguese,
Mongolian, Mughals and Hitler,
many influential leaders sought
after these scriptures.
However, none could succeed
in this quest.
But in this age,
a desire arose to wield
those divine scriptures
and plunge the world into darkness.
Acharya
Ambica's been meditating
for the past 48 hours.
That indicates she's sensing danger.
Banshi, we must convene
a conference with the nine warriors.
This is a secret invitation
to the warriors' conference.
(in unison) honouring
the emperor's ambition.
An unimaginable danger
is looming over us
and we can't prevent it.
It will commence
at your Thanthravanam,
and spread to every place
that houses the sacred scriptures.
Rather than staying cautious,
it'd be smarter to strike first.
If there were a way to prevent it,
I wouldn't be here
sharing my prophecy with you.
This is in no way a warning to you.
It's a glimpse of the future.
The ancient scripture under my wing
is not guarded by strategy alone.
I've raised an army for it.
We concur
with the first warrior's statement.
(in Chinese) We also have
our own army.
(in Gujarati) We also have
(in Russian) We have
our own army as well.
(in African) We also have
our own army.
Among us all, only your Amaragrandha
stands without army protection.
It was my duty
to share this prophecy.
How you choose
to perceive it is your own.
Swasthi!
-(in unison) Swasthi!
-Swasthi!
Ambica, they're leaving.
Should I talk to them again?
When ego takes over,
not just the mind
but even the ears refuse to listen.
So, what do we do now?
There's only one way.
I must go to Mount Kailash.
You want to trek Mount Kailash
whilst bearing a child?
How do you plan to go?
And for whom?
Sage Agastya.
The immortal
who lived through four ages.
The omniscient sage
who guided Lord Rama himself.
♪ The embodiment of surrender ♪
♪ pure and filled with compassion
Bringing delight ♪
The danger is inevitable.
No power born in Kaliyuga
can stand against this.
Only by delving into our history,
can we unearth the solution.
It is…
a weapon forged in Tretayuga,
during Lord Rama's time
It is Mirai.
I shall bring it.
Kindly guide the way, Mahayogi.
-You're not destined to reach it.
-Then who is?
The solution demands
a great sacrifice.
I'm ready for any
and every sacrifice, Mahayogi.
What if the sacrifice I demand
is your newborn
would you give it up?
Because the child must be shaped
by circumstances, not by his mother.
Nature will challenge
him at every step
on his journey
to acquire the weapon.
It'll punish and teach him.
He must stay strong
through every trial
life hurls at him.
Those trials
will turn him into a sage
and a battle-ready warrior.
Why him?
You took on a journey
no human could ever,
facing the torments of hell.
Only a warrior's child like yours,
with steadfast determination,
can defeat this danger.
Fate blesses only someone like him.
Are these
tears of pain
or acceptance?
Acceptance.
Aadi Yogi!
This is your command and mercy.
Jaithreya!
♪ A bloodstained shade
From lives before ♪
♪ Is this illusion, nothing more? ♪
♪ The tale of ages, rewritten anew ♪
♪ Will one great war
The feud renew? ♪
Acharya
Ambica, our community leader,
has been away
from the ashram for 24 years.
Everything she had predicted
has started coming true.
An evil force has already
gained control
of six ancient scriptures.
We must put an end to it
before it reaches
the ninth scripture.
Who is that evil force, Acharya?
He's a demonic power
no human can confront.
Mahabir Lama!
With six scriptures
under his possession,
his ultimate goal now
is to possess the ninth scripture,
the one we guard.
To activate the power of immortality
from the ninth scripture,
all scriptures must come together.
He must not reach it
under any circumstance.
If he does,
it will transform him into a god!
How can we stop this kind of
a powerful force, Acharya?
We're not the ones meant to stop it.
Ambica found the solution
for this 24 years ago.
Bring my son back after 24 years.
Does that mean you won't come back?
His arrival is as good as mine.
He's the guardian
of Ashoka's scriptures
and fated to unite with Mirai.
Only three weeks remain
for both Ambica's warning
and his solution.
Here's the list
of orphans in Varanasi.
Can you see
if the name Vedha is in there?
He's in the list.
But to find out, it will cost you.
Vedha, Harishchandra Ghat.
You need not read my mind.
I brought him up.
His thoughts and actions are pure.
He has a unique perspective.
Baba, I think the stars
are calling me to the east.
From Kashi
to Kolkata.
Sir, sir!
I know where he is.
Brother, when I inquired
about Vedha from Kashi,
-I was told only you know him.
-Varanasi Vedha?
In our early days in Kolkata,
we used to sell coal together.
He was always happy,
even with empty pockets.
Then, around 10 years ago
Dude, selling coal
is ruining my complexion.
We can't change
the color of coal, dude.
So let's change the place.
Place? Where will you go?
The stars seem to be
guiding me towards the south.
Now that Dasu Daddy's here,
Scrap Vedha will be finished.
Inky pinky, Sunnam is a donkey!
These are better than the original.
The word on the streets is the same.
It's not that easy
to impress Dasu Daddy.
Gucci, Fendi,
Louis Vuitton, Balmain,
local, foreign, premium… my gosh!
Liquor, clothes, bags, phones,
watches, and laptops.
What else is left?
They're all fake!
-They named it a remake.
-Yes!
All of this is okay,
but what's with remaking my weed
and selling it back to me, man?
Where's my original product?
-Sorry, Daddy. It slipped.
-Coriander leaves?!
He used it
to replicate your stuff, Daddy.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Where's my weed?
You! What's with this screen?
Are we getting married, or what?
Remove it!
How dare you come into my area
and have the audacity
to steal my weed?
(in Hindi) Tell me
where my original weed is
Otherwise, this scrapyard
will turn into a graveyard!
DJ Tillus! Start the music.
(in Hindi) What, dude?
This scrap guy put on the music.
Yes dude! It's a banger.
♪ Krishna! What is all this ♪
♪ Oh, kids these days are
Just like that, brother! ♪
♪ Listen, Daddy! ♪
♪ Wherever a tree grows
That is its territory ♪
♪ The entire country
is my territory ♪
♪ Once Vedha lays
his eyes on the goods ♪
♪ There's no chance
of getting them back ♪
♪ If your number is one
My number is 420 ♪
♪ Business means there's a
Little giving and a little taking ♪
♪ Not a stingy profession of
Collecting spare change ♪
♪ If you still
Don't understand, Daddy? ♪
♪ He'll put you to sleep in
The Gandhi Hospital ♪
Hey, Nallamandhu!
Oh my Tiger Shroff!
Damn them! Jacks!
♪ Okay, nice! Proceed ♪
♪ If everyone wears the same thing
The expense will be high ♪
♪ How can we do our business
If you alone dominate it, brother? ♪
♪ Doesn't he know who we are? ♪
♪ He'll thrash
the hell out of you, boss ♪
Oh no!
♪ It will be extraordinary! ♪
Why attack one by one, you idiots?
-Go as a gang!
-Let's go, guys!
♪ You're so elegant
You're just looking wow! ♪
(in Hindi)
This DJ is messing with my head.
-Cut those wires!
-Yes, Daddy!
-Hey, shorty!
-Brother?
Are you saying we're the original
and you're the knockoff?
-Yes, bro!
-Have my blessings!
Brother!
♪ How can we do our business ♪
Here, catch!
Oh no, terrible fielding.
That's Dasu Daddy's product.
No matter
where you hide it in Hyderabad,
it is bound to reach me.
Nothing here belongs to you, Daddy.
All is but borrowed.
Yours today,
another's tomorrow. Get it?
I didn't hide it somewhere else.
It's right here.
Hey!
Hey, man!
-Sunnam, kill the fire!
-Water… Oh, I found it.
Hey, man!
It's a first copy of Whisky!
It'll blast!
No!
(singing)
It's over!
Bye-bye, tata.
This is my prayer to all of you.
My life's going well
with a few petty cases.
Please don't give me
murder investigations
-and don't let me lose my job, God.
-Sir!
Why are you so scared, sir?
We need fear
to live and grow, Sebastian.
Okay. We've come this far,
let's go in.
Go in?
Is this Subbaiah Hotel or what?
You're asking a family man
to walk into fire, you idiot!
They'll come out. Let's wait.
Hey, sister. Where are you going?
To meet Vedha, Vedha Prajapathi.
He stirred up some trouble.
The police
are arresting them as we speak.
Hey, ease up, man.
Leave the shirt.
-Greetings, CI sir.
-Greetings.
Where do you want the AC?
Behind your seat or in front?
It's for the people
in the cell, not us.
It's so the prisoners
can stay cool in summer. Take it in.
Why give them these facilities, sir?
What philosophy is this?
If they're treated well inside,
they won't seek
revenge after they're out.
It's called strategy!
Between the AC and biryani,
this place is more Green Bawarchi
than a police station.
Yes, ma'am?
I'm here to get them released.
Released?
Who? This weed gang?
You don't look like a lawyer
or a human rights activist.
So, who are you?
My name is Vibha.
I come from the Himalayas.
-Himalayas?
-Must be the Himalaya bookstore.
-Could she be our lawyer?
-Is she our lawyer?
We've had the same drawer
for three years.
Can we really hire a lawyer?
Since they unknowingly
inhaled the weed smoke,
they're victims, not culprits.
The weed stash
was completely burned.
That means…
you have no evidence
that they sold it.
According to NCB clause 21,
you can't arrest them
without supporting evidence.
Release them immediately
or you'll be the one inside.
What do we do, sir?
How long are we going to do
this small-time stuff, man?
Let's pick a bank
-and hit it. That's art!
-Nope. That's a crime.
First copy art is all about…
revising and creating
something new, man.
-Got it?
-Wow!
She was only a girl till now.
Now she's an angel!
Why did she show up
just as I said, "angel"?
Did you come here because
we didn't thank you
for bailing us out?
Hello?
Hello! Girl! What's with the stare?
Something's off about your look.
You're dressed like a sadhu.
You're not from that crew
that switches disguises
for their trade, are you?
That's Yesu Daddy's style, not mine.
I only deal with first copies.
Let me know if you want those.
Varanasi ghats, Bengal coal mines,
Howrah Beeda market,
and 16 police stations…
These are the places that shaped you
and the markers
that brought me here.
I don't have any loans,
so why did you come looking for me?
You're not a loan-taker…
but a trouble-stopper!
You are the only saviour
to the ninth book, Amaragrandha.
You must reach Mirai to protect it.
A warrior from the Shatadru dynasty,
one who can kill a hundred men…
She's calling you
Kaalabhairava, dude!
That girl is crazy, man. Crazy!
Crazy folks hate being called crazy.
Just look at her face!
Hey!
How do you know this art?
I can read a person's forgotten
memories in their face.
But I can't read your mind.
You are a warrior!
One who doesn't even know who he is.
You try to kill me
and then tell Hollywood stories?
You can read people's minds, huh?
Then read his mind.
He's been cursing you
since last night…
regarding Vantalakka.
There's no way he'd curse me--
Cursing me?
-Hey, man, are you cursing me?
-Wouldn't I?
Why did you give
your number for my girl?
How would I know
you would hit on Vantalakka?
I'll hit on whoever I want,
whether she makes punugulu or vada!
To each his own, man.
The point isn't about the snacks.
-Why did you give her your number?
-Because she promised home delivery.
-I don't want her number--
-Then, why did you smile?
Hey, I have a smiley face, man.
A girl came looking for me,
and you badmouth me to her?
I'll kick you
if you mention the lodge!
Why is that girl leaving, sir?
I have an idea.
Let's plant audio bugs.
So, should I place 50
all over the scrapyard?
One bug in her place
is all it takes, Sebastian.
Acharya! We have found the warrior.
There is light on one side…
and darkness on the other!
Master Yakuza!
I am a history professor.
I have come
as a representative of a new force.
I mean, the new master
of Ashoka's scriptures, Black Sword.
You are protecting
the seventh book, Kalagrandham.
Please give it to us.
You and your force will never
get your hands on that book.
Then, it's time for you
to face Black Sword.
(in Japanese) All alert!
Tear that guy to pieces!
When a shining star dies,
it becomes a black hole
that swallows everything.
No matter how powerful it may be,
it'll absorb it.
In the past, I was that star.
My present
is beyond your imagination.
To be executed
by the hands of Mahabir Lama…
is a great honour!
Powerful books in the wrong places!
Kalagrandham!
It's taken me
24 years to get my hands
on these seven books, Professor.
Now I only have two weeks left
to achieve my goal.
The one thing I don't have is…
time, Professor.
Here, older man.
I said I'd give you
your share, and I did.
You turned trash
into gold and sold it.
Why are you giving me the profit?
You're the one
who gave me the scrap.
So what?
This is your rightful share.
Keep it.
-Take care.
-Okay.
Oh goddess, Maisamma!
My heart skipped a beat!
-Why are you bothering me?
-I don't have a choice.
If you perform a mudra I suggest
and revisit your memories-- oh!
-Vedha!
-Dasu Daddy is waiting for you!
Finish them off!
(in Hindi) Kill them! Kill them!
I may not be able to read your face,
but I can very well read
your feelings.
Don't let your thoughts
go any further than that!
Hey, what happened?
You're bleeding.
-Wait, let's bandage it.
-I'll manage.
-Hey!
-Hmm?
The first time I saw Vibha
at the police station,
I felt a connection of ome sort.
I missed the signals back then,
but today… damn!
It was straight out of a movie!
The wind is blowing,
the lights flickering, …
her hair flying!
Touch the feel,
feel the breath,
smell the hair!
Feels like my heart
has a fever, man.
-Will you visit the lodge?
-You idiot!
But why would that girl
come in search of me?
Why would she shed her blood for me?
This is definitely love.
One shouldn't let go of
a girl like her, man.
If you don't want to lose her,
then hold her close! I mean propose.
This is the location Mapu sent.
-How is it?
-If you put yours on,
I'll take mine off!
-I'll take it off myself. Jealous!
-Let's go.
(in Hindi) Watch where you're going!
Why are we at the lodge, man?
What is this?
Why is it all so strange here?
Shit! Shit! Shit!
You said she was in your heart.
What's she doing here, man?
Welcome, boys!
It's your first time
at our lodge, right?
Do you want just a room,
or something extra?
Hey! Cotton candy!
Where's my sadhu girl?
-She came a week ago.
-That's the girl roaming around
wearing those huckaback clothes!
That sadhu-looking girl?
First floor, 105.
Dear, please put on your shawl.
He's not that type.
It's already open.
It's already open?
Is she into witchcraft?
-What is this, man? Shut up!
-Black magic.
Look at you meditating here
while those women
are flirting outside!
There's no connection
between you
and what's happening here.
We've lost the seventh scripture.
We don't have time.
Our yodha must get ready.
Vedha, listen to me carefully.
There are nine scriptures
that can turn a human into a god.
Emperor Ashoka hid them
in different places.
Someone has already acquired
seven of those nine.
He's about to reach the eighth one.
You must stop him
before he reaches the ninth one.
(gibberish)
-Her chip is busted.
-Hey! Stop it!
What's with this place?
Come on, let's get out of here.
(gibberish)
You're a coward.
Is this an undercover operation
needed, sir?
Somehow, we closed the case.
Why take the risk, sir?
National Task Force pressure
is high on me, Sebastian.
They are asking me that
"How can you let go
of thirty men at once--
"Be answerable for that
"or give an explanation
for the ganja that got fired off. "
These two tasks
can't be carried out by us.
We must obtain the evidence.
-Vedha!
-Vibha!
I came here
to tell you something serious.
Your story and that pigeon
completely jacked up my mind.
The thing is, I love you.
I am ready to deal with your madness
and actually help treat it.
You and I… we'll marry.
This isn't the mission I came for,
nor the one you're meant to fulfil.
I am neither the one you seek,
nor the place you're destined for.
You are the address fate has chosen
as the solution to this problem.
Hello! He has a complete
understanding of himself.
Don't confuse him.
Who gave you the name Vedha?
You know only the Kashi Aghora
who raised you,
not the mother
who handed you to him.
Your mother's name is Ambica!
She is a holy tribe's leader
worshipped by thousands.
She possesses
the ability to see the future.
His mother?
I don't know
anything about a "mother. "
I'm just like him.
I roamed around the ghats,
and I grew up among corpses.
I ate whatever I found,
and I went wherever I liked.
No mother came looking for me.
Come with me
if you understand my situation.
Otherwise, don't.
In this journey to acquire
all nine ancient books of Ashoka
why didn't you
ever mention the last book?
You can gain possession
of the eight books,
but you'll never be able
to touch the ninth one.
The ninth book
is a big puzzle, Professor.
To reach the ninth book,
we must overcome Ambica's schemes.
Which means we must think like her.
For ten years, my shadow
has toiled in the darkness.
Yuka!
Yuka, after ten years
of rigorous training
in this monastery,
you are now worthy
of a higher stage of training.
For that, you must go
to Ambica's ashram.
With all your blessings,
I aim to meet Ambica.
Her whereabouts are kept hidden.
You deserve to suffer
for the ten-year delay.
This is my guru dakshina!
I needlessly overreacted.
Hey, did I say too much?
Will Vibha ever come here again?
Don't worry, dude. If not Vibha,
I'll hook you up with Nagole Nabha.
The fever in your heart
will soon fade.
First, fix those flickering lights!
When did we buy
those sturlite lights?!
Hey, Map! He's talking to you.
Sadhu girl!
Hey!
The light is back
and so is your lighthouse.
Why has he turned into a sticker?
Hey, eyes are giving away
your feelings.
Bring out your attitude!
Will you come out for a second?
Do you remember
how did this car get here?
It's from Chor Bazaar. Why?
Had you not brought this car
here to make a first copy,
it's failed brakes
would have taken four lives.
You're aware
of this bus's story, right?
This bus is unfit to drive.
If you hadn't brought this,
it would have been
used as a school bus.
I don't have to spell out
what would you've
followed after that.
Who taught you to mix
coriander leaves into weed?
Who will teach me?
It was my own idea.
That's what I'm telling you!
Your thoughts hold good intentions.
That's the reason
why did it never get delivered
to the college.
In the same way,
there's a good intention
hidden behind
every single item here.
Whether you agree or not,
you are special!
By practicing this Matrika mudra,
you'll recall your mother's guidance.
Come, I'll show you who I really am!
What are we going to do now?
We're going to demonstrate
a sample of what we really do.
Pick your choice of car, boss.
Shiny black.
Thaviz Mahima.
(humming in native language)
-Oh no! Sir…
-Let's exchange!
Complimentary milkshake
from our drive-in. Thank you, sir.
I'm so sorry, common rich people's
problems, you know? It's okay.
See? His loss is our gain.
-See, what's special about it?
-Yeah!
I'm ordinary, not as special
as you describe me to be.
Hey, what's that sound?
Nothing can hurt you.
Don't be afraid.
Where do you live, little ones?
I've had many shocks in life,
but this one's high voltage!
Have I truly been doing
all these good deeds?
The stars
are here at the right time.
There he goes again.
I see a man holding
an arrow right now.
If what was unseen is now visible,
the time has come for you
to act upon it.
What do I do? Where do I go?
Hey, Map, how do I get
from Purana Pul to Ramnagar?
There are two routes, dude.
One via Afzalgunj
and the other via Nampally.
See the clarity?
Explain it as clearly as he did.
The one who considers himself God,
is about to kill masses of people.
To prevent this,
you must reach Mirai.
Let's say Mirai's in Ramnagar
and I'm in Purana Pul.
How do I get
to Ramnagar from Purana Pul?
The patch is etched
within your memories.
The only way to recall them
is through a mudra.
You're saying I can see it
if I use that mudra?
-Which mudra is it?
-Matrika mudra.
Follow my lead.
Try to recall your mother's words.
How can I remember words
spoken to me in the womb?
You are Ambica's son!
You possess the power
to recollect the past.
This mudra is meant for that.
I know you can hear me.
Your first goal is to reach Mirai.
Every word you hear
will bring you closer to Mirai.
We're not parting ways.
We shall be reunited at a place
called Thanthravanam.
What happened, dude?
It's like I'm listening
to Mom's voice playing on a stereo.
This is a Moroccan flute.
It has a very unique sound.
Mashallah!
Overnight, a mountain
between two villages
in Morocco,
it magically disappeared.
It wasn't caused
by a man or a machine.
I'm sure there
are sound weapons there.
Which means the eighth book,
Shabdagrandha, has to be there.
I can offer it to you
for a good price. Okay?
What instrument or…
I seek the scripture that withholds
the knowledge
to make weapons of sound
that can erase mountains and people.
That's the eighth scripture!
You have no idea
what you're about to face now.
Almuka Thilin! Yatha Jamian!
Professor!
If the weapons
alone are this fascinating,
imagine how tremendous
their damage would be!
You haven't just come close
to our scripture,
you have come close to your end!
(in Arabic) Confront your death.
Kala!
I invoke the darkness!
A ruler plus a commander
is equal to… God!
That's me.
(in Arabic) Bow down to
the greatest power.
Kneel before this unbeatable force!
Unexpected visitor, aren't I?
The only unexpected visitor
is death.
I know mine has arrived.
Well said.
I know the goal you have in mind.
You won't just stop at my death,
you'll burn this ashram
down to its ashes.
Let's keep it simple.
Where is the ninth book?
From what I know of the future,
you will not be able to reach it.
"We're close to the goal. "
Clearly, the destiny
is not with you.
My job here is done.
Now it makes no difference
whether I exist or not.
Get ready for the war!
As you wish! Burn it!
Track it.
Hey, Zareena sister,
what brings you here at this hour?
You said you'd give my son
a gaming computer copy.
I brought money for that.
So, you'll come out
in this condition?
Stay home until your delivery.
Go home. I'll drop it off.
Since you're pregnant,
you don't have to pay.
Your mother gave birth
to a noble soul.
-Let's go!
-Hey!
You're messing up every deal
with your "Mummy Returns" nonsense.
Hey, it's my Mom. Don't you dare
utter a word about her.
-That's not it, dude--
-Move!
This guy!
Hey, Map! Come here.
He's not understanding
that it's all
emotional manipulation, dude.
Hey, idiot!
Why aren't you saying anything?
-It must be true if he said so.
-Truth? My foot!
If he becomes a saint like her,
we'll be selling blankets
on the road.
This is hypnotism!
What we do comes back to us.
-Then what about the car?
-It was a fluke, man.
Hey, let's conspire
to send her away.
Vibha.
I'm here to tell you something.
You need to leave immediately.
I'm saying this gently
because you're a lady.
Why is the pigeon bleeding?
Why is there a tracker on it?
If they're talking about trackers,
they must be planning something big.
Now's the right time
to gather all the evidence.
-Alert the entire team.
-Yes, sir.
-Go through the entire CCTV footage.
-Okay, sir.
We need to get there
before they leave the lodge.
-Start immediately.
-Yes, sir.
Why are you crying? Is anybody hurt?
Many people have lost their lives.
And now they're coming for us.
Sebastian, is everyone in position?
Yes, sir. We're in position.
What's your status?
I'm right behind you in the van.
Wait for my command.
I'm watching everything
on the CCTV. Ok?
Okay, sir.
You wait here.
Sir, did you notice that?
Who is this face
that doesn't match with Chaderghat?
Shall I arrest her, sir?
We can't arrest her
without proof, Sebastian.
Wait.
Here, have some dates.
I got them imported
from Dubai for you.
Girl. From the Himalayas?
(indicates) Girl. From Ameerpet.
Room 105, first floor. Third right!
They have arrived.
We must find Vedha!
Vibha!
Hey, Vibha! Vibha!
The sadhu girl and her friend
are getting away, sir.
They're not our priority right now.
Focus on that lady villain.
Arrest her once she comes out,
and take her
straight to the police station.
-I'll meet you in court.
-Take your positions.
Sir…
My… sir…
is in… the van.
She is…
with Scrap Vedha.
I'll take you.
Dude!
Something's about to happen.
Someone's after Vibha.
Vibha, what happened?
The one who raised me,
the one who told me
to bring you to him,
is no longer alive.
Now all I have left is you.
I lay my faith in you
just the way your mom did.
You have risen for many,
without even knowing it.
Now rise once more,
for those who lay
their faith in you.
-What exactly happened?
-I have to leave.
Take care.
What happened--
You're the only one alive.
Don't make me burn this place down!
It's a business holiday today.
Nothing goes out of the store.
You may leave.
Damn them! Jacks!
This looks like a pan-world
setup to me.
Come on, let's fight!
Hey, Vedha!
Leave him…
or I'll kill myself!
I'm the only one who can lead you
to the ninth book.
Leave him!
Vedha, in order to fulfill
this noble mission,
you will need
more than mere strength,
you will need allies.
You came into this world
with the path
already etched within you.
With the five elements,
and the stars as our witnesses…
May Ambica's sacrifice
and Agasthya's resolve stands firm.
This child is the eternal beacon
of the future.
This is the blessing bestowed
by the tilakam of the Ikshvaku line.
Jaitreya!
When the time is right,
Only when droplets of rain
merge with his blood
will the holy path
unveil itself to him.
The time has come, Vedha.
Vedha!
Hey, Mapu!
Dude, like you said,
it's not a tattoo.
It's actually a map.
The destination points to somewhere
outside the Northern Himalayas.
Here, take a look.
This map leads not to the Himalayas,
but straight to his grave.
He's already lost his mind,
and you're encouraging him further?
Was getting stabbed
not enough for you?
Shut up, man!
Listen to me,
and stop pursuing this.
What Mom preached, Vibha repeated.
Mirai.
To meet them,
I must reach Mirai.
Dude, what are you doing? Vedha!
It's not as simple as traveling
from Kolkata to Hyderabad.
Where will you go
without any direction?
The path will pave itself
once I take the first step.
Another 600 meters to go, dude.
Careful.
-Oh God!
-Watch your step.
-Hey…
-I can't.
(in Hindi) Is there a village
nearby?
This is the last village.
You stay here.
I'll come with you.
(chanting mantra)
Sir, please stop.
For the past 300 years,
no one who walked that path
has come back alive.
This is Lord Garuda's domain.
Those who step foot on it
without his permission
never return alive.
In Lord Rama's time
lived two eagles,
Sampati and Jatayu.
Jatayu sacrificed his life
in the aid of Lord Rama.
Sampati helped Lord Rama
and regained his lost wings.
Sampati's lineage now guards Mirai.
Mere strength is powerless
against a divine being like Sampati.
If you want their help,
you'll have to find a way yourself.
If they think
your intentions are pure,
they'll be willing to help you.
That will only be possible once you
connect to Sampati's mind.
Sir, this is the most ruthless
and a barbarous gang I've ever seen
in my service.
She slaughtered 20 police officers
without a shred of humanity.
They've got a helicopter
and martial arts.
Sir, their setup is remarkable!
Don't spare them,
no matter what, sir.
Please arrest them all.
Goodbye and all the best, sir.
Twenty policemen are dead,
don't you understand
the gravity of the situation, Ashok?
We need to close this case
before the media finds out.
I'm relieving you
of your duties as CI.
-Sir? Are you firing me?
-Ashok…
That's exactly what will happen
if we don't catch them.
You've been assigned
to a new task force
to solve this case.
He is Mr Sridhar,
and she is Ms Zoya Ben.
-Soya Bean?
-Zoya Ben!
Sir, Emperor Ashoka, the Himalayas,
and scriptures…
it all seems very risky.
What can I do there?
No matter who they are,
we must catch them
to honour our fallen officers.
In order to save that guy,
you deceived me into believing
you knew the way to the ninth book.
No matter where he is hiding,
I'll find that scrap guy
and I'll kill him for sure.
Does this stick truly hold
superpowers, dude?
No doubt about it, man.
Once I learn what it is
and how to wield it,
I'll conquer all and everything!
Hey!
How did you manage
to stop it, noble sir?
It's spiritual physics.
What you fail to grasp,
your mother surely would have.
-Do you know my mom?
-Yes.
-What's your name?
-They call me Agastya.
-Ag…
-It's okay.
Just call me AG.
AG… AG!
Where did my mom go?
Where is she now?
Each time I attempt the mudra,
all I remember is Thanthravanam.
How do you even know my mother?
How could I not know her?
I was the reason she sacrificed you.
Why did you stop talking?
I only stopped
myself from cursing you.
-Are you even a human?
-Your so-called 'solution' led
-my life into shambles!
-Hey! Hey! Sit down. Sit down.
I had no other choice.
That solution…
helped you defy Sampati
and led you to Mirai.
What is this Mirai, you ask?
This is the answer
to all your questions.
Tell me about its powers.
Let's put it to use.
Damn it! Jacks!
I knew this was something special.
I have total clarity now.
I'll press this,
get to Thanthravanam,
meet my mother and finish him off!
Okay, ta-ta, see you, bye-bye, AG!
Go to the ninth book!
Go to Thanthravanam!
Has no one told you that you haven't
outgrown your childishness yet?
These places are all in my mind.
This weapon won't work for you
the way it works for me.
It leads you
based solely on your intention.
Since my mind is spiritual,
it brought me
to this boundless land.
Your path will only reveal itself
when your intention aligns with it.
You must become one with Mirai
for that to happen.
But I'm already holding it.
Just holding it
won't make you one with it.
Soil is God,
and the seed is life.
And from their bond grows the tree.
You are the life,
and what you're holding is God.
Once they both combine…
the war commences.
For that, your next destination
would be…
Siddhakshetram.
Dude, did you see that?
What am I supposed to see?
While you two sat there
frozen like statues,
I finished the noodles
so they don't go to waste.
AG, you mentioned a holy place.
Tell me where it is,
and I'll head there.
That is Siddhakshetram,
the place where Lord Rama
first held his weapon.
Can't you take me there
through the power of Mirai?
If I eat your noodles,
does it make your stomach full?
Understood.
I have to do it myself.
-AG…
-Yes?
I've carried an unknown ache
within me since childhood,
and I've just realised it was
due to my mom's absence.
Looking back, made me realise that
my mother never really left me.
She's always been with me,
in my thoughts and in nature
around me.
AG, we'll meet her
in Thanthravanam for sure, right?
Knowing the future changes it.
What must be, will not be.
Well then, is the ninth book
hidden there at least?
That's for you to figure out,
isn't it, brother?
So, what's in that ninth book?
What the virtuous avoid,
and the evil pursue…
Immortality.
Especially if it falls
into his hands,
your people are as good as dead!
I am beyond your level
of reading or understanding.
By hiding the ninth book,
what do you hope to achieve?
You people have had the nine books
for seventy generations,
what has changed in the world?
You call this change?
Stealing holy scriptures
and posing as God?
God is the one who mercies
and treats everyone equally.
Lacking those virtues,
you have no right
to lay hands on the scriptures.
God?
Mercy?
My life began in the light
of the very God you speak of.
And that same God
became the reason for my darkness.
I questioned
why I was given a new mother
while mine was still thriving.
They called it destiny.
They claimed she was possessed
and killed her
in the name of a ritual.
The entire village
labeled me a bad omen.
-Who can answer this?
-I will.
Hey, what are you doing here?
You're born of a demon.
How dare you set foot in here?
-Please listen to me, sir.
-Unworthy rascal!
Worthiness?!
God creates everyone,
but chooses only a few.
That's worthiness.
He did not choose you
in this life. Get lost!
When a strong man rises,
those who fear him
call him unworthy.
They talk
about his caste and religion.
If someone does manage to succeed,
they question his caste.
Despite their harsh behavior
I solved their water crisis
by redirecting water from
the mountain to our village.
It's me, Swami.
I brought the water myself.
What do you mean you
brought water, damn it?!
God blessed us with this water.
Go, stay away.
That was the day
I finally understood.
My hurdles were
worthiness, status, ritual,
and even being labeled a bad omen…
All of them were given to me
by the Lord himself.
You don't exist!
That's blasphemy!
-How dare you mess with God?
-Hey!
I became hungry for revenge.
I killed the teacher
who called me unworthy.
-It's a sin.
-I killed the priest
-who talked about ritual.
-It's a sin to kill a priest.
So, I killed my family
who labeled me a bad omen.
Even that didn't put an end
to my hunger.
At last, I burnt the entire village
down to ashes.
That finally
put an end to my hunger.
Since then, it's been
my single-point agenda!
Power alone decides who thrives.
No questions asked!
One comes up with the idea,
another gets the award!
One drafts the plan,
another enjoys the glory!
One works hard,
the other reaps the benefits.
I'm fed up with this crap!
I'll bring about change
with the power of these nine books…
the change that you failed
to achieve
in seventy-five generations!
The only answer to all of this is…
a new force to purge
the filth and sickness!
Mahabir Lama 2.0!
The powerless may fear
as the powerful must reign.
All of this would only be possible
in a world with no God!
This is the mark
Mahabir Lama will leave on Earth!
No force can stand in my way!
What you want to create
is not a new world,
It's just a graveyard.
The day you arose as a threat,
Ambica weaved a solution.
A battle stands between you
and the ninth book.
That battle is personified
as "Ambica's son. "
A weapon I found
in the Shabdagrandham.
This is a reward for your courage.
Go, get him.
“Siddhakshetram, ” he said.
“You must become one
with the weapon, ” he said.
Why is he performing
Sandhya Vandanam here?
[chants Vedic hymns]
Hello, my dear Lord Ram.
Your getup is okay,
but shouldn't your grip match it?
In the hands of others,
it sparks war.
But in Rama's grasp,
it spreads peace.
If you want this weapon
to unite with you,
-chant "Jaithreya".
-Jaithreya!
It has a powerful vibe!
Jai Shree Ram!
(in Hindi) You'll have
the blessings of Ram Lala.
Priest, kindly bless our weapon
and bring it to life.
What kind of weapon is this?
We don't bless these things here.
Hey, priest! I brought this
all the way from the Himalayas.
Could you at least keep it
at the Lord's feet for a minute?
Don't bother me!
It's time
for the devotees to arrive.
-Priest, actually…
-Don't waste my time.
Get out of here. Go!
AG, he's saying
he won't perform the puja here.
I know someone
at the Peddamma temple.
Should I get it done there?
This is indeed a weapon.
There's a spot nearby
where Lord Rama
is believed to have meditated.
Place this there, and what you
wish for shall find you.
May you be victorious.
Go.
I think this is the spot, dude.
Ask him.
Hey, man.
Is this the place
where Lord Rama use to meditate?
Do you realise you're disturbing
someone who's meditating?
Dude, it's the same spot-- huh?
You escaped last time.
I won't let it happen again!
Where is the ninth book?
HEY!
Jaka!
Dear little one…
What's your name?
Ambica.
Your body
is a reflection of the universe
and this weapon
is a reflection of your body.
Once this weapon
aligns with your intentions,
it will work wonders in your favour.
I share the same intentions
as my mother, Ambica.
I am ready for war. Jaithreya!
When this weapon becomes one
with your body,
it will transform into a wonder
that can command all five elements.
It attracts fire
and fuels it with air.
The air surrounding it alone
is enough to cripple a person.
A single strike from it
brings instant death.
Till the time you understand this,
you remain Vedha.
And once you do,
you turn into a true yodha.
That's not a regular stick.
It's something else!
Vibha!
Vibha, please get up!
Can you hear me? Stay with me!
Vibha!
Vibha, stay with me.
Look at me. Can you hear me?
Look at me, Vibha!
Vibha, can you hear me?
Vibha, stay with me. Look at me!
Vibha, please look at me!
"If we embody courage
for a good cause,
"Mirai will stand with us. "
AG told me that.
Dude, I looked everywhere,
but I can't find AG.
You'll stay with us until
the task is done, right, AG?
You won't need a guru
once you understand your goal.
-AG is not coming back.
-What?
How can we do this without him?
Vedha, time's running out.
We must reach the ninth book
before they come here.
The place where we're destined
to meet again is Thanthravanam.
My mother told me we
would reunite at Thanthravanam.
You mean, the first yodha's place.
Kamakhya Island.
Every time
someone crosses the ocean,
a miracle takes place
and a new chapter begins.
As per the procedure,
we're here to catch Veda, right?
Then what are we doing
at the government airport?
If we are to achieve our goal,
we need a shortcut, not a procedure.
Who are you referring to
as a shortcut, Ashok?
Why does he look so strange?
Sir, this strange guy
is the right choice
to deal
with that kind of strangeness.
Jet lag!
Did you find out where he is?
Hey, Mapu.
You mentioned some kshetram.
Are you guys still there?
We've crossed the borders, bro,
chasing some island named Kamakhya.
Okay, I'll send you
the location. Take a look.
The location is…
in my phone.
Follow me.
Once every three generations,
the esteemed guru Angamabali appears
in the northern forest, to honour
the many tantrics' rigorous fasting.
Today is that full moon day.
It's not that easy to meet him.
If he got past Yuka
you could face 50 men,
and a hundred trained soldiers,
he must be aided by some superpower.
Maybe we should take
him more seriously, Lama.
Professor!
Do you know
that there exists a weapon
more destructive than an atom bomb?
Ego.
Even the damage
caused by an atomic bomb
originates from the ego.
So…
whom do you think
has that kind of an ego, Professor?
-Lama!
-So then…
why would I take him seriously?
The only reason
he's still breathing is
because he'll take us
to the ninth book.
His ambition is of use to us
only until we find the book.
Once our quest ends,
so will his breath.
What does this guy know anyway?
He said they went to Kamakhya.
Must be Ambica's scheme.
Angamabali.
Ashok, are you alright?
[in code language] My right side
is fine, sir.
But the left side
seems to be aching a little.
How do we find Angamabali
amidst all this crowd?
Ask that Aghora.
Aghora ji…
who amongst you is Angamabali?
I'm not an aghora,
I'm your lucky charm!
-Dude!
-You?
-Stop there! Statue!
I have come to save you. Step aside!
Hey!
Vibha Tours and Travels. Non-stop!
Man, she fooled you
by claiming to be a mind-reader.
This woman is a trouble-maker.
See? It's true!
[chanting]
He is Angamabali,
the one you're here to meet.
He is surrounded
by an army of tantrics.
Despite of being
right in front of us,
he remains beyond our reach.
Sir, look! There he is.
Jaitreya!
Hold!
Mirai!
His arrival…
is the key to Ambica's prophecy.
This is the answer
we've waited two decades for.
The grace of Mahadeva
is with us today.
The yodha has come to save us!
It's time to repay the debt
and fulfill your destiny.
What's happening, sir?
Why are all the tantrics
bowing down to him?
What is that stick and that shield?
What's with his monkey jump?
And how did he dodge my bullets?
What is this, Ashok?
Hey, what's with our guy
flying like that?
What's that stick in his hand?
What's this
Yuganikokkadu setup, man?
From Sampati to Siddhakshetram
to Thanthravanam,
it's a mind-boggling,
world's most mysterious,
globe-trotting,
-scintillating treasure hunt--
-Stop talking like a review writer!
I've brought the police with me!
Why are you talking about the police
when you have tantrics here?
Sir, is it really necessary
for us to follow them?
It is necessary for my fraternity!
-Let's follow them.
-Stop!
Ashok…
how did we end up here?
What's happening?
What was that powder?
What was in it?
Cinnamon, cloves, cardamom,
coriander and pepper!
-What are you saying, Ashok?
-How the hell would I know, sir?
Do I look like his supplier?
Or his consumer?
You're asking me everything
just because I'm here!
Did you listen to me when I tried
to stop you from going after them?
You're asking so many questions
like a journalist at a press meet!
Ashok… Ashok!
The protector of this Thanthravanam
is Bagalamukhi Matha.
If the Goddess takes human form,
She will appear as
"Ambica Prajapati. "
Our tribe's existence
is a boon from Ambica.
What exactly happened to my mother?
This story began
with me helping an orphan.
The whole village was ablaze,
and a young boy
was the lone survivor.
How did it happen, son?
I don't know!
-Where is your family?
-In the flames…
I took him home with me.
and loved him like my own son.
He would watch with interest
while I taught Tantra.
Do you want to learn too?
He grew up with my son,
learning all about the Tantric arts.
Just a minute.
I was impressed by the way
he used his Tantra.
When I saw the way
he had mastered his Tantra,
I thought of making him
the protector
of the Thanthra grandham.
One day, I announced that
I'm the protector
of the Thanthra grandham
and that I'll choose
my successor through a contest.
Aghata!
Aghata Asra!
Mahabir!
Are you aware of what you just did?
When a mantra is charged with fury,
it transforms
into a life-taking force.
Your fury could endanger lives.
During the test, I got scared
of Mahabir's fury and nature.
Keeping the future in mind,
I chose my son to be the protector.
As per the will of Bagalamukhi!
You must guard
the Tantric knowledge
with your life.
Mahabir couldn't bear the reality
where my son was chosen
over him as the protector.
Mahabir didn't utter
a single word that day.
But I never imagined he would
turn it into a quest for vengeance.
These bracelets
are made with holy intent,
for the welfare of the tribe.
Baba gave it to me.
What is that bracelet?
Mahabir gave it to us,
saying you made them.
That was my position, Baba!
Vaghata!
Subahu…
Mahabir, do you realise
what have you done?
You're the one
who needs to understand!
Aghata Vasra!
Praghata Vasra!
How did you get
hold of these powers?
No, you're not allowed
to touch that book!
Come on, guys.
Dhamani Sthanath!
Those bracelets
are a combination of my capabilities
and Tantric knowledge.
Just one page
of the book single-handedly
made the entire village
bow down to me.
Within an hour, everyone here
will turn into a statue
due to a lack
of air and water in their body.
My village is burning down
was not a mere accident, Baba.
I set it on fire myself when they
denied me the position I deserved.
Now I'll watch your village
come to its end,
just as I did mine.
Hey!
The Kaalabhooti he used
cannot be escaped
by any other way but death.
It weakens your bones,
withers your nerves,
drains your blood
and claims your life.
That is the power hidden
within the Thanthra grandham.
The whole tribe lingered
on its final breath.
Their only hope was to pray
to Bagalamukhi one last time.
As the whole tribe
was dying before my eyes,
a protector stepped in.
That was…
Ambica.
This force will be a threat
to every book.
Ambica, please leave immediately.
You must live to protect
the Amara Grandham.
Amara Grandham
must not fall into his hands.
Ambica decided to use
the only known method…
to stop the Kaalabhooti.
In order to put an end to it,
one must perform the Mahamudra
and initiate the process of reversal.
The body of anyone who attempts it
will burn like a ritual fire
due to the power of the mudra.
What do you mean?
She sacrificed herself
for the tribe's well-being.
Do you think you can stop my Tantra
with your sacrifice?
Go ahead!
Vidamba Pradura Aghata!
Skhatabha Makshadra Vidamba!
Hacchanji Oma Akshata!
Today, I gained insight
into two things.
First…
is my weakness.
You have the power to stop me.
And second…
is my future.
This Mahabir
will return after acquiring
all nine powerful scriptures!
Mahabir!
You will acquire all eight books,
but you'll never even catch
a single glimpse of the ninth book.
A battle stands between
you and the ninth one.
This is not a sacrifice
but a sign of my resolve!
(in Unison) Hail Bagalamukhi Matha!
Ever since then, Ambica has lived on
in the form of this flame.
She sacrificed her son for
the greater good.
She sacrificed herself
to protect the tribe.
This sacrifice must stand
for something crucial.
I take the oath of returning
all of the scriptures
back to their rightful protectors.
I was able to uncover
your mother's past,
but I could never find out where
she hid the Amara Grandham.
I'm sure my mother didn't send me
to Thanthravanam
solely to learn about her.
The book has to be somewhere nearby!
Never once since childhood
have the stars led me astray.
They won't now either.
Vedha!
All of you, stay put.
I must go alone.
♪ Righteousness, Jaitreya! ♪
-♪ Courage, Jaitreya! ♪
-Dada, bye. It's time for me to go.
-Hey! Who's calling you?
-♪ Everything, Jaitreya! ♪
-The stars, Dada.
-Hey Vedha!
♪ In this brave pursuit
of our purpose ♪
♪ O planets, will you not bless us
And deem it worthy? ♪
♪ On this mission
for my mother's glory ♪
♪ O cosmos, grant us
Your blessing of victory! ♪
This car isn't yours.
You could've let go of it, right?
It becomes mine once I accept it!
O Aadi Yogi!
This is your command and mercy.
Jaitreya!
♪ With fire-lit flames as
My guiding star ♪
♪ And the lightning above
Blessing my way ♪
♪ As silence whispers
its gentle cue ♪
♪ Bright stars above
Won't they show me the way? ♪
♪ Each particle of my being is
Your blessing, Mother ♪
♪ In every moment, your love
Guards me like grace ♪
♪ With your fierce will
Lighting the skies ♪
♪ Won't your sacred vow
Rise and be realised? ♪
I may not think like my mother…
but I will fulfill her desire.
Guide me the way, Dear Goddess.
This book leads to immortality,
forged from all
the scriptures as one.
What are these banyan roots?
Why make bracelets from them, Lama?
What's your next move?
Kaalabhooti!
The Kaalabhooti he used on our tribe
he will now unleash it
onto the world.
An unwanted burden
weighs heavily on Earth.
I must be
the one to reduce it, Professor.
To prevent mass destruction…
the nine books
must not fall into his grasp.
It's your duty to prevent
that from happening.
You're confronting someone
who dares to defy God!
If the nine sacred scriptures
fall into his grasp,
another bloodshed
like Kalinga is sure to happen.
He knows the book
is under your possession.
And he's definitely heading
your way now.
I will not let him succeed,
even if it costs my life.
The day I carve my mark
on this Earth
has finally arrived, Professor!
The minute we spot him,
I'll shoot him in his face.
-What do you say, Zoya?
-We have to kill them.
Sir, we greeted Tantra,
smeared powder on our faces,
and almost hugged death.
You still want to catch him
despite all of this?
I salute your professionalism, sir!
We can't catch them
without God's grace.
Come in! Command central!
Four people with the markings you
spoke of were seen
at the railway station.
Sir!
What do you say to this, Ashok?
(speaking Khmer)
No, aunty, that's not it.
What is this?
Is it coffee or tea?
Is it vodka or whisky…?
What is this? Shut up and pour!
Chatterbox.
Hey!
Looks like God
is on our side today, Ashok.
Now the game is over.
Take that mystical stick.
Sir, you don't know
anything about him.
-Listen to me--
-Hey! Shut up.
First, lock them all up.
-Sir, at least…
-Sreedhar.
-Take that book.
-Yes, sir!
Sir, listen to us.
-We need to go to Kumbhamela.
-Come.
Sir, many lives are at stake.
Sir… Sir!
-Don't panic! We're police.
-Calm down! Calm down!
-Please listen to us, sir.
-Please sit.
Don't panic!
This is a police intervention.
Move, move inside, please!
It's an open-top setup.
Hope you're comfortable.
Sir, something feels off.
My left eyeball is twitching.
Sir, you don't get it. I heard
the entire history in the flashback.
Since the book is here,
chaos will break out here itself.
If you don't uncuff him,
it'll lead to a catastrophe, sir!
Professor,
this is the same type of stone…
they pelted at me when I was a kid.
Now it's my turn!
I'll sacrifice millions
of these wretches,
who misuse God's name
to deceive people,
to my Kaalabhoothi.
I'll prove that
the worthy ones don't need God!
For that to happen, the immortality
in the ninth book must be mine.
Sir, they arrived. Remove the cuffs.
Please, sir!
Stop!
You'll all die either way.
There's no driver on this train.
Don't panic, don't panic!
Pull it! Pull the chain, sir!
It's over, sir!
Call your loved ones while you can.
Vedha!
Dude!
Hey, Lord of the stick!
Sir! Sir!
Sir!
Finally.
I swear on Maisamma.
It's your final day on Earth.
It's meant for good. It won't work
in the hands of the wicked.
Hurry up!
Get down. Hurry up!
-Sir, please wait.
-Come on.
-Sir! Sir!
I get it now. This isn't an arrest.
it's just you covering your fear.
Uncuff me. We must help!
Vedha!
Jaitreya!
This is the end…
And the beginning!
In this great ritual
that saves millions,
this is the only help
I can offer you.
This was the first bracelet
Mahabir put on my tribe.
I hid this for 20 years, knowing
Kaalabhoothi could strike any day.
This method demands…
the sacrifice of a life.
Dude!
As death closes in on him
during this great battle,
who will protect him?
If he stands
ready to die for Dharma,
nature itself
will become his shield.
If a demon who has conquered
death dares to defy,
God himself will descend
in the form of the weapon
that is meant to slay him.
Do you know what kind of
weapon he's reaching for?
It is the Tandavam once wielded by
the First Warrior to uphold Dharma.
O Sage, this weapon I touched
will turn divine in the hands
of the one who stands for Dharma.
It is the Kodanda, the sacred
bow of Lord Rama, the Purushottama.
This is history.
This is the destiny yet to come.
This is Mirai!
With Mirai's help, the sacred texts
reached their rightful keepers.
Most importantly, this has come
to the notice of a person,
who has been seeking vengeance
against sage Agatsya and Lord Rama.
This end has opened the curtain
for a new beginning.
Hey! I rented you my shed
to make metal.
What the hell is going on here?
Where is all this gold coming from?
How did you get
a ton of gold within a week?
How?
Like this.
Gold is a metal too.
Didn't you tell him that?
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
This is a dead end!
An end where death is the
only thing left behind.
Mirai.
Whatever destroyed the
one who defied death…
must belong to me!
I will deliver justice in this age
that was denied in Treta Yuga.
Boom!