(bright music)
(laughing)
(echoing train)
(suspenseful music)
Dear Author,
my name is Kim Dokja.
I just read the last episode
that you uploaded today.
(atmospheric music)
Your web novel, TWSA,
Three Ways to Survive
the Apocalypse,
began its publication
when I was
in my third year
of middle school.
Mammals include
humans, bears...
I still remember
that first sentence.
The subway car stopped
in the middle of Dongho Bridge.
(screeching)
(woman over PA system):
Planetary system 8612's
free service has now ended.
(Kim Dokja): To punish
fallen humanity,
the gods sent down
terrible hardships.
And as the world
neared complete collapse,
the hero Yoo Junghyuk
and his companions
overcame these deadly trials.
(screaming)
(grunting)
At first,
TWSA was quite popular.
But as the story went on,
people called it too extreme
or unrealistic.
Many stopped following
the story.
(beast barking)
(grunting)
- Hey! What's that?
- (grunting)
Let me see it!
- Just let me see it!
- Give me my phone!
Do you wanna die?
Still, during my school years,
your story was everything to me.
(atmospheric music)
With every update,
I'd reread the last two episodes
to keep the flow.
And on weekends,
I reread the entire
week's episodes.
And yes, when the views
fell to just one reader,
that was me.
Why read a novel for 10 years
when no one else was reading it?
(swelling dramatic music)
Yoo Junghyuk.
I wanted to be him.
(screaming)
(grunting)
Yoo and his companions brought
vicious enemies to their knees.
And they never backed down,
whether it be monsters
or humans alike.
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
Lee Hyeonseong!
But as his companions
fell one by one,
to survive, Yoo Junghyuk
resolved to be stronger.
(screaming)
And so he did.
He got stronger and stronger,
but as I entered high school,
I stayed the same.
Now, you two are going
to fight each other.
The loser will become
our doormat.
But the winner gets his freedom.
What? You can't even
fight to save yourself?
Alright, fine.
Don't do it, then.
(phone dinging)
But then,
that just means both
of you losers are doormats.
If only...
I could also get stronger.
Like Yoo Junghyuk.
That was always my wish.
I went to a mediocre college,
worked a bunch of mediocre jobs,
then I joined this company.
On a temp contract.
(somber music continues)
Today, the novel ended.
And so did my contract.
Good work. Thanks, Dokja.
Huh. Hey.
Call if you're in the area.
I'll treat you.
Thanks.
This is why we shouldn't hire
these regional college grads.
(sighing): Yeah.
They're not on our level.
(Dokja): I really appreciate
all your hard work
writing this story
for so long.
But I have to ask:
Why'd you make Yoo Junghyuk
the only survivor at the end?
(curious music)
What's the point of an ending
with only one survivor?
Yoo Junghyuk once said,
"I can't help it if others
are sacrificed so I can live."
Is that the theme of the novel?
If it is, I can't accept that.
Sir, your novel...
is the worst.
(indistinct chatter)
(echoing train approaching)
(woman over PA system):
The train for Daehwa
is approaching.
Repeat. The train for Daehwa
(low mechanical humming)
(sighing loudly)
Jeez, that was quite the sigh.
Uh, hi... Sangah.
Was it your last day, too?
(chuckling)
I knew they'd never
hire me full-time.
No use fighting for something
that was never gonna be yours.
Just need to move on
and find a job that suits me.
Oh... thank you so much.
Have you, uh,
already found a new job?
(chuckling)
Just a part-time one.
Need to survive
the month somehow.
Hey, you know how I designed
all those character costumes?
I felt that was something
I was really good at,
so I think I wanna pursue
designing real clothes.
Eventually launch my own brand
and open a shop.
Cool, huh?
That sounds really great,
Sangha.
- (chuckling)
- Oh, Sangha!
- Fancy meeting you here.
- Uh, hey Mr. Han.
Didn't I say I'd buy you
dinner tonight?
Uh... thank you,
but I have plans.
(chuckling)
I gotta say, I'm disappointed
our little Sangha
is leaving us.
(nervous chuckling)
You know,
if you'd given me a chance,
I'd have fought harder
to get you hired.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I don't think my skills
were there yet.
What do you say we
get off this train
and maybe grab that dinner?
I know a nice place
in Apgujeong.
Oh. Uh, I'm heading
to my part-time job.
Hey, no excuses.
I'll pay for the hours you miss.
Uh... that's really okay, sir.
I'm actually seeing someone.
Ah. Is this him?
Uh, hello, Mr. Han.
Uh, we've met. I'm Kim Dokja
from map development.
Huh.
(chuckling)
So, you two have had something
going on all this time?
Well. That's disappointing.
(nervous chuckling)
(woman over PA system):
Our next stop is Apgujeong.
Apgujeong.
The doors are on your right.
(chuckling)
Enjoy your dinner, sir.
-  - Please stand clear.
- Thanks, Sangha.
I'll see you around, I guess.
We are not
responsible for any...
(sighing)
(softly): God.
That guy is such a creep.
I couldn't even report him
'cause I was worried about...
(scoffing)
...getting fired.
That was smart.
Silence is golden.
Oh, please.
I wasn't being smart.
I was being an idiot.
And that's what's so
frustrating about it.
I knew I should've
said something,
but I didn't
because I'm a coward.
Huh? You see how
frustrating that is?
(phone buzzing)
(announcements continue
indistinctly)
Sorry. Just give me a minute.
(woman over PA system):
The doors are now closing.
(train station horn ringing)
(doors shutting)
- Your girlfriend?
- Oh. No.
(mechanical humming)
(scoffing)
(suspenseful music)
(Dokja): The ending I want?
What does that even mean?
Next stop, Oksu.
Oh. Thank you, miss.
(Dokja): Readers' submissions
at seven PM.
But I was the only reader.
Does that mean
I can change the ending?
(suspenseful music continues)
(loud crashing afar)
(screaming passengers)
(screeching)
(people groaning)
Are you okay?
(woman over PA system):
Planetary system 8612's
free service has now ended.
This is the beginning
of paid content.
(dramatic music)
I repeat.
Planetary system 8612's
free service has now ended.
This is the beginning
of paid content.
(Dokja): Is this actually...
"An announcement echoes
through the air,
planetary system 8612's
free service has now ended.
This is the beginning
of paid content.
This one fellow who
I'll call a Dokkaebi..."
What? A Dokkaebi?
(electronic buzzing)
(overlapping chatter)
(man): What the hell
is going on?
-  - Oh, my God...
- (camera shutters clicking)
This is just like
the start of the novel.
Hello! The language patch
is now working. Ha!
People. Can you hear me?
Oh, Jesus Christ, man.
What is this?
Yes. I understand
your frustration.
I know you're all busy,
but I still require
your attention
for a moment--
(man): Enough of this
crap already!
Get this train moving!
This is unacceptable!
I'll have to ask you
to quiet down.
You need to listen to what
I'm about to tell you all.
'Cause I assure you all,
it's of the utmost importance!
Why don't you shut the hell up
and get us out of here
before I lose my shit on you?
(robotic grumbling)
I got a bunch of shit
to get done
and you guys stop
the train for this?
You're nothing but a bunch
of stupid ass--
(laser zapping)
(gasps of surprise)
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
I said quiet!
(dramatic music continues)
Now, humans,
I want you to listen closely
to every word I say to you.
High up in space,
watching with cruel amusement
are celestial beings
far greater than any human.
And they have, at last,
come to a decision.
That humans, the most
vulgar, greedy, pathetic,
self-centred race
in the whole universe
must all be punished!
(woman over PA system):
Channel BI-7623 has opened.
Constellations are entering.
Welcome, dear Constellations!
Some very interesting things
are about to happen.
So, please enjoy!
From this moment on,
all you humans will be
given a scenario.
(suspenseful music)
And how you solve that scenario
will help determine your fate.
(fingers snapping)
The first main scenario
is starting.
(gasping)
Since this is your first time,
I'll explain it to you.
Kill one or more
living organisms
in this subway car
within 10 minutes.
Succeed and you each
get 300 coins.
Fail and you'll end up
like that poor soul.
Simple. Huh?
Our dear Constellations will be
watching it all unfold closely,
so pay no heed
to laws or ethics.
Just show us without reservation
the true nature of you humans.
(diabolical laughter)
(dramatic music)
(clock dinging)
(dramatic music swelling)
(clock dinging loudly)
Our phones aren't working,
right?
No. They're not gonna work.
(indistinct background chatter)
Are you alone?
Are your parents here?
(gasping)
Are you gonna kill me?
(indistinct chatter)
(woman): Oh, my God!
(distant screaming)
(dramatic music)
(all shouting)
(grunting)
(crying)
(tense music)
(Dokja): Yoo Junghyuk?
This is crazy.
A novel that only I've read
has become a reality.
That means I know the future.
Wait... then next is...
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
First, I have to beat
this scenario.
Let me think.
One or more living organisms.
One or more living organisms...
(passengers screaming)
Sangha.
(breathing heavily)
Hang onto this.
I'm gonna go save the others.
Where are you going?
Are you crazy?
You'll die if you go there!
(breathing heavily)
I know this.
- Huh?
- I think I know
how to solve this.
(suspenseful music)
(screaming)
Hey! Everyone! Listen up!
(indistinct arguing)
People! Listen to me
for a minute!
(screaming)
I know what to do!
(suspenseful music)
(announcer): The first kill
on this car has taken place.
The killer will now
receive 300 coins.
(electrical humming)
What? Wait.
How did you do that, huh?
It said we've all gotta kill
one or more living organisms,
right?
It said...
living organism.
It didn't say humans.
(gasping in surprise)
Wait, wait! Stop.
Hold on. Don't come closer.
Stop.
Stop or I'll kill them all!
Wait, don't! Wait!
How many ants are in that thing?
Tell us that.
(suspenseful music continues)
Let me see.
Not enough for everyone.
Hey, buddy!
If there's not enough,
you should've said so.
Why'd you kill one
before saying anything?
How do we decide who gets one?
We should give them
to the kids first.
Hey, hey! Shut up, lady!
Everyone's life is worth
the same thing here, okay?
Your kid's life
is not more important!
Everyone, calm down.
Look, I wish I had enough
- for everyone, but I...
- So? What do we do?
There's no time.
We need to hurry!
(echoing): Hold on. Hold on!
This guy works for me.
I'm his boss.
Let me through. Just a minute.
Okay, look. Why are you making
the call on this?
There are people here with way
more life experience than you.
So give it.
(overlapping chatter)
Yeah, that might be true,
but people here--
Trust me. I know
how to do this properly.
Just give it to me!
(overlapping arguments)
(shouting)
(man): Hey, back off!
(suspenseful music)
(overlapping shouting)
Come on! Why won't you die?
Sheesh! Just die already!
(grunting)
The hell's wrong with you?
You wanna get yourself killed?
Here. Both you and her
can live, okay?
I've got my own ant.
Right here.
(groaning weakly)
A pathetic, useless insect.
In the novel, Kim Namwoon
is part of Yoo Junghyuk's team.
Was he always like this?
- Hey!
- Get off!
(grunting)
Alright then. Maybe I'll
just kill you instead.
(grunting)
Wait. If this is really
just like the novel...
Spend 300 coins on strength.
(announcer): 300 coins
have been spent on strength.
Strength is now increased.
(grunting in pain)
(groaning)
(dramatic music)
You son of a bitch...
Now you're a dead man.
(announcer): Kim Namwoon
has activated
the Grim Dark Awakening skill.
(Dokja): In the novel,
Namwoon was first to receive
the Constellation's support.
But why a guy like him?
(tense music)
(grunting)
(coughing)
Ah... Got some skills.
This is cool as hell!
(laughing)
If you wanna save the old lady,
then you have to die.
(screaming)
Are the ant eggs
living organisms, too?
(announcer): One organism
killed.
300 coins paid as a reward.
(repetitive dinging)
(Dokja): Spend 3,000 coins
on stamina.
Spend 3,000 coins on agility.
(grunting)
(groaning)
(breathing heavily)
Wait. Wait!
Okay.
I won't hurt the old lady.
- Just give me an ant.
- I've changed my mind.
I don't want you
in this story anymore.
What the hell
are you talking about?
(breathing heavily)
Get off! Move!
Hey! Out of the way!
Out of the way!
Come on, move!
(grunting)
Move!
Get away from her!
Argh! Come on!
(grunting)
I'll keep going. I swear to God!
(announcer): Time has expired.
The scenario has ended.
(somber music)
(thudding)
(screaming)
Ma'am. Ma'am!
Excuse me, please wake up.
Ma'am?
(groaning softly)
(somber music continues)
Dokja?
Hey, are you okay?
(somber music continues)
Ta-da! We wish
to give a heartfelt congrats
to all of the 17 humans
who cleared the first scenario!
You were supposed
to kill each other.
But killing the ants wasn't
technically against the rules.
The Constellations said that
this car was more fun to watch
than the others.
So I guess we better move on.
Now, for the Constellations
to review and determine
amongst themselves
which of you will receive
the Constellations' support.
The Constellations' support
is a tremendous gift.
If you choose well,
it'll be a big help
in clearing future scenarios!
(electrical dinging)
(Dokja): "Thanks
to your actions,
the following Constellations
wish to give you their support."
Support? Constellations?
What does this mean?
The Constellations watch over
all the scenarios
from all the way
out in space.
(atmospheric music)
They enjoy laughing
at the struggles of humans
who are trying to survive.
If you're chosen to receive
their support,
it can be very helpful.
But eventually,
that debt must be paid back.
(loud banging)
(shouting)
(deep roaring)
(loud metallic groaning)
(shouting)
(glass breaking)
(glass shattering)
Quick! Come to this side.
Quick!
(tense music)
(screaming)
Lee Hyeonseong.
He's another character
who fought with Yoo Junghyuk.
(groaning)
Listen, don't waste
your strength.
- Use your skill.
- My skill?
How the hell do I do that?
At the bottom right
of your vision
there's a skill window.
If you just think hard about
your skill,
it should work.
(mechanical groaning)
(screaming)
(creaking)
(announcer): Lee Hyeonseong
has activated
Great Mountain Push level one.
(dramatic music)
Out of the way. Move.
(yelling)
As soon as you're out,
get yourself across the bridge!
Fast as you can!
I'm Lee Hyeonseong.
I'm Kim Dokja.
You better go.
(metallic groaning)
- (loud banging)
- Ahh!
(thudding)
(breathing heavily)
What are you doing?
Hey, hurry! We have to go.
(metallic clanking)
Ah! Ugh...
Ugh, goddamnit.
We need to go. Come on.
(shaky breathing)
(sighing)
Don't cry. It's okay.
But we need to go right now.
(whimpering)
What's your name?
- Lee Gilyeong.
- Hmm, Gilyeong.
Can you run fast, Gilyeong?
Wait...
My ant farm got destroyed
because of you...
I know.
I'm really sorry about that,
but we really need to--
No. My mom says apologizing
isn't always enough.
(sniffing)
You should take responsibility.
(dramatic music)
(announcer): A sub scenario
has arrived.
Cross the severed bridge.
Why are they calling it
a severed bridge when it's not?
'Cause it's about to be!
(screaming)
(grumbling)
(growling)
(water splashing loudly)
This is so exciting,
but you can't just stand there,
you fools!
I'll raise the difficulty level!
Ahh!
(groaning)
(screaming)
Argh!
(grunting)
Dokja!
How is that even possible?
I just thought of that
and it appeared out of nowhere,
almost like I summoned it.
Perfect! I'll go first!
Lee Hyeonseong!
(creatures growling)
(dramatic music)
Sangha!
You chose a sponsor, right?
Your sponsor is helping you.
Come on, let's move, Sangha.
Soon, poisonous gas
will start to spread.
We need to get underground
quickly.
And make sure to collect coins!
That's really important!
How do you know all this?
Let's just get
to the subway station.
Geumho station is the closest.
If we take the same subway
station Yoo took,
we should be safe.
Wait.
But at Chungmuro station...
(screaming)
Early in the novel,
Yoo died at Chungmuro station
fighting the fire dragon.
(dramatic music)
Yoo used his Regression skill
to go back to the beginning
of the story.
But in a world without a hero
everyone disappears.
The hero must not die.
But even with
the tactics I know
one can't defeat
the fire dragon alone.
(tense music)
(breathing shakily)
(sighing)
This is so tedious.
(creatures growling)
What if...
I tell Yoo Junghyuk
those tactics?
And we can fight together?
Dokja! Come on, hurry!
Wait. I'll be there in a sec!
(gunshots ringing)
Hey, Yoo Junghyuk!
(suspenseful music)
(breathing heavily)
What are you?
(hesitating groans)
Uh, well...
Kim Namwoon
shouldn't die this soon.
- Did you kill him?
- No.
No, I swear I didn't kill him.
(announcer): Yoo Junghyuk
has activated
the Lie Detection skill.
(groaning)
Interesting.
You already know
how to use coins.
It's... not that, I just...
Mr. Dokja!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just stay there.
I'm really okay!
Please stay!
And you know Lee Hyeonseong.
Uh... I just met him
earlier today.
I'll ask you again.
What are you?
If I tell him that I read
all this in a novel,
he'll never believe me, right?
(suspenseful music)
My name is Kim Dokja.
In a few days, you'll die
fighting the fire dragon.
In Chungmuro station.
Even if you regress,
it'll take a long time
to clear the scenario.
But if we go together,
you can defeat the fire dragon.
I know the tactics you need.
(announcer): Yoo Junghyuk
has activated
the Lie Detection skill.
How do you know
about those tactics?
My personal skill is prophecy.
So if you take me with you,
you can beat all the scenarios.
Let's cross the bridge.
You'll go via Geumho station,
right?
- Hey, Kim Dokja.
- Yes?
(screaming)
Wait! Please!
Why are you doing this?
Tell me about the tactics.
We can just go together
and beat the scenario!
(screaming)
I can't stand dragging
people along.
But if I tell you,
you're just gonna drop me.
I'll drop you anyway.
(screaming)
Wait! Please wait! Wait!
Mr. Yoo, I have a terrible
fear of heights!
(deep roaring)
Ah! Please!
I'm just trying to help!
First, let go!
Wait! No, no, no! Don't let go!
Ah!
(breathing heavily)
Last chance.
Why is all this happening?
Why are humans
suddenly being punished?
How... do you expect
me to know?
(chuckling)
Survive and come to Chungmuro.
Then you'll know.
And then I'll decide
if I'm gonna fight with you.
(screaming)
Yoo Junghyuk! You bastard!
In a few days, Yoo will die
fighting the fire dragon.
But for me to live,
the hero of the story
cannot die.
But before any of that...
I'm gonna die.
(screaming)
(echoing scream)
(groaning)
(coughing)
(retching)
(spitting)
(breathing heavily)
(announcer): A hidden scenario
has been unlocked.
Kill the Ichthyosaur
and escape from its stomach.
(breathing heavily)
I have to kill it to escape?
(sighing)
Oh, shit!
I don't have any items.
Huh?
Huh? He's alive? He's alive!
Constellations,
as you can no doubt see,
a human has entered
the Ichthyosaur's belly.
(laughing)
This is a truly...
(Dokja): If I get on
the Dokkaebi's good side,
he can help me get coins
or an item.
And the thing a Dokkaebi
likes most of all...
...a human surprises us.
Am I right, Constellations?
Hey! Get over here.
Oh. The human's talking to me.
I better get closer.
You lowly human.
You are quite a sight
playing God with that ant farm.
And you were
really terrifying, huh?
Shooting people
with that little laser.
(chuckling)
You will speak to me
with more respect.
Yeah, well,
if you don't like it,
why don't you just
shoot me then?
(laughing)
How dare a foolish human
speak to a Dokkaebi this way?
- Hey, Bihyung.
- Huh?
You're doing
a star stream now, right?
What the... You know my name?
And how do you know
about star steams?
Your channel
must be exploding now.
Who else is as entertaining
as me so far?
The Constellations
must be so curious
what I'll do next.
But if you kill me now...
Could you handle the blowback?
Uh... But how is it possible
that you know all of this?
Close your channel for a sec.
Let's talk.
Oh, wow. Constellations,
let take a quick ad break, okay?
(chuckling)
(cutesy music)
Hmm. Now speak.
How can an ordinary human
know about star streams?
(groaning)
Oh, shit. That hurts.
Star steams are not important.
Uh, what?
You told me to close it!
- (groaning)
- Bihyung,
you need to think
about this, huh?
- Hmm?
- How long you've been
a panhandle to some
lowly ninth-grade Dokkaebi?
Huh? What are you saying?
What does a Dokkaebi
do anyway?
Let Constellations
into your channel
and show them random stories
and scenarios with humans?
Hopefully get enough donations
to be a first-grade Dokkaebi.
(grumbling)
But I guarantee you,
my story will be better
than you can ever imagine.
Hmm...
Sign an exclusive
contract with me.
(scoffs)
And you'll be the Dokkaebi king.
(gasping)
Wow!
(laughing)
You poor human.
You're overreaching.
Why sign a contract with someone
who's about to die?
Why do you think
Constellations
watch the streams, huh?
Well, it's very amusing
watching puny humans
struggle to survive.
That's why they donate, too.
(sighs)
Of course.
Well, then suppose
we do sign a contract.
In the subway I used ants
to clear the scenario
and I fought Kim Namwoon
using my skills.
Then I was eaten by
an Ichthyosaur,
but if I escape
and keep clearing
every scenario once I get out,
how many donations do you think
our channel will get, huh?
How can I be sure
you can do all that?
Why don't you go see how many
donations you have now?
Hmm?
(gasping)
Oh...
(gasps)
Whoa, look at all this.
How many zeros!
I can't believe this!
(laughing)
Okay, let's sign a contract!
Exclusive Contract for Partnership
We split the profits 50:50, okay?
Hmm.
(deep roaring)
(suspenseful music)
(squelching)
(trickling)
Oh. It's starting. Okay.
Constellations,
the Ichthyosaur stomach acid
has started to flow.
How will our human escape this?
Bihyung.
Open the Dokkaebi shop, please.
(gasps)
The Dokkaebi shop?
How on earth do you
know all of this?
(atmospheric music)
(soft chiming)
The human has
purchased an item.
Let's see what he plans
to do with it.
(grunting)
(deep pained roar)
(breathing heavily)
(Dokja): Yoo Junghyuk
was trapped in an Ichthyosaur
stomach once, too.
If you block all its stomach
acid ducts with thorns,
it'll die.
But the problem is...
there are so many of them.
(sighing loudly)
(suspenseful music)
In a few days, you'll die
fighting the fire dragon.
In Chungmuro station.
Even if you regress,
it'll take a long time
to clear this scenario.
But if we go together,
you can defeat the fire dragon.
(suspenseful music continues)
(pained roaring)
(grunting)
This scenario's a test
of endurance.
The last one.
(grunting)
(groaning angrily)
(low roaring)
(announcer): The hidden
scenario has been cleared.
9,000 coins have been awarded.
(breathing heavily)
Huh? Wait. Is it true?
Dokja, did you really defeat
the Ichthyosaur?
- Amazing!
- Get out of the way. Move!
Oh.
(grunting)
(squelching)
(yawning)
(grunting)
Wait.
That's the Ichthyosaur Nucleus.
How did you know where it was?
Put this in
the Dokkaebi shop auction.
- Ah...
- Not to sell.
I want a one-to-one trade.
And I'll only trade it
for Ether of Faith.
Put up a notification window
when there's an offer.
(gasping)
Dokja,
this is very impressive.
I must say,
killing the mighty
Ichthyosaur is one thing,
but knowing exactly
where to find its nucleus
and wanting to trade
for Ether of Faith...
Ether of Faith
is so incredibly rare,
I doubt anyone in the early
scenario will have it.
Yeah? We'll let's try
and get it.
Soon as we can.
And when I call you,
come right away.
And open the Dokkaebi shop
when I need it.
- Okay?
- I'll do my best, Dokja.
And it's nothing big,
but here's a gift
to celebrate our contract.
You'll need it when you go out.
Huh.
A starter pack.
(scoffing)
Nice.
(muffled coughing)
(muffled panting)
(groaning)
(announcer): The Constellation
Hunter of the Dark Moon
admires your endurance,
and wishes to sponsor you
and join you on your journey.
The Constellation Bringer
of Dark Light
wishes to sponsor you
and join you on your journey.
(Dokja): Constellations,
you're really enjoying this,
aren't you?
(grunting)
(atmospheric music)
Hey, Bihyeong, turn off
all notifications
related to Constellations.
Yes, sir. But where
are you going now?
Geumho Station, I need
to meet someone there.
Are you referring
to the tall fellow?
I wouldn't do that,
he's got many items,
and his level far exceeds
your own.
We just signed a contract,
what'll I do if you die?
I'm hungry.
(gulping)
(panting)
(coughing)
(gasps)
(breathing heavily)
Hey, hey, hey.
(whimpering)
Hey. Can you hear me?
I need you to wake up.
You good? Can you stand up?
(ominous music)
(breathing heavily)
Ahh!
Did you say Exit One?
(growling)
Wait!
Wait! Please wait!
(thudding)
(panting)
(grunting)
Hey, are you okay?
- Over there!
- What's going on?
- Can it be?
- Yeah, look, see. Over there!
Jeong Heewon?
Are you really alive?
(Dokja): Jeong Heewon?
I thought for sure
you were done for.
I'm gonna kill that asshole!
Er, just one question.
Why did you bother dragging
her all the way back in here,
when you know damn well
we already finished with her?
Come on, don't be a nuisance!
(Dokja): This chapter
in the novel
was particularly boring.
The characters
were such stereotypes.
Bang Cheolsu?
Excuse me? You know who I am?
(sighs)
Well, let's do it.
Spend 1,500 coins on Strength.
(announcer): 1,500 coins
spent on Strength.
(grunting)
(shouting)
Holy crap, he's using skills?
Hey man, you should've
just said so!
(announcer): Bang Cheolsu
is supported by his sponsor,
Monarch of the Small Fries.
Why would he choose
such a shitty sponsor?
Right, chest, right.
This guy's so predictable.
(grunting)
Argh, ugh!
- Boss, you okay?
- What are you waiting for?
- Kill him! Now!
- You okay, boss?
(groaning)
Bang Cheolsu!
What is going on down here?
Ah, shit! Come on, let's go.
(groaning)
Oh.
Wait, who the hell is this guy?
Huh? Dokja!
Ah!
Ah...
The people are saying
the congressman
is the only reason
they've all survived down here.
He's been able to persuade
the high-level people
to provide, like,
go out and hunt,
then share it
with the residents.
All done, it should heal
pretty quickly.
(gasp)
Gilyeong, I told you
to please stop doing that!
Why? They're my friends.
Oh, he's been acting weird
since that day on the train.
He says he can talk to bugs when
he puts his hands up like that.
I'm not weird,
I just like doing this.
Hmph!
Mr. Dokja.
Why did that man
on the bridge
just let you fall like that?
What?
Heh, oh him.
I've known him since
I was in school.
He's never been the easiest guy
to get along with, you know?
Didn't he cause
a scene here too?
No, he hasn't
been here at all.
A-are you sure?
He crossed the bridge,
and even when the gas came out,
he just walked away to Namsan.
(Dokja): Yoo Junghyuk didn't
come to Geumho Station?
That doesn't make sense.
Hold on, that means you haven't
cleared the scenario, have you?
A group of people
went into the tunnel
to try and clear it,
but no one came back.
Damn, if we can't clear it,
we can't pass the barrier
and get to Chungmuro.
But that isn't
what happens in the novel.
Alright everyone, listen up.
The survival fee payment
is due in three hours.
Search party'll leave
in five minutes,
so make sure you're ready.
We let the elderly stay behind,
but every able-bodied man
is required to come with us.
The Geumho Station scenario
exacts a survival fee
on all residents, until
all the monsters are defeated.
One hundred coins per day.
Residents who couldn't afford
the fee
went out on dangerous hunts.
And those who couldn't
make the payments...
(screaming)
...would die on the spot.
Hey, you!
You, new guy!
They say that you took
all the coins for yourself,
is that true?
- What?
- You earned coins
by hunting monsters
in this district, didn't you?
Then share the coins
with the rest of us!
What, you were just gonna keep
your mouth shut and not tell us?
Give the coins
to the congressman,
so they can be shared
with everyone!
He thinks
he's the only one suffering!
- Yeah, exactly!
- It's true!
No, give it to us!
Look, I think
there's been some sort
of misunderstanding.
I've never gone out hunting.
Don't lie,
we know you have, huh!
- I don't believe this guy!
- Come on, we know
the only reason you fight
so well is because
you earned those coins
while hunting!
Er, no, really,
I've never been hunting.
And, even if I had,
then those coins would be mine.
He just doesn't understand!
Listen, this is how it works.
The only reason we've survived
this long
is by pooling our strength
and working together.
(scoffs)
Oh, right. You must have.
But...
who exactly told you
I have all these coins?
Does that really even matter?
Please, just go to the office
and turn them in.
We're all really desperate here.
So then, you should just tell
me.
And if you do,
I'll give you each
100 coins. Huh?
(crowd murmuring)
Who told you? Bang Cheolsu?
I told them.
When I saw how proficient
you were fighting that gang,
I just knew. Usually,
those with a lot of coins
are least willing to help
those in need.
I was hoping you'd understand
how dire our situation
is down here,
but with us being so desperate,
we may have been a bit rude.
If we offended you at all,
I apologize.
No, no please, it's okay.
I-I'm not offended.
Kim Dokja,
20 people can't afford
the fee today.
I want to keep everyone alive
by any means necessary.
Please help us,
I'm begging you, sir.
(Dokja): Wait,
I remember now.
I know who this man is.
You want my coins?
Well, that's not gonna happen.
(crowd murmuring)
You really don't care if 20
of these people die today?
Even if they live today,
there's still tomorrow.
Let's deal with today first!
How can you just stand there
and not help?
(crowd yelling)
Alright, that's enough.
Everyone, please stay calm.
(yells)
(scoffs)
What's wrong with you?
I thought you were
a good person, Mr. Kim.
But I guess I read you
all wrong.
Alright. I'll help you.
But even if I give you
the coins,
you'll still need more tomorrow.
So instead,
"Pass Through the Tunnel
and Neutralize All
the Monsters Within It."
I'll clear the scenario
for you. Okay?
Cheon Inho of Geumho Station.
He sold himself
to the Constellations,
and gave up his humanity
to become a monster.
Ant eggs?
Instead of human beings?
Uh, that shouldn't be allowed,
should it? I mean, ah, ow...
If a man like you
was beaten by him,
the rumors must be true.
Kim Dokja has the highest
abilities
and most coins
in Geumho Station now by far.
Well, if he's that strong,
he'll be able to clear
the scenario, no problem!
How many times
must I repeat myself to you?
As long as I am here,
that scenario
- will never be cleared!
- O-of course.
You're right,
of course you're right.
When you're right,
you're right.
(laughing)
It's human nature for the weak
to bow down before the strong.
A pathetic, meaningless
weakling like him,
who suddenly gains strength,
will run wild,
thinking he's a big shot.
It's nothing
but reckless gallantry.
This world is filled
with the decaying bodies
- of nobodies like him.
- Well then, if he dies,
we better make sure
we're the ones who collect
all his coins. How much
do you think he really has?
If the rumors are true,
it could be
in the tens of thousands.
Is that correct, Mr. Han?
(coughs)
Yes. It's true, sorry.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Help yourself.
(chuckles nervously)
I'm not going,
why would you go? We'll all die!
We're not gonna die,
don't worry.
I'll go, Mister!
I had fun fighting
those monsters before.
You think I'm gonna let you
fight any monsters?
You're still in grade school.
No way!
Mr. Dokja?
If you have extra coins,
why do all this?
Why not just share them
with everyone?
Exactly, thank you!
Why do we have to go through
all this trouble-- Oh!
I mean, you, that is!
Even if I shared the coins,
people would still die.
If we want to stop people
from dying,
we have to get to the root
of the problem.
Isn't that so, Heewon?
In the novel,
Heewon rebels against
Cheon Inho,
loses her friends and dies
in the convenience store.
Now, all she has left is rage.
You said the congressman
is behind all this, but how?
When I found Heewon,
it wasn't monsters
that attacked her.
Bang Cheolsu's gang
is on his side, too.
They recruit a search party
to go out looking for coins,
and after hunting,
they quietly kill everyone.
My friends died when we tried
to stop them once and for all.
But, why? Why would
they kill those people?
When you die, your coins
fall out for anyone to take.
That bastard Cheon Inho
isn't really human.
(sighs)
It's way too dark in here.
How are we supposed to fight
if we can't see anything?
Gilyeong,
can you give us a hand?
Me? Can I?
What are you talking about?
That thing that
you thought of, show me.
Hey Gilyeong, don't you dare
call cockroaches!
(soft chiming)
Wow, Gilyeong!
They told me
the monsters are coming.
(suspenseful music)
Make sure to use
your sponsors.
You know how to increase your
abilities with coins, right?
Spend all your coins
on strength and agility.
All my coins? Shouldn't I save
some for the Survival Fee?
(Dokja grunts)
Maintain this formation.
Don't fight on your own,
we all need to help each other.
Gilyeong,
keep the fireflies steady.
But I wanna fight, too!
Stay behind me.
(low grumbling)
(snarling)
Argh!
(screeching)
- (snarling)
- I got him!
(grunting)
(screaming)
(panting)
Okay, if we follow that one,
we can get some new items.
(breathing heavily)
Mister! If we go this way,
there's supposed to be
really strong monsters, right?
The fireflies told me!
Huh? I don't know.
But you always seem
to know this stuff.
You've been right
about everything.
You're like a god
or something.
Would I be doing this
if I were a god?
If there's any god here,
it's the author.
(ominous music)
(panting)
Sangah! Where are you?
Dokja! Help!
I'm tied up in here!
Ahh! What was that?
(soft eerie music)
(announcer): Welcome.
You have now entered
the Ground Rat's Shrine.
Eliminate the Warden
of the Dark.
(sinister music)
Alright, I guess
I'll go first.
(grunting)
(screeching)
Do I need an item
to defeat a Demon Species?
Mr. Dokja, I'm coming!
Hyeonseong!
Don't! Wait! Stop!
(squealing)
What the...
Oh shit.
Can he do that?
(growling)
(announcer): The Warden
of the Dark
has activated
an illusory prison.
Illusory prison?
(Dokja): The illusory prison
traps the body
and destroys the mind.
If you're caught in it,
you relive your worst memories
and die.
Run, Heewon!
(screaming)
(whimpering)
(breathing heavily)
- What the hell was that?
- No time to explain!
Gilyeong! No, wait! Stop!
(tense ethereal music)
(grunting)
Over there, look!
Ahh!
(panting)
(tense ethereal music continues)
(roaring)
Heewon! I need you
to buy me some time!
- Hey, Bi-heyong, you watching?
- Of course, how can I help?
Open the Dokkaebi shop,
White Star Pure Energy.
But that's 50,000 coins,
you only have 49,000!
(grunting)
(snarling)
Ahh!
(grunts)
(snarling)
(roaring)
(announcer): 50,000 coins paid.
You have bought
White Star Pure Energy.
Your weapon can now deliver
a one-time critical hit.
(panting)
Hyeonseong!
(soft whimpering)
(high-pitched ringing)
- Huh?
- Oh, he's awake!
Hey, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I must have fallen asleep
or something.
Argh!
Take it easy.
You should get some rest.
You'll feel better, trust me.
The Hyeonseong in the novel
was so consumed
by overwhelming guilt
for not saving someone
that he was not able
to make full use
of his abilities and potential.
The Lee Hyeonseong here
is exactly the same.
Well, nice work, everyone.
I think I spotted some treasure
chests further back there.
Let's each go open one.
Two swords for Heewon.
An arm protector
for Hyeonseong.
What about Gilyeong?
When I wear this helmet,
I can hear the insects
more clearly!
Tada! Nice, huh?
Apparently, it'll help me
fight better, too.
Then, I guess
I'll open up mine now, too.
(whirring)
Huh? But yours is broken!
But you did the most,
why do you get something
that doesn't work?
It'll be useful somehow,
I'm sure. Let's go.
This is it, the Broken Faith.
Now if I can just find
an Ether of Faith,
the weapon will be complete.
Huh? What is this?
Mister, I just found something
on the ground, what is it?
Well, if you eat this,
then those white hands
will come out,
and you'll have scary dreams.
So stay far away from it, okay?
Alright, Mister.
- (chuckles)
- Dokja.
How do you know all of this?
What?
Every step of the way,
you seem to know exactly
what's coming
and where we need to go.
It's like you've already
lived in this world.
Okay, thank you!
I was thinking the same thing.
What's going on with you,
Dokja?
Okay, uh...
I don't have any sponsors
or any real special skills.
But I do seem to be able
to predict things
before they happen,
like some sort of prophecy.
Can you really see
what'll happen?
Prophecy?
Dokja,
that is so freaking cool!
Then, do you know
what will happen to the world?
Shouldn't you be able
to see that, too?
Well, the world...
can go back to how it was.
Really?
When?
Because I really wanna go home!
Well, it's gonna
take some time.
Then, tell us
what we have to do.
We're gonna have to clear up
to the 99th scenario.
The 99th?
Is that even possible?
There is someone
who can do it.
A hero who can clear
all scenarios.
And save the whole world.
And that's not... you?
(chuckles nervously)
The two of you saw him
back on Dongho Bridge.
Yoo Junghyuk.
(beast growls)
(groaning)
(loud gasp)
Wait, that guy?
He was so good-looking!
The problem is...
tomorrow, he's gonna die
fighting a monster.
But what happens if he dies?
Then the world dies with him.
It can never go back
to how it was.
He'll be
at Chungmuro Station now.
Once we finish clearing
this scenario,
the barrier will be lifted,
and then I can go there
and help him.
I can try and save him somehow.
Wait!
Didn't we just bust our asses
clearing this scenario?
There's one monster left.
(announcer): Ten minutes
until the Survival Fee payment.
Please have your payments
prepared.
Hey, I just heard that people
in the search party
- are being killed for coins.
- Get off.
- My husband isn't back yet--
- Get off!
Damn, you're annoying!
Yeah, I killed your husband!
What about it?
- No! You didn't!
- Huh? What are you gonna
do about it?
Stupid annoying bitch.
(others screaming)
I told you I'd kill you,
remember?
Sweet dreams!
(groaning)
(coins rattling)
Ms. Jeong Heewon!
If you really want to clear
the scenario,
you know what to do, so do it!
I mean, what is all this, huh?
That's why I'm here!
To kill the last monster
in the scenario.
(laughing)
Well, go on.
Kill them all
and take their coins.
(gang yelling)
(suspenseful music)
(blades clinking)
(Dokja): In the novel,
Jeong Heewon
wasn't that famous,
and wasn't used much
in the story.
But maybe, that's why I rooted
for her more than anyone else.
Heewon, in this story,
you are the hero.
(announcer): The Constellation
Demonic Judge of Fire
approves the use of this skill.
Time of Judgment
has been activated.
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
- Ahh!
- (grunting)
(soft tense music)
(laughing)
Argh!
(grunting)
(tense music)
Hey, wait! Miss!
Hold on.
(chuckling)
You're not actually
gonna kill him, are you?
Maybe you don't know this,
but we don't clear
this scenario.
If we clear it,
the next one is even harder.
At a station nearby,
they cleared the scenario
and all got massacred
in the next one!
It's better and easier
for all of us to just
- pay the 100 coins every day.
- Hold on a second!
What the hell's the matter
with you people?
Why didn't you
tell us that before?
We just spent all our coins
fighting those monsters
to clear the scenario.
Well, every person who tried
to clear it before died,
so we assumed that
you all would just die too.
You saw when you die,
all your coins come out.
The congressman collected
and shared them all.
How were we supposed to know
you'd make it back?
Exactly.
(woman chuckles)
(Dokja): Why'd this happen
to the world?
Why are humans
the ones being punished?
(muffled shouting)
Is this what Yoo Junghyuk
was talking about?
(coins rattling)
Kim Dokja!
I guess that means...
you don't have enough coins
to pay the survival fee!
(announcer): Three minutes until
the Survival Fee payment.
Humans within this district,
prepare for payment.
(Jeong Heewon grunts)
(dramatic music)
(grunting)
One minute until
the Survival Fee payment.
Everyone prepare for payment.
Hey, Heewon!
You need to catch him now!
(grunts)
(thudding)
(laughing)
Why are you so surprised?
It's the barrier!
You must have known you have
to clear the scenario
to pass it.
You killed all the most
monsters at Geumho Station,
except the most
important one.
(grunts)
(panting)
Time's up!
- Wait!
- That reckless gallantry
of yours is always the problem,
isn't it?
And now, it's gonna get you
and your friends killed.
- (bullet whizzing)
- (squelching)
(gunshot echoes)
(groaning)
- (gun clicks)
- Take cover!
(announcer): All monsters
have been neutralized.
The Daily Survival Fee
has now been lifted.
You have cleared
the main scenario.
Who the hell is there?
Whoa, whoa!
What's with the attitude?
I just saved your butts,
shouldn't you all be
thanking me?
(sighs)
Since I killed him,
I'll just take all these.
(coins rattling)
Calm down, I won't hurt you.
I can tell you're just beggars.
(nervous chuckling)
Yes, well, thank you.
Hey, yeah, she looks kind
of terrifying, let's go.
Where are you going?
We need to clear the scenario.
Uh, but didn't we just
clear the scenario?
Thanks again, by the way.
Yeah, but that was
your scenario.
And you just stepped
into my district.
Ah, haha! Oh!
What's going on?
We're blocked again?
Yeah. And just so you know,
the scenario here isn't one
where you band together
and sing kumbaya.
It's everyone for themselves.
Are you guys really
just gonna stand there?
I'd suggest you start running.
(Dokja): Lee Jihye.
(background screaming)
In the novel,
during the first scenario,
when everyone else
was panicking...
(screaming)
Jihye, what are we gonna do?
...Lee Jihye
survived on her own.
(announcer): Day Four of
the Chungmuro Station scenario
is starting. Ten minutes
before the monsters appear.
Green zones will be created.
Take refuge in a green zone
to survive.
Current survivors:
104 people.
Number of Green Zones for today:
52.
Take refuge in a Green Zone.
(chiming)
(suspenseful music)
(all shouting)
Ten minutes left!
If you wanna live,
it's 750 coins per person.
It's safe in here, huh?
Ten minutes left!
There aren't many empty spaces!
Hello, sir. How much
in cash just for me?
The idiot said cash!
Look, buddy!
We don't take cash, huh?
You gotta bring us coins.
Look, I don't have any coins
on me,
but I'll give you as much cash
as you want.
- 20, 30 grand?
- Yeah, no, you gotta
get outta here.
Can't you read the sign, huh?
1 night 1 person, 750 coins
- Goddamnit.
- Please, just take this!
There's a hundred thousand
dollars in here.
- Save it!
- No, please, you gotta take it!
I said no! Now get outta here!
- Please, I swear--
- I said move it!
Hold on a second, hold on.
Where'd you get
a hundred thousand in cash?
- I passed through
Myeongdong Station yesterday.
Some guy was offering
$100 per coin
to anyone who passed.
You never know when the world
might go back to normal, right?
So I exchanged it, just in case.
- (laughing)
- What's so funny?
- That money's from my safe!
- (all laughing)
Idiots like him are the reason
I have so many coins!
The key to survival is adapting.
(laughing)
My God, you don't stand a chance
in this world, do you?
You sad, pathetic little man.
You'll be broke and dead!
(laughing)
(announcer): Intruder detected.
(alarm blaring)
(indistinct shouting)
(rapid gunfire)
Tell me something,
why do the beggars fight so hard
to survive?
What do they wanna live for?
They have nothing!
Ah... We haven't even started!
Are we gonna have to fight
like this every day?
(grunts)
At midnight,
the monsters are all
gonna rush into the station.
You can live if you go inside
the green tiles.
We'll split up
and look for empty spots.
But listen, there may not be
room for all five of us.
If you find a green tile,
protect it at all costs.
That way, at least
one of us will live.
You got that?
(background yelling)
No spaces left
in Chungmuro Station.
If we wanna live, we have
to take someone else's spot.
You're that prophet,
aren't you?
I heard about you from Master.
Since you've managed
to survive this long,
I guess it's working for you.
Yoo Junghyuk, where is he?
He got outta here already.
This scenario is nowhere near
his level, he's too powerful.
Why are you just standing there?
If you're really a prophet,
then you should know
where the bonus green zones
are gonna appear.
What? Too heroic
to just save yourself?
Master wanted me
to tell you this.
He'll take you up on your offer,
but you have
to leave the others,
and survive the night
all alone. Hmm.
What? You can't bear
to just save yourself?
But, but I just told you
what would happen
if you win, huh?
Hey, let's go.
- (bully): Ho-ho!
- (boys laughing)
What did I tell you, huh?
I told you they would do it!
You should give up.
(bully): Every time,
they always act like they won't,
but they do!
That way, at least...
one of us gets to live.
- (all shouting)
- Get out of the way, it's mine!
I got it, I got it!
(suspenseful music)
(electric whirring)
6-1, 6-1.
Okay, so it's five tiles
back from the 6-1 mark.
Dokja!
Dokja, we've looked everywhere,
there are no empty spots.
Gilyeong, over here!
Come on, you must know somewhere
else we can try and look.
(overlapping eerie voices):
Everyone listen up!
I'm Biryu, the Dokkaebi
in charge of this scenario.
You have less
than one minute left,
yet I'm not sure
I feel the urgency.
Are you starting to get tired?
Maybe I should just go ahead
and free the monsters right now.
Raise the tension
in here a little bit.
To those who don't have
a spot yet,
this is your last chance.
(announcer): One minute warning.
Some green zones will vanish,
while other bonus green zones
will appear.
What?
(chiming)
(all shouting)
(dramatic music)
(chiming)
- Dokja, come on.
We need to move right now!
Is... this prophecy as well?
It can't help in this scenario.
At least try for those spots.
If we push them out,
are those people just gonna die?
If you wanna live,
it can't be helped.
Can't we just fight them
like we did before?
How many monsters are there?
Hey! It doesn't work that way.
You'll die if you don't
find a zone!
(announcer): The portal has now
opened, monsters are entering.
(electric whirring)
(creatures snarling)
(screaming)
(grunting)
You need to find a spot.
It's the only way
you'll make it!
What are you all doing?
(blades clink)
(crowd clamoring)
(whimpering)
It just can't end like this.
Wait up, wait!
(panting)
Go towards the portal.
And, over there.
Isn't it more dangerous
down there?
All scenarios are designed
for max entertainment
for the Constellations.
If it's entertaining,
the rules can change.
Green Zones can appear
in the most dangerous places.
(grunts)
Hurry!
(panting)
Dokja better be
sure about this!
(panting)
(electric crackling)
- (creatures barking)
- (blades slashing)
(woman screaming)
(creatures snarling)
(grunting)
I see one!
(Gilyeong): But wait, Mister...
Hey, kid. Please shut up.
You could've stayed
on your square.
- Why'd you come back?
- There's this novel I read
where only the hero survived.
But to be honest,
he was kind of a jerk.
(monster roars)
(music fades)
(silence)
(Dokja): Yoo Junghyuk?
(grunts)
(monsters snarling)
(blade slashing)
Hey, Yoo Junghyuk! Move over!
You don't need a Green Zone.
We do! Come on!
You wanna fight
the Dragon together?
Then this is your test.
Leave the boy and come on in.
Otherwise you both die.
(Green Zones chiming)
(grunting)
Hyeonseong, grab on!
(growling)
(snarling)
(blade slashing)
(growling)
- Gilyeong, stay here.
- What about you?
(monsters growling)
(dramatic music)
(sword scraping)
(growling)
(Dokja): If I eat this,
I'll be trapped
in the Illusory Prison.
- (grunting)
- (creatures growling)
(growling)
Had a feeling...
(panting)
(groaning)
(announcer): The Illusory
Prison has been activated.
(echoing thump)
(ethereal music)
(muffled laughter)
(child): Whoa, he hit him!
Time's running out,
better hurry up!
Come on, let's go, boys!
I wanna see some action!
(sombre music)
(panting)
(grunting)
(whimpering)
(muffled sword strikes)
(somber music continues)
Whoa, stop! Stop!
Stop, hey, I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry!
(bully): Wow, Dokja,
you beat his ass!
(Dokja): Dear author,
Yoo Junghyuk once said,
"I can't help it if others
are sacrificed so I can live."
(whimpering)
Is that the theme of the novel?
Because I can't accept that.
Sir, your novel is the worst.
(heartfelt music)
(teacher): I'm sorry to tell
you that, yesterday,
Minseop died.
We're still trying
to figure out all the details.
But for now, I know it's hard,
but try to focus
on today's mock exam.
(sobbing softly)
(Dokja): Author,
I once caused a friend's death
so that I could live.
In the novel, Yoo Junghyuk
seemed to be telling me
that it's not my fault.
(monster roaring
in the distance)
That it couldn't be helped.
So I cheered for Yoo Junghyuk.
Until I read the ending
of the novel today.
I personally find
this ending terrifying.
And the reason is,
I'm scared it could also
happen to me.
Sir,
I wanted a different ending.
The ending I couldn't have,
where whatever sacrifice
it took,
the hero survived to the end
with his friends by his side.
(Junghyuk): Don't be
ridiculous.
(announcer): Yoo Junghyuk
has activated
the Dream Conversation skill.
- If that's what you wanted,
you would've fought that bully.
I know what you wanna do.
But humans aren't built
that way.
(Dokja crying)
We aren't made to be
heroic and selfless.
I used to think like
you do now.
But after losing
too many friends
in this never-ending hellscape,
it just became easier
to fight alone.
(sighs)
But then...
what do we do now?
Why do you assume
you have to do something?
Remember, Dokja,
you're nothing.
(pained gasping)
(Sangah): His wounds
are too serious,
they're not getting better.
(coughing)
Dokja, are you okay?
I was worried you'd be out
of commission
for the rest of the day.
(soft music)
What happened to everyone?
- What's wrong with Hyeonseong?
- (Hyeonseong): Mr. Dokja.
It's good to see you
up and about.
Hyeonseong pushed himself
too hard.
Sangah also strained herself
trying to heal him.
Are you sure you're really okay?
Yes, but, did we...
Did you fight the monsters
all night?
Because of me?
(distant voices shouting)
- Oh, our time's up.
- (footsteps nearing)
We need to go
to the next scenario.
(Dokja): My friends survived
outside the Green Zones.
- Too tired.
- You need to wake up.
-  - By all working together.
- (Sangah): It's time to go.
(Dokja): Maybe the best way
to clear this scenario...
(Heewon): Hyeonseong
and Gilyeong can't fight today.
You'll need to find two
Green Zones for them,
and we'll hold them off
out there.
But today...
Yoo Junghyuk dies.
(soft tense music)
On the last day of
the Chungmuro Station Scenario,
a Fire Dragon comes out.
Yoo Junghyuk will try
to fight it, and die.
But you told us if he dies,
then this world ends.
Well, to be clear, if the hero
who can save the world dies,
the world will be destroyed
within minutes.
In order to prevent that,
someone else needs
to fight the Fire Dragon.
Well, if that's us...
that would mean one of us
has to die, right?
I'll do it.
And besides,
I'd already be dead
if it weren't for Dokja.
Tell me what I have to do.
(sighs)
No.
There's something else
you need to do, Heewon.
- I have to do this.
- No, no, wait!
Yoo Junghyuk is at
a much higher level than you.
He's in a completely different
league than us.
If a person like him
can't kill it,
then where does that leave you?
(sighs)
You all protected me last night.
You saved my life.
And because of that,
now I see what I need to do.
(announcer): Current number
of survivors, 57 people.
Number of Green Zones
for today...
(Green Zones chiming)
We have an announcement.
(Biryu): Everyone, listen up!
As you know, this scenario's
rule is everyone for themselves.
The concept is survive
on your own.
But last night,
some of you survived
outside of the Green Zones.
By helping each other.
Our dear Constellations
are very upset.
So today,
we'll be raising the difficulty.
(announcer): Current survivors,
57 people.
Number of Green Zones
for today...
one.
- (crowd clamoring)
- (woman): What?
You can't do that!
That's a death sentence
for all of us!
Quiet down!
Today, I'll be deciding
who is worthy
of the single Green Zone.
Who should get it, you ask?
The kindest human?
The most unfortunate human?
Or maybe the smartest human?
But I hear in your world,
the wealthiest reign.
Then let's do that.
(Green Zones chiming)
(announcer): A Green Zone
has appeared.
- If you want to live,
rise up and take this spot.
But even if you do,
there's still only one.
(chuckling)
(tense music)
Hang on a minute.
Jihye! I need your help.
Why would I help you
when I can just take that space?
Work with us. Together,
we can do this, trust me.
(sighs)
If you'd just stayed
in that zone,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
(gun clicking)
Everyone's gonna die now
because you had to play
the hero.
And that's why I need
your help.
Listen, I have an idea.
You just need to help me--
I said no!
You saw who got the Green Zone.
In this world, it's always
the strong who survive,
and it always will be.
(chuckles)
And I think that's great.
It's straightforward and fair.
If you don't wanna die,
then you just have to win.
Isn't it already enough?
That you killed your friend
to survive?
Even as she took
her last breath,
she didn't even lift
a finger to stop you.
I couldn't help it.
(voice shaking): I couldn't
help it.
(grunting)
(crying)
(Dokja): I know
you couldn't help it.
But you also know
what happened
when you tried to survive alone.
(sombre music)
(crying)
(sniffling)
Bihyeong, you there?
Dokja, wow!
Just like you told me,
our channel is absolutely
exploding!
The Constellations
love this story,
and donations are pouring in!
Let's cash in
those donations right now.
How much exactly?
All of it.
(clicking)
(tense music)
When I tell you,
shoot it all out.
Okay, hold on.
Let me convert it.
(crowd clamoring)
Hey, mister!
Yeah, you, Gong Pildoo!
Now what does this bum need?
Any chance you'll do
some work for me?
- What?
- I have an important job
for you. How much do you charge?
I thought you were just
some bum.
I didn't realize you were
also a kook.
How does a hundred thousand
coins sound?
(murmuring)
(chuckles)
That much?
Sure, if you really
have that much,
I'll do whatever stupid job
you want.
Now show me the coins.
Coming right up.
Bihyeong, now.
Here it comes, 113,000 coins!
(announcer): The Green Zone
is being regenerated.
- My spot!
- (Green Zone chimes)
(crowd gasping)
(muffled banging)
(Pildoo): You crazy
son of a bitch! Stop!
Wait, you can't! No!
I'll shoot you!
Go ahead and shoot me then!
(crowd screaming)
I know you couldn't help it.
But you also know what happened
when you tried to survive alone.
(grunting)
- (screaming)
- Get off me! Get off!
(Dokja panting)
(sound fades)
(bullet whizzing)
(ting)
(hissing)
(Dokja panting)
(Pildoo): Hey, you!
What the hell did... damn.
That psychopath really
broke through it!
Out of my way.
Look at me, you bastard!
You destroyed my safe zone.
What're we gonna do now?
(announcer): Monsters will enter
in one minute.
The portal is forming.
(crowd clamoring)
- Listen to me!
- They're coming!
If those Green Zones
didn't exist,
we all would've
fought the monsters.
And maybe we'd have all
made it through.
(tense music)
(electric whirring)
(announcer): 100,000 coins
have been transferred.
- Where are you going?
- I paid you to do a job.
- Keep your word.
- But, but what do I do?
I don't want a single person
here to die.
I counted everyone!
(man): Yeah, you need
to help all of us.
(woman): Right! Let us live too.
- (crowd shouting indistinctly)
- You owe it to us!
Hey, I won't charge you
for today.
So those who want
to fight, fight.
Those who can't,
come on to my land. Hurry!
(electric whirring)
(tense music builds)
(mechanical grinding)
Guess I'm gonna earn a shitload
of coins today.
(announcer): The Constellation
Defense Master
has given emergency defense
to Gong Pildoo.
(engine powering up)
(panting)
Gilyeong and Hyeonseong
can't help us today.
We need to fight for them too.
Do me a favor,
don't die, you two!
(snarling)
(rapid gunfire)
(shouting)
- Suck on that, you scum!
- (shells clinking)
(screeching)
- (blade slashing)
- (grunting)
(rapid gunfire)
(sound fades)
(low rumbling)
- (stone crumbling)
- (deep growling)
(sinister music)
- (roaring)
- (shouting)
- Gong Pildoo!
- Die you little--
I'll take that one.
Keep blocking the entrance.
- Go, quick!
- (growling)
(distant screaming)
(growling)
Yoo Junghyuk! Wait!
(panting)
If you fight, you'll die.
Let me do it.
(monster squeals)
With that sword?
What was it? Four days ago?
When you predicted I'd die?
Watch this.
- (whooshing)
- (creature squeals)
(suspenseful music)
(whirring)
(dragon growling)
(gunfire)
(dragon bellows)
(announcer): There's a human
in this area
with abnormal abilities.
With the unanimous consent
of the Constellations,
the difficulty level
shall now be raised.
(Dokja): What?
(electricity crackling)
(atmospheric music)
(huffing)
(Dokja): This wasn't
in the novel.
(clattering)
- (thudding)
- (groans)
(grunts)
Ah...
(gasping)
Argh!
- (roaring)
- (grunting)
Sangah! Quickly, pull him out!
But then, what about you?
This will keep me safe
from the flames.
(grunts)
- Now!
- (snarling)
- Ahh!
- (growling)
(panting)
- Ah!
- (low roaring)
(grunting)
(panting)
(tense music)
(wings fluttering)
(man): It's massive!
Look at that!
It looks like a mantis!
Gilyeong!
(grunting)
- Gilyeong...
- But what about Dokja?
- (roaring)
(crowd screaming)
- Ahh!
- Gilyeong, stop.
I'm okay. I can do it.
(roaring)
- (coughs)
- Gilyeong, you've done enough.
Stop. Stop it, Gilyeong,
please,
you can't do any more!
Ah!
(breathing heavily)
(announcer): Lee Hyeonseong's
attribute is ready to blossom.
Argh!
- (grunting)
- (energy humming)
(grunting)
Argh!
(ground rumbling)
Sangah!
(panting)
(grunting)
(dragon grunts)
(announcer): Lee Hyeonseong
has activated
Great Mountain Push, level four.
Argh!
(rocks crumbling)
(grunting)
(Dokja): Hyeonseong,
I'm coming! Ahh!
Watch out!
(crowd screaming)
(panting)
(Dokja): Somehow, I'll find
a way to face the Fire Dragon.
But listen to me.
In the dragon's chest,
there's a round shell,
and it has a core inside it.
If we pierce the core,
we'll defeat the Fire Dragon.
But the problem is...
whoever breaks the shell open
isn't gonna make it out of this.
If I'm the one who breaks
the shell and I die,
then Sangah needs to bind
its arms together,
and Heewon's gotta
pierce the core.
If you do kill the Dragon,
you'll receive
a special ability.
One time only,
you can bring someone back
from the dead.
You get what I'm telling you?
We need to trust each other.
That's the only way
it's even possible...
for us all to live.
(intense music)
(panting)
Ahh!
(grunts)
(dragon roars)
(Dokja screams)
(dragon shrieks)
(dragon roars)
(sounds fade)
- (grunting)
- (crackling)
(dragon shrieks)
(shouting)
(tense ethereal music)
Dokja...
(screaming)
Heewon! Now!
(panting)
- (grunts)
- Heewon! Quick!
(grunting)
(soft tense music)
(panting)
(Dokja): The core's shell...
it's reforming.
(clicking)
What do we do now?
(creatures barking)
The only way
to end this fight...
(tense heroic music)
(grunts)
(panting)
(roaring)
(grunting)
(panting)
(Dokja): The core's pierced.
And now Yoo Junghyuk will die.
Just like in the novel.
(roaring)
(flames hissing)
Dokja, what now?
(panting)
(Dokja): The hero is dead.
I...
couldn't do anything to stop it.
(announcer): Activating Yoo
Junghyuk's
Regression skill.
All matter in the present world
will cease to exist.
(soft eerie music)
(panting)
(music fades)
(heroic music)
- Hey, Bihyeong!
Send me the item! Quick!
- But wait! Dokja,
the world is disintegrating!
Just send it!
(music builds)
(energy humming)
(announcer): Broken Faith
has transformed
into an Attribute Weapon.
(Dokja): I still have a chance.
(footsteps thudding)
Hyeonseong!
(thud)
Heewon!
(sword slashes)
Sangah!
(heroic music continues)
(sword rings)
(dragon shrieking)
(announcer): The Green Zone
scenario has been cleared.
10,000 coins paid as a reward.
As an additional reward,
you have received
the King of No Killing.
Kim Dokja revived Yoo Junghyuk
using the King of No Killing.
(soft music)
(Pildoo): We won!
- (distant laughter)
- (indistinct chatter)
Yeah, haha! Ya-hoo!
(laughing)
We took all those bastards down!
(Dokja): Yoo Junghyuk.
(Pildoo laughing)
Are you okay?
(Junghyuk): I didn't think
you could do it.
(indistinct cheering)
(uplifting music)
Whoa, nice work!
We kicked their asses, huh?
(laughing)
(indistinct chatter)
Nice work with that sword,
Dokja.
Guess it wasn't broken
after all.
And Hyeonseong,
your skills were badass.
I only wish
I'd stepped in sooner.
But all of us did great.
(Dokja):
I, who was truly nothing,
lived this story,
and met new friends.
And together, as a team,
we can write a new ending.
(heroic music)
(announcer): A new scenario
is starting.
All of the barriers
have been lifted.
(distant screaming)
(man): Help me!
Somebody help! Help!
Whoa!
Mr. Han?
Watch out! They killed
everyone at Geumho Station!
Even the children
and the elderly,
they killed them!
Don't just stand there, come on!
They're on their way here now!
(train horn blows)
That's them,
they're almost here!
(Dokja): Wait, already?
(whimpering)
(crowd murmuring)
(panting)
They're coming.
They're coming!
(train horn blows)
(sinister music)
(heroic music)
Subtitling: difuze