Then he flipped.
He tried to grab
me, but I ran away.
But then that idiot
chased me down the street
in nothing but his underpants.
I broke the heel on
my shoe running away.
You need to deal
with your daddy issues.
Nothing like that's
happened to me in years
because I worked it out at
my tantric workshop at Goa.
Is it the one
where they heal you with sex?
Will there be
a gang bang in the woods?
That would really
help with your daddy issues.
That's what we're gonna
be working on, right?
The navigator is directing
to the forest. Should I?
Yes, of course, turn.
This is more a Vedic workshop,
so no orgies out here,
but I know some other programs
that might give
you what you need.
Unless you act
like a bitch, of course.
Fuck.
Are we going in the
right direction?
Yes.
So, tell
me what happened.
It seems
pretty obvious to me,
but she won't say.
Let me guess,
"Everything's fine
with me and my husband."
She always
gives me the creeps
with all her, "It's
all good," bullshit.
We all have problems.
They are life lessons.
Mm, bullshit, if
you life to your friends,
you also lie to yourself.
But what's the life
lesson in that?
He kicked her out?
So we are to blame
for what they do?
Well, you're not gonna like
my answer, but in a way, yes.
Listen, you can talk
drivel all you want,
but I'm being serious here
and you keep spouting
all that self-help crap.
So, I have to
pretend to be enlightened?
I'm not a bullshitter,
unlike some people,
but I believe you
that it'll be fun.
- Hmm.
- As long as no one acts
like a wet rag.
I just couldn't
leave her at my place.
She showed up in the
middle of the night crying.
You should be a little
more sympathetic.
So, here we are.
Which way now?
GPS doesn't show Las Govo.
Las Gavo.
You know what? This
is the entry test.
It's a new thing they use
for the advanced trainings.
I've seen it before.
I'm gonna check out
what's on the stone.
What happened?
Oh, morning. Hmm.
Our enlightened friend
brought us to who knows where?
I think she's finally gone nuts.
Look, a dog.
Where?
I don't see it.
Lyuba, don't scare me.
Zoya, there's a
big dog over there.
This is the sign.
We go that way, huh.
Don't you dare call him back.
Sure as hell not before
you tell us what happened.
Nothing.
Come on, Lyuba. The ass
kicked you out, didn't he?
Or worse.
He didn't kick
me out.
I just need a couple days alone.
Sveta, stop pretending
to be the family shrink.
Fate gave Lyuba a chance to
come to this workshop with us.
It's destiny.
Oh, we can ask him.
Hello.
Could you please
tell us how to get
to the village of Las Gavo?
Sveta, I don't like this.
Sveta, let's go. Sveta, Sveta!
Don't yell at me!
Zoya, you never told
us about the zombies.
Okay. I brought a change
of clothes for you.
The bag in the back.
Sweater and shorts.
Thanks.
I really hope, Zoya,
you're not bringing us
to a sectarian retreat.
You need to
work on yourself, Sveta.
Stop resisting the stuff you
can't replace in your life
and embrace everything as it is.
What kind of bullshit
is that? Please.
That's what resistance is.
We'll work through it together.
Fuck.
Fuck, uh, fuck!
Just in time for the
mosquitoes' dinner.
Where the hell are we?
Zoya, are you sure this
is the right place?
There are no signs or anything.
Maybe we should call them.
Uh.
- Let's go back.
Go back?
At night? Uh.
Fuck.
On these dirt roads?
Well, what else
can we do?
I don't know.
We can go back to the village
and ask someone if
there's a motel nearby.
Yeah, good idea. Zoya?
- Hmm?
- Let's go.
- Zoya.
- Hmm.
Okay, let's go back, girls.
It's clear, Zoya,
you've been scammed.
Hey, there.
- Are you going to Las Gavo?
- Yeah, yeah, we are.
Look, ladies, they sent
a boat for us.
Where have you
been? Come on, get in.
Yeah, the transport
is the bomb.
I told you. Everything
is taken care of.
You have to be able to
trust the world.
So, what are we waiting for?
Fuck.
Don't worry, he's harmless.
Now we can go.
I can't see
anything from here.
There is always fog.
Where are we going?
To the island.
And what's
on this island?
People.
Encouraging.
You, you look so sad.
I was watching you and I decided
to come and cheer you up.
Not drinking?
I'd love to, but
I'm driving tonight.
- Pavel Viktorovich,
- Huh.
such a wonderful party.
You always find something
to surprise your guests.
And I want to drink to your
inexhaustible vitality.
You are an example for me.
- And your wife?
- My wife is real angel,
and she lets me
drink 'cause tonight,
she's the designated
driver.
Come on, it's my
birthday. Ha-ha.
Don't be a party pooper.
- I, I've got.
Everyone is drinking.
- I, I've got it, I will,
- Yeah.
I will drive myself. Honey,
um, what can I bring for you?
- I'll go get one myself.
- No, no, no, no.
Sergey, bring this
lady champagne.
Okay.
You are a lucky lady,
in love with a diligent,
driven husband.
I also love him.
I'm considering hiring him
for a federal position.
You could move to Moscow.
Buy a big house...
Oh!
There we are. Go, boy.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
So, this doesn't look
like a retreat center.
Maybe we should go back.
Your fear shows
distrust of the world.
And that's exactly what
we're here to work on.
Don't pretend to be
calm. Middle of nowhere.
Look at this place. We're
in the fucking forest.
Let's go back.
Wait. Wait, we wanna go back.
Please. I'll pay you.
Huh. Great.
The old fart's gone. Uh.
Fuck!
So what do we do now, Zoya?
We'll freeze out here overnight.
It will work out.
Listen, the world
will take care of us.
- Are you fucking serious?
- Yes.
Fuck, you're sick.
You should have checked
into a psych ward
instead of coming
all the way out here.
- Is that so, Sveta?
- What?
You wanted to come here too.
I didn't ask to be
abandoned on an island
in a forest in the middle
of the fucking night.
Maybe that's what you need.
Shut up. What a bitch.
Oh, wolves?
Hey. Hi there.
We're actually here
for the retreat.
Sorry we're late. We
got a little lost.
That's okay.
We were notified that you
were indeed running behind.
You guys are funny
sneaking up like that.
Or maybe it's a part
of the initiation,
scaring the new girls?
Fear changes the
sense of reality.
It's like life is
getting brighter.
- Give me your bags.
-  Oh my.
Thank you.
- I'm Ignat, by the way.
Oh, I'm Zoya. These
our Sveta and Lyuba.
And you are?
- I'm Tikhon.
- Oh, Tikhon.
And yours?
I don't have one.
Is your past too
heavy to carry with you?
This place is gorgeous.
I get it. No electricity,
no unnatural magnetic field.
Sustainable and healthy.
- Be careful.
- Woo!
Wow.
What is this place?
This is Las Gavo.
You mean that
you live here full time?
Of course.
Our people have lived on
this land for over 300 years.
So you
guys are all related?
Almost.
But  you don't
look like a country boy. Hmm.
Well, I studied at the state
university in St. Petersburg.
- For real?
- Yes.
Faculty of psychology.
- And you came back here?
- Yes.
Actually, that was the point.
Um,
if I had to guess, I'd
say you're a lawyer?
No, I'm an accountant.
- All right.
- So, um, mm,
are you the person in charge?
- No.
- Don't worry.
You'll meet him soon.
Okay.
Thank you.
Whoa.
- You're welcome.
- Awesome.
Thank you.
Wow.
All your devices, please.
Oh.
It is so that the outside world
doesn't interrupt
our self-examination.
I see you understand
how the subtle mechanics
of our program work.
- Well, I don't.
How will I manage for three
days without my cell phone?
Sveta, this is digital
detox, and you need it most.
You missed tonight's
opening meeting
in which we introduced the rules
as well as your
fellow participants.
But no worries. We work with
everyone individually here.
- Yeah.
- So if you have
any questions, feel free to ask.
Okay, good.
We'll wake you up
early tomorrow.
Oh, one last thing.
It's best if you stay
inside until sunrise.
- Hmm.
- Goodnight.
Goodnight, Tikhon.
Girls, this is the bomb.
And those guys are so, so cool.
I feel this wave of power and
energy radiating off them.
I wonder how they feed us.
I wouldn't be
surprised if they don't.
- Really?
- Fasting really helps
when on a journey of
self-discovery, mm-hmm.
That sounds more like
a concentration camp,
but with cute guards.
I'd hate to steer
you wrong.
Lyuba, listen,
cut loose a little.
Have some sex, some fun. Relax.
I don't cheat on my husband.
- Come on, Lyuba.
- I just can't do it.
But your personal
happiness is a human right.
- Sveta.
- Hmm?
I sure love you,
but you've always been a slut
and you'll never
change.
I just take
a broad view of life.
- Hmm.
- Look at her.
She suffers.
- Mm-hmm.
What the fuck?
He was hitting on
me. Touching my ass.
- So what?
- It was gross.
So what? He was drunk.
It happens.
Is it so hard to
flirt back?
Why can't you just act
like a regular woman
and not a fucking prude?
Mm!
Jesus Christ. Are you crazy?
Oh my God. Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. There was a dog.
I almost hit it.
-  What fucking dog?
Huh? I'm soaked
now because of you.
You're a pain in the ass.
Are you frozen or
what? Let's go.
Yes. Okay.
Stay in the car.
Regular gas and full tank.
I'm sorry, miss.
Um, are you okay?
- Yes.
- Can I help you?
No, thanks.
Everything's fine, really.
Is this your husband?
You could use this.
Thanks.
I'm sorry, I, I, uh...
I just came out for some air.
Still waters.
What?
Hey. Hey.
- I should probably get back.
- Shh.
Having nightmares.
It will hurt.
Wait.
What did you mean by that?
What, what's going on here?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
What's going to happen?
This is a rite of passage.
Just copy what I do.
Ooh!
Sergey, there's
nothing going on between us.
He's just someone I know.
You've got it all wrong. Okay?
You spent two hours with him.
I'm watching you
for your own safety.
Are you serious?
That's not fair. I have
never cheated on you.
Careful!
Ah!
I don't believe
a word you say, Lyuba?
Not anymore.
And now I know why
you've been so distant
because you're playing around.
I've never cheated on you.
I'm always the one home alone
while you are out working.
How do I know what you're
doing?
Huh!
Look, what a
magical day today.
Look.
You're safe now.
Hmm? Mm.
What are you running from? Huh?
Are you mad at him?
You shouldn't be.
He gave you the
best gift possible.
He set you free.
How do you know?
You would've never
done that yourself.
You should thank him.
I just happened to be here.
A coincidence?
Mm.
Well then the universe
heard your cries
and gave you what you need.
And do you know what I need?
I do.
And what is it?
You decide. Still
water.
Come on.
Oh.
It's amazing, Zoya.
Come on, tough guy.
Wow. I didn't expect
such a mind fuck.
Oh, thank you.
Uh!
I felt like I was back in
the closet my mother hid me in
when she fucked her boyfriend.
Wow, it's amazing.
When we hide things, they
destroy us from the inside.
Yeah, I know.
Sharing gets it
out of our system.
Oh.
Listen, I'm sorry.
Don't
worry about it.
Ooh. Ooh.
Wow.
Yeah, but we all
have different stories.
- Really?
- Mm.
Maybe.
But it made me finally
realize something.
What's that?
I have to leave Sergey.
Hi.
Sergey, let's talk.
Ah, what, what's this?
Sergey, it's not
working between us anymore.
I want a divorce.
So you were lying when
you said you didn't cheat.
No, I didn't.
Nothing happened.
If so, what's all this about?
You and me, it's, it's
not working anymore.
I can't live like this.
I just can't.
Lyuba,
honey, forgive me, please.
I bet you to forgive
me. I'll do anything.
You know that I, I love
you so, so much.
It's just that I am
up to my ears in work.
Chronic stress and sometimes
it gets frustrating,
especially if you
hang out with someone.
Yes, I'm jealous, but how do
you want me to feel about this?
It's not just that.
We've become like
strangers to each other.
- Uh.
-  Please.
Lyuba, my love, please
be patient a little. Hmm?
I'll hand over the project
soon and we'll go on vacation.
Where do you wanna go? Huh?
No. I've made up my mind.
I'm leaving.
- Mm.
I need time to think.
You made up your mind.
You didn't think about me. Huh?
You know, what about
me, Lyuba? Fuck!
And here I am pleading
with you like a fool.
- Sergey, calm down.
- Calm down?
Calm down, Lyuba?
You belong to me.
Do you think I'm just
going to let you go? Huh?
If I have to,
- Please.
I'll skin you from head
to toe, Cheek to cheek.
Let it out.
Scream with your whole body.
Scream with your
body. Let it out.
Feel the energy. Let it out.
Louder.
Ah!
- Ah, ah!
- Ah!
Ah!
Come on. Breathe your fear.
Throw it into he
flames. Let it burn.
- Uh.
- Jump, come on.
- You bitch!
- Uh!
You fucked my husband
and then stalked me!
Are you crazy?
I've never seen you
before in my life.
Don't lie to me, you slut.
What are you doing? Don't
fucking touch her, bitch.
Stop. What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
They've never been here before
and don't know how to
handle the program.
Come here.
Oh, shit.
You scared me.
You were wonderful.
I knew how strong you
were.
What are you talking about?
I attacked that
woman back there.
I have to apologize.
Mm.
How you burned in the fire.
You should just stop thinking.
Let go of your old thoughts.
Stop thinking?
I can hardly keep myself
together as it is.
I don't understand what
the hell's going on here.
It's your new self.
Stop it.
You just need to accept it.
Accept what?
You mean to be an evil bitch?
Or worse?
To be a strong,
beautiful woman
- Mm.
- who is admired
and loved.
A woman
- No.
who creates her own destiny
and who decides for
herself what she needs
and desires.
Lyuba, fuck.
What are you doing?
Stay in the car.
Let's figure out what we can do.
Invitation only? Your
car needs to be fixed too.
You know?
Yeah, so look, could
we, of course this,
let's, let's just stay calm,
but I could use some cash
to cover the damages.
What's blind to,
what's blind to the eyes
but known to the heart,
mirrored deep inside and
kills you, pressure it.
The secret of life is
not freedom, but death.
Still waters run deep.
Still waters run dry.
An the air, it stings.
Still, the still will rise,
still waters run deep.
- Stop.
- Still waters run dry.
- Are you crazy?
- You're extending still-
- What's going on?
Please, let me go!
Do you hear me?
Let me go!
Please. I'll do
whatever you say.
- The fears from your chest.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- I can be strong.
You see? I, I can be strong.
The fears from your chest.
Safe travels.
Wait.
Please! Don't leave
me here!
Don't leave me alone! Please!
Don't leave me alone! Fuck!
Let me out!
Please!
Please.
A
crease, you dumb idiot!
Do you even know what that is?
I want a proper crease in
these pants and I need it now.
I
couldn't get them last night
because you fell asleep in them.
You dare to talk back
to me? You silly bitch!
I feed you, put a
roof over your head,
and you can't learn to
iron a pair of pants?
Kolenka, please.
They're clean.
I, I just have to do...
Shh.
Move!
The range of our
thoughts and actions
is limited by what we
are unable to notice.
To change this, you need
to see what you cannot see.
Mm.
Really? What are you doing here?
I'm happy you agreed
to come, but seriously,
you have to control yourself,
even if you see things.
You don't understand.
He's doing something to
me.
He's a lunatic.
He buried me in the
ground.
Zoya, we have to
get out of here.
Why is everything
always a problem with you?
Why did I drag you with me?
Seriously, you're
always in some crisis
that we try and help you with.
And now the guru is
wasting his time on you.
Can't you just be patient
and behave yourself?
Or maybe you just
like the attention.
Everyone thinks they
know what I need. Hmm?
But I want to do what I
think is best for me. Okay?
Listen, can you
just do what he asks?
Stop trying to save me.
I'll take care of
this myself, okay?
Wow. Look at you.
Unless you're going
to swim across that lake,
you're here till it's done.
And you can thank me
when it's all over.
Mm.
Mm. So she took
her cell phone, huh?
So where is she?
But it isn't part
of your program.
You may need to push harder.
Ah, come on.
Where could she go?
It's an island. Let her
breathe for a while.
She'll be back by tomorrow.
Sveta, Sveta.
Is it you? Wake up, wake up.
Do not go
gentle to that good night.
Shit. Dammit.
The wise
men know dark is right.
They do not go gentle
into that good night
Rage against the
dying of the light.
These are
all nice and tight.
Mm. No one's ever got
out on their own before.
I don't like it either.
We need to find her.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ah.
Oh, yeah. She's almost ready.
So, what's next?
Huh.
Every life and every death is
one of a kind, itself unique.
Another world beside you stands,
but in darkness, hard to see.
May hide...
- Sveta, Sveta.
- But life reveals...
Wake up.
Oh my God. Please.
- Sveta.
- He's close.
- Sveta, snap out of it.
- He's almost here.
Please, help me!
- Who is?
- The child.
- Please.
- My baby is almost here.
- What?
What are you talking about?
You're not pregnant,
Sveta. Look at me.
Look at me.
- I can feel him inside me.
- Where?
- I know it's here.
- Look, look.
Your belly's flat. Listen,
you're not pregnant, Sveta.
It's all good.
I swear to God, Lyuba.
I can feel him inside me.
It's gross. It's inside.
I don't know how he did it,
but he wants me to,
to give birth to his son!
- Shh, shh, shh.
He did it somehow, I can
feel it in my womb, I swear.
It's true. He's evil,
destroy everything.
- Sveta, it's not, shh!
- I don't want his child!
It's not real. Listen to me.
It's all in your mind.
- No.
They gave us something
and we're all hallucinating.
Wake up. Wake up.
Look at me. It's gonna be okay.
Everything's fine.
Here, it's Lyuba.
Look at me.
- Oh my God.
- Shh, be quiet.
What have they done to
us?
Fucking... Oh, fuck.
Fucking psycho. Oh my God.
Oh my God. We have
to get the cops.
- Yes.
- All of us.
- Yeah.
- Those bastards.
They'll lock them up.
- Shh, be quiet, please.
We'll call them. Of course.
What about the others? We
can't leave them behind.
I saw at least 10 other
people buried to their heads.
Listen, I'll try to find her.
I think, I think I know
where they keep our phones.
I can go and and get them.
I'll try to get them.
And do you, go to the
room and get the car keys.
Okay? We'll all
meet at the pier.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Stay away from me!
It works, doesn't it?
It makes you feel so
alive. Look at you.
You burn like a flame.
Are you mad? You
buried me alive.
A wild dog nearly
ate my fucking face!
This isn't therapy,
it's torture!
You can't do that to people.
A little bit, you can.
But you should have asked me.
Would you have agreed?
Oh, fuck.
Ah!
Ah! Uh!
How can I...
Where am I?
How?
I...
Wow, aren't you restless?
Oh, come on.
Lay down, lay down, lay down.
Why is it that you make
yourself so ugly on the outside?
Biting your lips,
cutting your arms.
Find beauty inside and you
feel beautiful outside.
Fuck.
Sveta, Sveta.
Sveta, it's me.
It's me, Sveta. Are you okay?
-  It's back.
- What's wrong?
I knew it was real. I knew it.
- Shh.
- The baby is coming.
- Fuck!
I'll get you
out of here. Okay?
Do you have the keys?
Ah, fuck!  Yes.
- Okay, let's get outta here.
- Yeah, okay.
But Zoya put them in her
purse. She took them.
You went running
and then we get off.
There's no boat.
There might be another pier.
Let's follow the shoreline.
Let's go. Let's go, Sveta.
Oh, fuck, fuck, here.
- Oh my...
Shh, Sveta!
She's not here.
What's next?
Let's check the other pier.
Okay.
Did you read anything
else interesting?
"In Xanadu did Kubla Kahn
a stately pleasure-dome decree,
where Alph, the
sacred river ran.
through measureless
caverns to man
down to a sunless sea."
- Oh my God!
- Ah!
Oh, fuck!
Lyuba, where are you going?
When you overcome your fear,
you will know who you are.
You can't hide from it.
Lyuba.
Zoya. Zoya.
Uh!
Sergey.
Uh! How did you
get here so fast?
Lyuba, what do you mean?
Where are we? Huh?
Uh, who the fuck are you? Huh?
You understand
this is kidnapping?
You know who you are
messing with? Huh?
Talk.
What? Who are you?
You're the boss here? Huh?
Not to me. To her.
He asked you to talk. So talk.
- Did you plan all this?
- What?
Uh, had these thugs
bring me here in a hood
just to talk to you?
- No.
- Huh?
- No, no, no, no, no.
I, I have nothing
to do with it. Okay?
They're all insane. They
won't let me go either.
But you did ask for it, right?
I guess you're their
little bitch in heat, huh?
What? Me?
I'm not the one who
fucks whatever he can.
What did you say? Huh?
You heard me.
I saw you on the boat
with that woman. Okay?
And I'm sure she's
not the only one.
Shut your, shut
your fucking mouth!
- Get your hands off me!
- Mm!
I'll show you who's the boss.
Suffer. Suffer.
I'm so tired of all your
bullshit.
I'm bruised all over,
and my head, my
head is killing me.
Sergey.
Oh my God!
It really happened.
But it was, it was Sergey.
You saw it! You were here!
I'm really sorry,
but we're not here.
We just found you.
You, you! What
have you done to me?
Huh? Did you give me
something to drink?
And everything is
just a hallucination?
Tell me this is not real!
- Shh, shh!
The forest is very wild
here. There are runaways.
But you did the right thing.
- No.
- You defended yourself.
No! It was not me.
You, you did all of this.
You, you were messing
with my head, right?
You, you just...
- Lyuba, shh.
Right now, it's like in a
swamp. Do you understand?
Most important thing
right now is not to rush.
Otherwise, you can
get stuck and drown.
So you relax, get
back to your senses,
and then you and me together
decide what to do next.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay. All right.
Okay, fine.
Yes, you're right.
I did the right thing.
It was justified, right?
I don't feel good.
I haven't done, I couldn't.
- That's it, what a good boy.
Huh?
I couldn't. No.
You can't let
her go unfinished.
If we do, she will
make a fuss for sure.
If the authorities
find out about us,
they'll shut us down and the
entire village would vanish.
I'm just not
capable of doing that.
I'm not built that way.
Try to remember.
Move to Moscow.
If you try anything
or cause trouble,
I'm sure the prosecutor's
office will be interested
in the kickbacks
that Sergey pays you.
Mm!
Uh!
Stop!
Don't do this!
Don't!
Uh!
Sveta, Sveta, come here.
Sveta.
Hurry up.
Lyuba.
Oh, Lyuba. I'm so
glad to see you.
A lot has happened to me.
I found the keys and I think
I know where the boat is.
If we go now, we have
enough time to get away
before they find us, let's go.
I don't want to anymore.
Listen, he helped me
discover who I really am.
- You've been drugged again.
- No.
Brainwashed.
Our fears laid bare
in front of our eyes,
but if you face them.
I gave birth and
it was beautiful.
No, you didn't give
birth, Sveta. No!
- Please, please trust me,
- No, don't touch me!
- and everything will be fine.
- No, let go of me.
It's all for your own good.
He can help you if
you let him inside.
No!
You can't do it
by yourself. Please.
She's over here in the forest.
Ah!
Daddy needs to
calm down. Come on.
Let's play a little bit.
My little baby, come on.
Come on, my little baby.
I told you, let's play.
Daddy needs to calm down. It
was a very, very hard day.
Be a good girl. Come
on, here to play.
Come on, please? Lyuba, please?
I don't wanna live anymore.
That's it!
I can't take it anymore!
This is some kind of nonsense.
Why are we going along with her?
What do you think of yourself?
The queen of the ball or what?
Zoya, you have to
be more merciful.
Sveta, are you kidding?
Or did you lose your mind?
Now you're being
judgmental. I say what I feel.
- What?
- Listen.
Did you actually
just tell me this?
You've got spiritual pride
and this is a direct
path to ignorance.
Did you fucking
forget who brought you here?
And I am very grateful
to you for this.
I don't feel alone anymore.
- What?
The way I see it, you want
more attention from him.
Are you fucking
teasing me, bitch?
Please, your pride,
you need to work it out.
Fuck you, bitch!
No.
No. No, stop it!
No! Stop it!
Please, no!
I don't want this.
Stop it, please!
No!
What the fuck
is going on here?
Get away from her. Get back now.
Lyuba, come here.
Sergey. Are you really here?
Really? Who the hell are they?
They're crazy. Drugged me up.
- Hmm?
- I'm so glad to see you.
- Let's get out of here.
- Lyuba, please don't do this.
You're almost free.
Shut up! Anyone moves
a muscle and you're dead.
I said, don't move. You're dead.
Let's get out of here.
It's okay, Lyuba. Let's go.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
Thank you. You saved
my life.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming.
You can't imagine what
I've been through here.
They fed me something.
Hallucinations all day.
They tried to burn
me at the stake.
Why the hell
did you come here?
Zoya brought me.
Didn't I tell you
she's a fucking moron?
But you never listen.
Always get into fucked
up shit like this.
The most lunatic was the guru.
He's dangerous. He hypnotized
us and made us do things.
Ah, I'll make sure he
regrets screwing up my woman.
And the worst, I'm
not sure about it,
but maybe I killed someone.
No, I'm serious.
It felt so real.
What?
Lyuba, I spent three days
dealing with your fuck ups.
My boss, the car
wreck,
I called in a lot of favors
to make it all go away,
and now you tell me
you killed someone?
Lyuba, goddammit,
what's wrong with you?
Why are you always
fucking up my life?
Killed someone.
It's too much,
Lyuba. It's too much.
I'm not the one
who beats his wife.
So what? It's your own fault.
You should have told me.
About what? It was nothing.
He's a psychologist and
he wanted to help me.
Help with what?
Massaging your pussy, huh?
I was going to kill myself.
Oh, bullshit.
Don't be so dramatic.
I've put up with
something my whole life,
and not just you
and all your shit.
My mother told me, "You have
to suffer to survive, Lyuba."
And that's how I've
lost my will to live.
I provide for you.
I give you everything.
You never worked a
day in your life.
Maybe it's me who's had to
put up with you. Please.
Honey, shut your mouth and
let's go home.
Uh!
Let's go.
Lyuba.
Lyuba, get in the car.
- No.
Listen, you ungrateful bitch.
I didn't drive four hours
to the middle of nowhere,
listen to your bullshit,
get in the car.
Don't touch me. No!
Listen to you.
Now get in the goddamn
car or I swear,
you can ride home
in the trunk, hmm?
I'll never get in
that car with you again.
You ungrateful slut.
I'll shoot you like a
rabid dog.
Huh?
I'll kill you. Huh, huh?
We part in peace.
Let's swim.
I'll never make it.
Okay, we'll get the boat.
Lyuba!
No, no!
No!
Please, look at me.
Don't close your eyes, please.
Please stay with me, Danila.
Danila, I need you.
I need you, I really do.
I can't do it in my own. Please.
You're struggling, you
can do whatever you want.
You don't need me.
No, don't.
Please.
I will, I will watch over you.
No, please. No.
No, no, please. Please,
please don't close your eyes.
No.
Lyuba!
Huh! Lyuba!
Huh!
Step away.
Step away. I said, step away.
Don't come near me!
I don't give a fuck!
You're weak! Just
like your father was!
Uh, but I swear, I'll make you
a real man
if it's the last thing
I ever do!
I prayed.
Hi, Dad.
I know, it's been too long.
I'm coming to visit you.
Yeah, tonight. See you.