I forgot my ID card.
Dad, just a minute.
Where is your attention?
Mom, can you bring my ID card?
I forgot it.
- Yes.
- In getting ready.
Hey, get out of there.
It's my turn.
- Anaya.
- Get down!
Take this, quick.
Mom, ask her to get out,
I won't sit in the back seat.
- Anaya, make it fast!
- Vivek!
But it's getting late.
Jiya, get back.
Jiya, move back! It's getting late.
No one will sit in the front.
It's not fair,
I was the first to sit there.
Go inside. Cry-baby.
- What are--
- Go inside.
- Get in from that side.
- Jiya, stop it, go inside.
Why are you making a fuss?
It's getting late, make it quick.
What is this chaos every morning?
You just relax. Now drive calmly, okay?
Bye.
- Bye.
Don't tolerate anymore, I'm warning you.
If she raises her hand,
then you raise your hand too.
If she pushes you, push her back.
The more you fear people,
the more they'll try to scare you.
Look at me.
If you return from school again
after getting beaten
I'll come to your school
and teach her a good lesson.
Are you listening?
Hey! Are you listening or not?
Yes, Mom.
Nice. You can raise your voice
in front of me.
But out there, you're scared.
Your bus is here.
Bye.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Bye, Dad.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Hi.
In my confusion of turning left or right
the boy behind me
got so confused and frustrated.
He was like, "Hey!
What is wrong with you?
Where do you want to go?"
And I was like, "To my home."
- Seriously.
- What?
Yes, you should have seen his face.
I was just staring at it.
O Lord Hanuman,
may I always remain your servant.
May you always reside in my heart.
O Son of Wind,
you are the destroyer of all sorrows.
May Lord Rama, Laxmana and
Mother Sita dwell in my heart, always.
Hail Lord Hanuman.
Please stay with me forever.
- Quick, quick, quick.
- Why do you always rush?
There is no point in reciting
the Hanuman Chalisa so fast.
Can we leave now?
It's getting late, quick.
Wake up early then. You have
to wake up just 15 minutes earlier.
You always start your day in a rush.
You are late in getting dressed,
you are late for breakfast,
you even pray in a rush.
Stop lecturing me, drive faster.
What kind of language is this?
From where have you learned all this?
Does your school teach you such behavior?
Dad, focus on driving fast.
Or else, they'll close the gates.
- Sir, please move ahead.
- Yes, sure.
Please move ahead.
Shreya, wait for me.
I'm standing right here, come here.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, dear.
Yes. Two minutes.
Move ahead.
Don't just stand there.
Clear the way ahead.
Do you get paid for doing nothing?
What can I do
if these parents don't understand?
What a nuisance.
Hello, mister.
Move back, sir.
Yes, go back a little.
Go from here.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, dear.
Mister.
Thank you, Uncle. Bye.
- Bye.
- Go on...
Listen.
Go straight to your class.
Once school is over, I'll be waiting
right here to pick you up.
And if I see that worthless guy
anywhere near you
then he will face my wrath
and so will you.
Dad, lower your voice.
Here I am, sending you to a school
I can hardly afford, and you...
Sorry, Dad.
Just... be careful.
What if something goes wrong?
Go now.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, dear.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, come on.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- No way you're winning.
Listen, I forgot to do my homework.
- What?
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- What is she up to?
- Should I kick her hard?
She bumped into me.
Pass the ball, this side.
Pass it, pass it fast.
Pass it this side, fast...
- Yes, yes.
- Yes!
- Come on! Come on, girls!
- Yes, yes, pass, pass.
Very good, very good.
Come on, yes.
- Come on, girls...
- Yes! Oh, no...
Very nice, girls.
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning.
Sorry, ma'am.
Victory, victory...
Victory to thee...
Open it quick.
Thank you.
- Hey, bro!
- Hey! Same, buddy! What's up?
- Oh, shit, shit...
- Oh, sorry, sorry...
- Sorry, sorry...
- It's okay, I will manage.
- I will manage, buddy.
- I am so sorry.
So sorry, buddy.
We are always late because of you.
Look how long the queue is.
Yes, but we can go now.
- Now, stand in the long queue.
- Oh, God.
Why don't you say anything?
Her glasses...
The food on Saturday was also really
awesome, absolutely fantastic.
What happened?
That's my birthmark.
Mm-hmm! Chandni.
That's my name.
Hmm, right.
So, Saturday is confirmed, right?
Yes, yes, it's confirmed.
Will you come?
- Yes, I'll come.
- It's confirmed for both of us.
It didn't break,
but it got really messed up.
- Sorry, ma'am.
- Move from here.
Everything got messed up.
There are bruises all over.
My spoon is broken,
give me another one.
Sure.
- Thank you.
- It's always something or the other.
Now there's this extra
hospital expense too.
Feels like it's never-ending.
Hey, I'll try too. Shit!
- Hey, man!
- Your turn is up.
I'll beat you up now.
No way, Agamya.
Hey, but it's Agamya's turn now.
Come on, just do it.
Come on...
Keep the plate aside.
Come on.
Is this how you follow me?
Get up and go.
You go.
I told you, I won!
So many plates are left.
What happened to these girls?
Why have they all gone silent?
- Oh, no!
- What happened to you?
What is wrong, dear?
- What is happening to you?
- What happened?
You ten girls, get up.
Start saying your names.
Avni.
V-Vaani.
S-Shivani.
Kanan.
V-Vidhi.
Vidya
Kinjal.
Vaishali.
R-Ruchi.
Anaya.
Good! Now you all have to do
exactly as I say. Okay?
- Okay, sir.
Do you all have a watch?
Yes, we do.
- Good.
- Who are you?
How did you come here?
I hope it's okay with you, ma'am.
It's only for tomorrow.
Only then can I leave a bit early.
From the day after, it will be as it is.
No problem at all.
I'll take the last lecture.
Thank you, ma'am.
Where are the girls?
No, no, no...
Hey, girls! Get down from there!
Bimal, Ashok, Kishan.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am, look, her head is injured!
Hurry!
But how did she fall down?
Oh, God!
Look, ma'am! Look!
Her head is wounded.
She's bleeding profusely, ma'am.
Just look at her condition!
Hey, girls! Ma'am, look up there
and talk to them.
Come down!
Look here, ma'am.
Girls! What are you doing?
Go back!
Ma'am! Please save us, ma'am.
Ma'am, we don't want to die.
I am coming,
I am coming, I am coming.
Ma'am, if you come any closer,
we have to jump.
- Ma'am, please don't come upstairs.
- Don't come!
- Ma'am, I don't want to die.
- Ma'am, don't come closer.
Don't do anything stupid!
Just stay there, I am coming.
Somebody, call an ambulance!
Call the police quickly!
- Ma'am, don't come upstairs!
- Please don't come upstairs!
Quick, quick.
Ma'am, don't come closer!
Ma'am, please stay away.
Stop! Stop right there!
Or I will jump.
- Girls, what are you doing?
- I will jump.
Ma'am, stay away,
or else I have to jump.
Ma'am, that guy told us
that we have to jump from here
exactly at 3 o'clock.
Ma'am, don't come close.
Please...
Please, I don't want to die.
Who are you talking about?
Ma'am! I don't want to die, ma'am!
- Then please come down, dear.
- No, ma'am!
Even if you come to save us,
we still have to jump.
Oh, what do you mean?
Just come down.
- No, no, ma'am!
- Please don't come closer.
Then you come down.
Ma'am, we have to do
what that guy said.
I don't want to die, ma'am.
No need to jump to death.
I'm here, just come down.
No, we have no choice
but to listen to him.
Who is he?
Whose instructions do you have to follow?
Enough! Enough, Ruchi!
Come down, everyone.
Ma'am, please stay away.
Don't listen to anyone, please come down.
Think about your parents.
Mom, Dad...
Girls, listen to me.
Girls! Listen to me!
Listen! Listen!
I'm coming to you.
Let's talk.
No, ma'am...
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, God! What should I do?
Girls, I am warning you!
Come down, everyone.
No! Ma'am, please.
Please! I beg you, please!
Come down everyone.
Vaishali, come down.
I can't, ma'am.
That guy said so.
You don't have to listen to him.
Ma'am, please move away,
we have to listen to him.
Who is he, Anaya?
Anaya!
Janardan, go away.
You killed her! You killed her!
Ma'am, leave him!
Let go of him! Let go of him!
I shouldn't have gone closer.
Ma'am...
The traders could not fill this
form on time,
so Vadodara traders have
requested the deadline
to be extended until 30th May.
Ten girls ended their lives
by jumping off a school rooftop.
The girls who committed suicide
were only 18 to 19 years old.
The school term had just begun,
no exams had been conducted yet,
and hence, no results were announced.
So the question is, when there was
no academic pressure on these students,
what could be the reason
behind this mass suicide?
The parents are in shock.
And after watching the CCTV footage,
the police administration is stunned.
Those who witnessed this incident
with their own eyes,
like the teachers
and the principal there,
keep repeating the same thing.
The girls kept repeating the same thing.
"We have to do it
because that guy told us to."
"At 3 o'clock, we have to jump."
If anyone tries to stop us, we will jump.
I begged them, I tried my best,
but my girls jumped in front of me...
- Please don't push.
- Please listen to me.
Don't push, try to understand.
Five minutes, stay calm.
Please stay calm.
Please try to stay calm.
- Please try to understand.
- Let us through!
- Hello.
- Hello...
Hello! Mr. Keshav...
Sir, we can no longer control this.
The parents are getting anxious.
Raghu, listen.
There is blood all over here.
It's a horrific sight.
The parents cannot stand it.
So control them.
- But, sir, the parents are not listening.
- Wait.
All the other girls sitting in the canteen
are very quiet right now.
Where is the principal?
She is not in a position to talk,
she is right there.
Listen, until the dead bodies
are moved out of the school
don't open the door.
- No one should enter until I say so.
- But, sir...
Hold them back somehow, Raghu.
Ma'am, tell me in detail.
Ma'am, you are a witness to the incident.
Please understand what's happening.
Just calm down for five minutes.
Let it pass, let it pass.
What's in the ambulance?
Please, for five minutes.
Please, please, calm down.
Please calm down.
Yes, we are investigating the scene.
We are concerned about
your daughters as well.
Hey, Pratap! Hey, Pratap!
Get up, open your eyes!
Hey, Pratap...
How many more like you are there?
How many others know this craft?
Enchantment!
How many others know
this craft of enchantment?
Hey! Hey! You are laughing!
Stop laughing.
Do you know him?
I came back after cleaning my uniform.
And when I saw it,
the canteen was completely quiet.
All the girls were scared.
And they were crying.
Watching them, I got scared too.
I didn't understand anything,
so I hid myself in the bathroom.
Did you see any unknown person there?
No.
Stop crying
and answer the questions I ask.
The girls on the rooftop
were talking about some man.
Have you seen that man?
Look at me and answer!
- No...
- Sir!
Ma'am, why did they jump?
- Please don't cry--
- I must talk to all the girls right now.
Please, come with me.
Mr. Keshav!
Please don't cry.
Sir, not a single CCTV is working
since this morning
other than the compound one.
Bring the surveillance people to me.
- Okay, sir.
- Ma'am, let's go.
Don't cry, nothing will happen.
Ma'am, just look
at what's happened to everyone.
- No one is saying a word.
- Ma'am, please come over here.
Listen.
Girls, there's no need to panic.
Alright? Calm down.
I will just ask you a few questions,
and once you answer them,
you can all go home.
Okay? There's nothing to be afraid of.
- Girls!
- Everything is fine.
- S-Sir...
- Girls...
Sir, I want to tell you something.
- What happened?
- Yes, tell me.
That guy has asked me
to give you a message.
Who is that?
Who are you talking about?
One minute, ma'am.
What is the message?
You have to find Mr. Pratap.
Who is Mr. Pratap?
I don't know.
He just told me
that I have to share this message
with some senior police officer.
Where is the guy
who gave this message?
- I can't say that.
- Why?
Why can't you say it?
No, I was told not to say anything else.
What else did he tell you?
And who is this person you are obeying?
- One minute, ma'am...
- What has happened to them?
- I don't understand.
- Don't cry, dear.
You just jumped because he said so?
You aren't talking to anyone
because he said so.
What has happened to all of you?
Ma'am, be quiet!
Let me talk to her!
No, sorry, sorry.
Please don't cry. Sorry.
Has he asked you to convey
any other message?
If Mr. Pratap is not found,
the whole city will suffer.
The ten girls who jumped off
the rooftop was just the beginning.
Sir, please find Mr. Pratap quickly.
Until Mr. Pratap is found,
all of this will continue.
Please find him quickly.
Girls, I've given the first message.
Now you can start.
Girls, girls, stop. Oh, oh, wait!
Girls...
What are you doing! Just stop!
You will get hurt, talk to us...
Girls, what are you doing?
Girls, where are you going?
Stop running!
Where are you all going? Stop, girls...
Are you okay?
Keshvi, my child...
Raghu Nandan, catch them fast.
- Vitthal.
- Yes, sir!
Take a photo of any one girl
and inform the control room
to send that photo to all
the police stations across the city.
Any girl in this school uniform
seen anywhere in the city
must be caught immediately.
There are around 40 to 50 girls.
Deploy the "She Team" from anywhere
in the city to the school immediately.
Deploy lady constables in the canteen area
and forces outside.
Turn the school into a fortress.
Not a single girl should
leave the premises.
I want ambulances, fire brigade,
everything on standby. Hurry up!
Right away.
Whatever this is, it's very terrifying.
Oh, ma'am...
Mummy...
Hey, you! Go away.
A fearful atmosphere has
spread across the city today.
The administration
has made a special appeal,
urging people to stay away from
girls wearing this school uniform.
The areas surrounding
J.N. Girls' School have been sealed off.
And the police have advised all
citizens to remain inside their homes.
The reason is that
the facial expressions of these
students are extremely terrifying,
and utterly savage.
And on top of that, their screeches,
their red, bloodshot eyes
and their physical aggression.
And due to their anger,
they are behaving uncontrollably.
These students have created a horrid
and terrifying atmosphere
in the city in broad daylight.
These students don't even
recognize their own parents.
Whether the cops come to stop them
or their own parents try to intervene,
these students are
attacking them lethally.
When the witnesses present there
were interrogated,
they believe that
these girls
are possessed or taken over
by some mental illness.
These witnesses have also captured
some videos on their phones,
which are currently
trending on social media.
After much effort, the police have
managed to capture
a few of the girls
and have taken them
to a safe location.
But around 150 students
are still inside the school.
And tight security arrangements
have been made for their safety.
These students have also
attacked the staff
and teachers inside the school.
The injured individuals have been
moved to the hospital for treatment.
However, there has been
no official statement yet
from the police
or from the administration.
But upon investigating inside,
it was discovered
that in order to find a "Mr. Pratap",
these girls are behaving like this.
Who is this Pratap? No one knows.
The police and the administration
are rushing
to stop this unimaginable incident.
Sir, what is happening here?
I don't understand anything.
It seems from the girl's behavior
that someone is controlling them.
I can't tell what's true
and what's false, sir.
This is the first time I'm seeing
such a case in my life.
The girls are doing all this
upon some guy's orders.
They are not ready
to go with their parents.
to talk to anyone.
There's only one girl who talks to me,
but all she keeps saying is,
"Find Pratap."
But who is this Pratap?
I have no idea, sir.
- Sir, I will keep you updated.
- Riti, come with me.
Let's go home.
Leave me, Dad!
Just go! Go, go.
- Riti!
- Riti, my dear.
- Riti, calm down.
- What did you do to my daughter?
That's it, just stay quiet.
- Sir, sir, please...
- My daughter!
Sit.
Sir.
We're also trying to understand
what's happening here.
All parents, listen to me carefully.
You all stay with your daughters,
talk to them calmly,
try to make them understand,
but don't force them.
What happened on the rooftop
this morning...
You all are aware of it.
The girls who left from here,
the way they ran away...
I saw their furious side.
And what did they do after going outside?
You all know that too.
So parents, calm yourselves first
and then talk to your daughters.
Try to make them understand
and please don't pressurize them.
Sir, you have only five minutes left.
Please find Mr. Pratap quickly.
W-Why five minutes? Why?
What's going to happen
after five minutes, dear?
Sir, you can't even imagine
how bad this will get.
Please find Mr. Pratap quickly.
- Sir.
- Later.
We will find Mr. Pratap soon,
don't worry at all.
- Sir...
- Whoever it is
ask them to call later.
No, you don't cry, dear.
We will find him.
- It's not a phone call.
- Then what is it?
Sir, him...
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
But he knows the location
of the person we are looking for.
Pratap is with me.
Who are you?
I have kept him alive.
Didn't that guy say
what to do next
once Pratap is found?
Who is this Pratap?
What is happening?
You tell us, look at the condition
of these girls.
Look at the parents.
What has happened to them?
Enchantment.
These girls are under his enchantment.
And the one making them do this...
is a monster.
He is wicked.
The more you all feel sad,
cry out,
and suffer...
The more he will enjoy it.
He just has to speak
and your daughters will have to do it.
And they will do it for sure.
No one can stop him.
Whoever tries to stop him...
No matter who they are,
they will pay a price.
They will look at you helplessly
and will scream from within.
"Mom, Dad, save me..."
But you won't be able to do anything.
You will just watch them suffer.
These people are already scared.
Don't scare them any more.
I'm telling you the truth.
You are so shaken after watching this.
But I have seen something much worse.
Terrifying beyond your imagination.
I have experienced it.
Who are you?
What is happening here?
If you know anything, please tell us
how this can be stopped.
It can't be stopped.
- No one can stop it.
- It can be stopped.
It can be stopped.
You said that Pratap is with you.
Then you bring Pratap here,
everything will stop.
Dear, when Mr. Pratap comes here,
all this will stop! Right?
Speak up.
Yes, but where is Pratap?
Who is Pratap?
He is also a monster.
He's with me.
But first, I need to meet the monster
who is making all this happen.
But where is he?
No one knows anything.
I'm trying to talk to this girl,
but she doesn't say anything
about where he is.
He is here.
Girls, what happened?
He has been keeping an eye
on all these girls.
I am that monster.
Seems like you are well acquainted
with dear Pratap.
Right?
Give me five minutes.
Let me finish talking to them first.
Then we'll talk...
Okay?
Five minutes.
Here, there, everywhere...
I am present.
For your daughters, I am everything.
And yes, I'm the one responsible
for what has happened to them.
Right?
Are you getting angry?
Feel like hitting me?
Don't even think about it.
If I get even a single scratch
your daughters won't spare you.
They will tear you apart,
rip you to pieces.
And in that frenzy,
they will destroy themselves too.
They will burn themselves to death.
If anything happens to me,
you will die in flames, right?
Yes.
Good. So stay away from me.
Okay?
You too step back.
Take these people outside.
Get them out. Stay away.
I told you what to do
once Pratap was found, didn't I?
S-Sorry, sir.
I had forgotten.
I couldn't remember anything.
- Hey!
Take your hand off,
or she will go up in flames.
Get back, get back.
Don't get angry, okay?
Or I'll lose my temper.
Let's go, girl, come on...
- Isha, no.
- Isha, no! Dear, no.
- Isha, no. Listen to me.
- You don't need to do anything.
Who has the knife
that was taken from here?
- I have it, sir.
- Come here.
You don't worry, dear.
Give it to her.
- No, no! What are you doing?
- Move aside, cut your wrist.
Let it bleed.
You forgot it, is that okay?
- No, Isha!
Now whoever touches you,
slash them...
You just move aside.
Move...
And listen, if anyone tries
to save you now
slash your wrist a few more times.
Slash, slash, slash.
Isha!
- Isha, please listen to me.
- Isha, please.
My dear, please don't.
I'm begging you, please don't do it!
Isha, don't! No, no, no.
Dad, please don't come closer.
Isha, look at me...
Let me stop your bleeding.
Stay away from her. Stay away!
- Dad, please!
- They will not listen.
What are you doing, Isha?
These madmen won't listen.
So we were talking about Pratap.
Brother, please...
They're not even letting us talk!
Hey, lady!
Stop all the shouting and screaming.
Let us talk.
- Don't listen to him, dear.
- Dad! Stay away...
Let me stop the bleeding, Isha.
Stop crying and let me speak.
You are looking at it, right?
Let me... Isha, please!
Let me take her to the hospital!
Please, let my daughter go...
Get lost.
That's it.
Isha, please...
Take the gun.
Go back.
This is what happens
when you try to be a hero.
I told you, didn't I?
If you act smart,
these girls won't spare you.
They'll tear you apart.
Be grateful to me, I just saved your life.
- Sir, sir, sir...
- Now just keep quiet. Let me talk.
- Isha, Isha, Isha.
- Isha.
Isha, Isha, Isha.
- Please.
- Now the drama will begin.
Let me take her to the hospital.
Oh, brother...
Isha!
I am tired of you all now.
They are not even letting us talk.
Get out, all of you.
Just go outside!
No, let her stay here.
- You all go outside, come on!
- Please, sir...
Let me take her to the hospital.
My daughter will die!
Why are you creating such a scene?
All parents, outside. Get out!
All parents get out right now.
Hey, lady! Let them stay here.
- Sir, please, please...
- You all, leave from here.
If I lose my cool,
everyone will end up like her.
Don't drive me berserk now.
Let him die right here.
Take whoever can still be saved
and get out.
Go, get out.
Please, sir.
Put pressure on this.
Please, please, please!
Everyone, go outside!
Think about your daughters!
Ma'am, for your daughter's sake,
please go outside!
Listen to her, otherwise
your own daughters will be troubled.
Listen to her. Everyone, go outside!
For the sake of your daughters.
You seem experienced.
Let's have a conversation.
It'll be fun, but first...
Let the situation calm down a bit.
Please, I request everyone to go outside.
Please listen to me.
Hello, make it quick!
Do you know how to use a gun?
No, sir.
Do any of the girls here
know how to use a gun?
Sir, I know.
- Come here.
- No, Chandni.
- She doesn't know. She is lying.
- Chandni, please listen to me.
Chandni, listen to me.
Let go of her hand.
I said, let go of her hand.
- Leave my daughter.
- Let go.
Should I make her suffer like her?
- No, please.
- Shut up.
Give me the gun.
Take it, dear.
From where did you learn to use a gun?
At the club.
Very good.
If these people don't listen
after being told once
bang, bang, bang...
Blow them all away, okay?
Take it.
Start with your mom and dad.
Well done, kid. Go on.
Mom, Dad, please go out.
- No, dear
- No, no, please.
Mom, Dad...
Dear, put it aside!
What are you doing?
- Please go out.
- What are you doing?
Enough, enough, calm down.
Calm down.
This girl has lost her parents.
Her whole family has been wiped out.
And this is the last time
I stop her, okay?
I won't stop her again.
Dear, all the people here
who are not ready to go,
finish off their daughters one by one.
Go.
- No, no!
- We will go!
Hey, Madam Principal!
Do I need to give an application?
Go.
Ma'am, stay away from her.
Otherwise, I will shoot Riya.
Listen to me, don't force me.
You people don't understand!
Why don't you go?
Otherwise, I will have to shoot!
Okay, now let's talk
about the main point.
Where is Pratap?
How did you meet him?
He has my daughter under a spell.
Okay, then?
She has been under the spell
for the last twelve years.
Oh!
Where is Pratap?
I've tied him up and have him under locks.
What?
For the past twelve years,
he's been suffering.
He cries in front of me,
begs me for death every single day.
Hey!
Mind your words.
He's my big brother, my mentor.
So?
I'll make your life hell.
In wickedness, I'm ten steps ahead
of my elder brother.
What will you do?
Will you kill me?
I've been waiting
for that moment for years.
And another thing...
These girls mean nothing to me.
I know
that their lives are
about to turn into hell.
Even if you order them
to set themselves on fire right now
I won't flinch.
After spending years
with a person like you,
I've also turned into stone.
Go ahead, do whatever you want.
Let the city burn, let fear spread...
It doesn't matter to me.
The parents standing outside
watching their innocent daughters suffer
will come to me, beg me.
They will beg me to hand over Pratap.
They'll scream, curse me,
maybe even burn me alive...
But my lips will stay sealed.
You will not get Pratap.
Where is Pratap?
Hand him to me, I will let you go.
I will hand him over.
On one condition.
Get my daughter out of his control.
Hey!
A petty man like you
has no right to put conditions
in front of me.
Do you even know who you're talking to?
With a monster.
I have kept someone like you
tied up like a dog for years.
Sorry.
Stop breathing!
I'll have to go.
If you don't reach on time, even Pratap
will suffer and die in the same way.
Wait.
Nothing will happen to your girls, please.
Ms. Rashmika!
He is calling you.
Dad, you stay away, go back.
- She is my daughter!
- Stop...
Come, ma'am. Greetings.
Do me a favor and clear away
all those people outside.
The police, journalists, parents
and teachers around the school,
clear them all out.
Lock them in the classrooms.
I don't want to see anyone.
And listen...
I'll need two school buses with drivers.
We're leaving in about 15 minutes.
Since it's a school bus,
I'm sure you've put a tracker on it.
So you'll know where we're going.
But don't follow us, okay?
Just watch from the computer,
only observe where we're going.
These girls of yours are the ones
keeping watch, right?
So if any cops are spotted in the area,
they'll either kill him
or kill themselves.
So, no following us.
I'll let them go at the crack of dawn.
And then, you can track them
to see where they are.
Go there and take them away.
I won't need them after that.
But before that,
make sure no one gets in my way.
The lives of the rest of these girls
are in your hands.
Okay?
Will you manage everyone outside?
Look up.
It will be done, right?
Please do it, we only have
15 minutes. Go ahead.
Nothing will happen to your daughter.
- Please stay calm, ma'am.
- Please cooperate.
Krisha, my daughter!
Save my daughter.
Nothing has happened to her,
please keep calm.
- Krisha will come back.
- Please listen, ma'am.
- Nothing has happened to Krisha.
- Please, ma'am.
Get in the bus.
Hurry up.
Come on, come on...
Make it quick!
Well done,
you are sitting on your haunches.
Drive, mister.
Show him the way.
Close the door.
Hey, stop, stop.
Come back, come back...
Okay, stop here.
Hey, girl!
Come here.
Come fast. Come on...
Get in the bus.
Quickly...
I'm telling you, get in the bus.
Come inside...
Come inside, I'm telling you.
Hey, listen.
Let's go.
One question has been nagging me.
May I ask?
Yes.
How could someone like you defeat Pratap?
I mean...
His power is so constant and unwavering.
He is a man of intelligence.
No one can match his penance,
his discipline.
Compared to him
I consider myself only 99 percent,
while he is beyond 100 percent.
So how did a common man like you
manage to defeat him?
When you meet him,
you'll see for yourself.
You're a really difficult person.
I need to meet my elder brother soon.
How long will it take?
About an hour and a half.
So, do we have to go outside the city?
Yes.
May I ask you a question?
After so many years,
why has the love for your brother
awakened now?
Love!
I have been searching for him
for a long time. For years.
I've made so many calls,
but none of them go through.
Without his permission,
I can't even go to his house.
His daughters would tear me apart...
Yet despite the risk,
I went to his house.
But neither he nor his daughters
were to be found.
So at first, I thought
that he might have gone somewhere
for some spiritual practice
or to make his spells stronger.
Or something of that sort.
Just for the success of one of his spells
he had stayed away
for two and a half years.
I thought he must have gone away.
I waited and waited for years.
Recently, I started feeling
that something was wrong.
I kept hearing strange sounds...
But...
I was sure that he is alive.
But where? How? In what condition?
I had no clue.
For the last two years,
I've been searching for him
day and night.
I've searched so many places.
Finally, I got so frustrated
that I had to take this step.
My brother has always warned me
not to bring attention to myself.
But I was so worried about him
that I couldn't think of any other way,
so this path seemed right.
And finally, this path was right.
I found him, didn't I?
Shall I ask you a question?
Yes.
What is your intention behind
controlling so many girls?
Why are you doing it?
You're a fool, really a complete fool.
Didn't you understand this
in twelve years?
Hey, girl, jump outside the window.
For centuries, it has been stated
wrongly in the scriptures
that female power is supreme.
That she can make anyone
dance to her tunes.
It's a lie.
It is the male who possesses power.
He can make anyone
dance to his tunes.
Man is power.
Man is creation, Man is Brahma.
Come on, girls!
Get off the bus and follow me.
Stop, stop, stop...
Everyone, come out quick.
Now...
all these girls will stay
behind with me, okay?
And the rest of the girls
will keep an eye out
all around the bungalow.
Make sure no one enters
from outside. Okay?
Let's go.
Where is Pratap?
First, my daughter--
Don't test me, okay?
First, take me to Pratap.
I will get your daughter out of the spell.
Where is my brother?
Downstairs.
Let's go.
Has she been smiling like this
for the past twelve years?
Yes.
Wow! This is something
only my big brother could do.
There's still a lot to learn from him.
Let's go.
Brother!
What is this?
What have you done to him?
Hey, Brother! Brother!
Hey, unlock his chains.
What have you done?
You're a bigger monster than us.
Monster!
Brother? Unlock his hands.
Bring him to his senses.
He's right in front of you, he's alive.
You've seen it. Now let's go,
free my daughter from his spell.
Hey...
I'm not used to taking orders
from anyone, okay?
My brother is still alive.
And if I tell these girls,
they will finish you
and your daughter in seconds.
If I break the chains
and take my brother and go away...
Then what will you do?
But no, I won't do it.
I'm actually enjoying talking to you.
I like your attitude.
Go, bring your daughter.
You come upstairs.
Stop stretching it, man.
To get your daughter
out of the spell,
my brother will be needed.
Go, bring her downstairs.
Go! You want to save your daughter?
Then go.
Bring her.
Girls, let him go. Make way.
Come, dear. Come.
Let's go, dear.
Where are you taking her?
Bring her inside.
Yes, one minute.
Tell me something,
did you invite my brother?
I mean, did you invite him in any way?
Move aside.
"Come, you're most welcome..."
"Come with me..."
Anything of that sort?
I don't remember, maybe.
You must have invited him, you fool.
Otherwise this wouldn't have happened.
Be careful.
Hey, hold the wheelchair in place for him.
Do you have
any unsettled debt with Pratap?
What?
I mean,
did you take something from Pratap,
like money, and still haven't returned it?
I didn't take anything.
He had once fed
my daughter some sugar, that's it.
No, sugar is used
in mind control rituals.
But that breaks anytime,
it's not permanent.
Let go of her hand. Come on.
I made all these girls eat the food
that's been enchanted by my spell.
Move! Hey, make space...
Come on, let him through.
Come.
But remember, the control lasts
only as long as they're near me.
If they go far,
or if they meet their parents,
the effect fades in two to four hours.
At most, 24 hours.
Then they're out of my control.
Didn't you see that girl on the road?
I kept asking her to come back,
but she didn't listen.
She ran away
and broke free from my control.
But the way this one has lasted...
I'm sure...
You and your family
are under some debt.
Even if the spell was cast
on your daughter
my brother must have bound
your whole family in this.
Otherwise, no spell lasts 12 years.
No, I didn't take anything.
I didn't even know him.
Then it's your wife.
No, she is no more.
She and my son are no longer alive.
Then you definitely took something.
- No, nothing at all... What did I...
- Hey, move aside!
You're standing in the way like rocks.
Think! Try to remember!
- I haven't taken anything at all.
- Try to remember!
Yes! He got me tea once
and he paid for it.
How much did it cost?
Rs. 10.
Fine, then, give him Rs. 10.
Rs. 10?
Yes, give Rs. 10 to my brother.
I don't have the change,
will 500 work?
Just give him Rs. 10.
Yes.
Here, take the money.
Not to me, give it to my brother.
First, wake him up
and let him come to his senses,
then give it to him.
Hey, Pratap! Hey!
Hey, Pratap... Take this.
- Rs. 10 for the tea.
- Hey, Brother.
Make him sit and bring him to his senses.
Splash some water,
let him regain awareness
and then give him the money.
- Girls, help out.
- Come on.
Come on, get up!
Stand up! Open your eyes.
- Get up...
- Go away now.
Hey, hey!
Get up, Pratap.
Come on, get up...
Open your eyes...
Get up... Pratap...
Here... take your Rs. 10 for the tea.
Take it back, here, take it.
Take your money back.
You gave it long ago,
now take it back.
Hey, Pratap!
Here, take your money back.
Here, take it.
Take it, take your money back.
- Big brother, take the money.
- Hey...
Look at me.
Look at me, here, take it.
Hold it.
Take it.
Take the money.
Take the money, I've given it.
I've given it.
I've given the money, now what?
Free from the debt.
Done, everything is over.
Now, go, call your daughter.
She'll be free from his control.
That's it?
Yes, call her.
Your daughter is free. Call her.
I will be the first to break
what my brother has done.
Aarya...
Aarya, my daughter...
Aarya... Oh, Aarya.
Shake her up.
Aarya...
Aarya, my child.
Look here, Aarya.
Give her a few slaps,
she needs to be free
from twelve years of captivity.
Aarya...
Hey, Aarya!
Aarya! Aarya...
Aarya! Aarya!
Aarya...
My child...
Aarya, Aarya.
Aarya.
My daughter...
Aarya, it's dad...
Dad, dad...
Aarya, my child.
Aarya... my daughter!
It's daddy.
Daddy...
Aarya...
My child...
Dad...
Dad.
Oh! My child...
No, Arya! No!
No, no, no!
Don't look there! Don't look there!
My child, it's all over!
Don't look there, I am here.
I am here. He can't hurt you.
I am here.
My child!
Don't be afraid, dear.
Aarya! Aarya!
Aarya, no! Aarya, no!
Aarya, no, no, be quiet.
No, no, no, my child!
It's over, it's over.
- Get aside, move aside.
- Hey.
No, my child!
Calm down, don't look there.
Don't look. Aarya, no!
No, Aarya! No, no, no.
Now your work is done!
Now unlock my brother's chains.
Unlock my brother's chains.
Take this.
Why are you giving me?
Girl, unlock the chains.
Aarya, no! Aarya, no!
Unlock all the chains.
It's okay, it's okay...
I am here, don't look there.
Don't look there, my child!
Don't look there, Aarya!
Carefully...
Now, move aside.
Brother, I'm Rajnath.
I've come to take you home.
Will you be able to stand,
or should I call the girls?
What?
What? Speak in a way
that I can understand.
No, no, look at me!
Daddy is here.
Please, look at me.
Look at me, listen to me.
My child...
I am sorry.
Did he cut off your tongue?
Hey! Move, move, go away.
Sorry, sorry, my child.
You cut off his tongue? His tongue?
Did you cut off my brother's tongue?
You cut off my brother's tongue!
You cut off his tongue.
Why? Why the tongue? Why?
You ruined my ten years
of hard work. Why?
To save my daughter.
But now you will not be saved.
Neither you nor your daughter
will be spared!
You know, I wanted
to let you and your daughter go.
I didn't want to do anything.
But you have cut off my brother's tongue...
Now he is of no use to me.
No use, all the ten years of effort...
The practices and austerities
he did are now wasted.
I still have the last lesson to learn!
But you've cut off his tongue!
I made a mistake, please forgive me.
Let me and my daughter go.
Please forgive me.
Dad.
Forgive you? Forgive you?
You ruined ten years of my hard work
and I should forgive you?
The ultimate guru mantra was left
and you've cut off his tongue.
Should I forgive you?
What should I do now?
Learn it by myself?
It will take years to learn it
by myself. Years!
Dad!
- Dad...
- Dad!
Now you will suffer like me.
Just as I suffered to learn the spells,
you will suffer for your daughter.
No.
I will take your daughter with me.
I will learn the spell through her.
Let's go, girls, come with me.
Come, girl, we have to go.
Let us go.
Leave my daughter or I won't spare you.
What did you say?
Dad...
I like your attitude.
What will you do?
You have given my daughter a new life.
You have freed her from the spell.
That is why I am letting you go.
But now, if you even lay
a hand on my daughter,
I will make your plight
worse than your brother's.
Hand? Here, I am using my leg.
What will you do?
Girls, kill both of them.
- Aarya...
- Dad.
Let go of me...
Fool.
How will you punish him?
I want to kill that bastard...
The death penalty is as good
as mercy for these criminals.
Let these two monsters stay here.
I will torture them every day.
All these girls were
in a mental prison for a few hours.
But my daughter...
She was in that mental prison
for twelve long years.
I will not forget that.
I will not spare those two monsters.
I will neither let them die...
Nor will I let them live.
The perverted joy they felt watching
all these helpless girls suffer...
The perverted joy that
these two demons felt
watching the parents cry...
I will do the same to them
for the rest of my life.
Every day.
The law will not be able
to give them such a punishment.
In fact...
No one can give such a punishment.