MORGUE
Sir, help me!
Help me, please!
Hello, Jun? What is it?
Jun!
Hello.
Yes.
Okay. I'll be there.
I'm good.
I can get there by myself.
I just landed three hours ago,
but that's not an issue.
Yes. Now.
Good evening, sir.
FORENSIC LABORATORY CENTER
He's here.
Sorry to call you here so late, Chief.
What's the matter?
Probably robbery.
We're investigating what went missing.
Right. How was Malaysia?
The usual.
Paid my daughter a visit.
I thought you went home to Pekanbaru.
No.
This way.
Excuse me, Chief.
The guard's name is Alim Sujiwo.
He's only worked here for three weeks.
This building closes at 8:00 p.m.
He checked the ground floor
around half past nine.
Before the incident,
he called the head of security for help.
He sounded terrified.
He didn't get to explain anything.
Then I heard glass breaking.
He was all by himself?
Yes, Chief.
Only one guard works the night shift.
For a lab as vital as forensics...
Only one guard?
How reckless.
Any theft or any missing items?
None so far. Except one.
One of the bodies went missing, Chief.
A body of a female disappeared.
Sofia Arini.
Cause of death, cardiac arrest.
No autopsy yet.
Who was the doctor in charge?
Doctor Nadia, Chief. Just the one.
We've contacted her.
TOE TAG - DECEASED
SOFIA ARINI - 50 - FEMALE
All the cameras are off but one.
Why is that?
Maybe he messed up.
Or maybe someone's messing with us.
Meaning a group of burglars
came to pick that body up.
Are you sure nobody broke in here?
Affirmative, sir.
We only have one problem.
We couldn't get into the control room
because the passcode was changed.
Chief, the forensic team is here.
Go see them.
Got it, Chief.
Julie.
Give me the details.
Who went missing?
Sofia Arini.
Fifty years old, married to Jefri Adam.
No children.
Just got back from Berlin on business
before finally being found dead.
An amazing woman.
ID NUMBER - NAME - ADDRESS
OCCUPATION - SEX
Be strong, Jef.
We all miss Sofia.
We should get going.
Go get yourself some rest.
Babe, why are you here?
I've missed you, baby.
You can always give me a call.
What?
I don't feel comfortable there.
I'm fed up
with all the fake crying all day.
Yeah, I know. But...
But what if someone notices
you coming here?
Nobody will notice.
I made sure everything's fine.
I swear.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Hey.
I did this for you.
For us.
We're safe now.
We can be together openly.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
Okay.
I'm thirsty.
Could you get me a drink?
One second.
You're not answering?
Just someone saying condolences.
This late?
Hello. Yes.
Yes, speaking.
Oh, right.
About that.
I provided all the details
to your partner this afternoon.
Disappeared?
What do you mean disappeared?
Of course.
Okay, I'll be there.
Okay.
Who was it?
The police.
What do they want?
They said Sofia's body disappeared
from the morgue.
She's really dead, right?
Yeah, she... She's dead, baby.
Are you sure?
I am. Totally.
I did it myself.
I made sure it worked.
So how could she go missing?
Babe.
Don't go.
What if they're suspicious
and they question you?
The doctor declared a heart attack.
A normal death.
There's nothing to be suspicious of.
The thing is,
if I don't go,
they really will suspect me.
Good evening.
Sorry to summon you here this late
with unpleasant news.
So how did my wife's body go missing?
Our first hypothesis,
someone stole your wife's body.
This is
the Police Forensic Laboratory Center.
Is there no security here?
24 hour surveillance.
Complete with cameras.
Strangely, they're all turned off.
The guard got spooked
and was rushed to the ICU.
As if he saw the undead.
- So there's no logical explanation?
- There is.
The thief is possibly
part of an organ trafficking syndicate.
Or they used black magic.
But if it's the former,
they'd steal more than just one body.
Did your wife have enemies?
I don't think so.
But she...
She owned the country's
largest pharmaceutical company.
She must've had rivals.
I'll set the record straight.
When it comes to business,
undoubtedly so.
There are countless new companies
that tried to copy our products.
But enemies...
Especially someone who would go
so far as to steal her body...
I don't think so.
How about you?
Do you have enemies?
Someone who would take revenge
on your loved ones?
I don't have enemies.
Fine. If it's not you, then...
could be some other family member.
Go ask Sofia's family.
- She had two siblings.
- We have.
We've talked to them.
- Before me?
- Yes.
They even
told us about
your prenuptial agreement.
We clearly should've talked to you first.
But you weren't home at the time, and...
they gave us your number.
I went out for a while.
I went to buy medicine.
I've had a terrible headache all day.
Feeling better now?
Absolutely.
May I see the medicine you bought?
Excuse me, Chief.
Doctor Nadia is here.
Excuse me.
We'll pick up where we left off.
Yes?
I need your help.
- What?
- The guard who worked at this place.
They said he's in the ICU.
I think he's in the nearest hospital
from here, Mitra Jasa.
- You have friends there, right?
- I do.
I intern there.
Find out who the guard is
and what he saw that terrified him.
Okay, I'll try.
How are you holding up there?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Call you later. I love you.
No smoking on the premises.
I thought you'd make exceptions
in situations like these.
Our forensic pathologist
would like a word.
Your wife just came back
from Berlin, correct?
Yes, correct.
This states that your wife
had aerophobia, fear of flying.
Yes. She'd already seen a psychiatrist.
And I reckon she managed to get over it.
Did you know
stress from long flights
can lead to cardiac arrest?
Do you think
that's what killed my wife?
Could be.
We still haven't made a conclusion.
- Anything hereditary?
- No.
Asthma, perhaps? Diabetes?
What does her medical record
have to do with her body's disappearance?
I'm looking from a medical perspective.
With her record, I'm...
suggesting that it might be...
catalepsy.
Catalepsy?
Suspended animation.
One moment.
Are you sure it's catalepsy?
It was me who received
the body when it arrived
and it was me
who issued the death certificate.
I examined the body properly.
In that case, wouldn't it be weird
if she just up and disappeared?
With her in the compartment,
she would've screamed for help.
That's true.
It would make more sense
if someone came here
and stole the body.
Fine.
Forget about the whole
catalepsy hypothesis.
There's a criminology theory that says
all deaths are homicide
until proven otherwise.
Cardiac arrest can be induced.
By putting someone
under high psychological pressure
or inserting something
in the body that causes cardiac arrest.
That said,
there's only one way to prove it.
Autopsy.
If there's no body,
there's no autopsy.
Sorry, Nad.
For making you work
in the middle of this rainy night.
Lio told me
you just got back from Malaysia.
Paid Lidya a visit?
How's school for her?
Finished college.
She just got a job.
Is she well?
All good.
Hey, your dad is here.
- Hi, Dad! Hello!
- Hello!
She's taken her little bath!
- Smells nice, doesn't she?
- She does.
Blow out the candles
Blow out the candle.
Yay! Clap your hands!
Lidya!
We are now in Bandung.
That there is our new home.
You must be exhausted.
Thanks for the ride.
- It's green.
- Yeah.
When will you stop carrying
that guilt everywhere you go?
You need to stop for yourself.
For your daughter.
I remember that night.
It felt just like tonight.
The exact same date as today.
Mr. Jefri, where are you going?
Please go back inside.
What do you still need me for?
We're not done investigating.
How much do you need?
All of you. Name your price.
Yes, yes.
But I'm afraid I'm still
going to need you to wait inside.
What time is it?
I'm still in mourning.
What are you holding me back for?
Yes, yes.
Get your boss here right now.
We'll have a little chat.
Get this over with.
What now?
You should wait inside, Mr. Jefri.
Hey, you two! Come here!
Bambang, Hardi,
go check the electrical panel.
- Go, get a move on!
- Yes, sir.
T-800.
We're working with the Germans.
They're going to invest in us,
so let's celebrate, come on.
Later, okay?
I'll arrange our dinner tonight.
I have to go to work.
We haven't seen each other for five days.
You can skip work just for today.
I just want to talk to you.
Hear your stories and be all romantic.
Let's spend today just the two of us.
I have a meeting, Sof.
Jefri Adam.
The director of my family's company.
You can arrange your meetings
or whatever however you like.
Even if you don't go to work,
who's going to fire you?
Oh, right.
Me.
Only I can fire you anytime, honey.
I'm sick of this kind of joke.
I work with all my heart.
My field of work is in fact
the science that I mastered.
I got here
not because I'm merely your husband.
Sure.
That's why I put you in this position.
Pharmacy is indeed your field.
But also...
So you won't be a lecturer forever.
Pure chemistry lectures? Come on.
- Can you live like this with your salary?
- Enough, Sof!
I'm not leaving for the office upset
because of your condescending remarks.
See you later.
What are you doing here?
I heard a noise here,
so I came to check it out.
Chief.
Power went out. Either deliberately
turned off or a short circuit.
They're looking into it.
What's this doing here?
These belonged to the body.
This box was supposed to be...
in the locker.
Mr. Jefri, please move out of the way.
It's broken open.
Everything is here but the phone.
I didn't take anything.
Did one of the bodies just get up then?
They got bored,
decided to see what's up online?
Empty your pockets.
Why would I steal my own wife's phone?
Mr. Jefri, please.
My phone.
Is that everything?
- Hands up.
- For what?
Hands up. This is a frisk.
- I'm not going to--
- Hands up, you bastard!
Let me go!
- I can sue you!
- Silence!
Sir. Mr. Arya.
Mr. Arya.
What's this?
I don't know. Found it here.
It has your company logo.
Our products are publicly sold.
And this is a forensic laboratory.
It's not weird seeing our product here.
What is T-800?
Some kind of toxin.
What kind of toxin?
I don't know.
- We make toxins for medical use.
- What use?
Plenty of them.
It's not within my expertise to explain.
Answer it.
It's my sister.
Yes?
Jef, I found it.
The name of the guard
is Alim Sujiwo.
I'm at the hospital now.
Yeah, I'm still here.
Sofia's body is still missing.
But they promise to keep looking for her.
What's with you?
Are you being watched?
Yes, call you later.
Bye.
My sister. She's worried.
Asked me when will I get home.
Anything else I can help with?
You're going to need
to write a statement letter,
then you can go.
Can I use the toilet first?
Mrs. Sofia Arini...
Jefri Adam.
"Every time I close my eyes,
All I see is you."
Where have you been?
We're supposed to go to a dinner.
There was trouble at the lab.
Penny said you weren't at the lab.
You weren't in your office since lunch.
I went out for lunch.
Didn't say a word to Penny.
After lunch,
I checked samples in several labs.
I called, why didn't you answer?
Phone was in my bag.
Left it in the car. No idea you called.
- I'll go take a shower.
- Wait.
Wear the gray suit I bought you.
You look great in that.
I prefer the black one.
Do you have a problem with me?
I don't.
I'm just tired from work and need rest.
Say it.
Say you still love me.
I love you.
Jef, I'm not losing you, am I?
We'll always be together.
EVERY TIME I CLOSE MY EYES,
ALL I SEE IS YOU.
- Not done yet?
- Not yet, sir.
Fine then, I'll take over.
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah.
Mr. Jefri!
What's taking so long?
Sir.
You're not allowed to smoke here.
Mr. Jefri!
My stomach is churning. Hold on.
You need to come with me.
We have an update.
Sir.
- Mr. Jefri.
- Just hang on!
You can't smoke here.
The smoke detector will go off
and you'll get us all drenched.
Mr. Jefri.
Sir!
Mr. Jefri!
What's taking you so long?
- Sir, hurry up!
- One second.
- Mr. Jefri!
- One second!
Mr. Jefri.
Yeah.
What's the update?
We have a new lead.
So, can we get it open yet?
Yes, sir.
We have reset the entire system.
Go ahead, sir.
Chief.
- Why am I here?
- This is the control room.
All the electrical and security systems
of the building are controlled from here.
Including the cameras.
However, there's a part of this building
that's easy to break into.
This vent.
They tore the grid from both sides.
And this vent would lead us to the woods.
Our team is looking into it.
Maybe they came through this hole here,
cut off the cameras,
and then stole the body.
Excuse me, ma'am. We found a new trail.
January 10, 2024.
Does that mean anything to you?
Nothing. Why?
Somebody changed today's date.
Set us back by eight months.
The culprit most likely did it.
From here...
access to the morgue is through this door.
A door only accessible via a passcode.
If the perpetrator can hack the system,
why would they change the passcode...
into a specific set of numbers?
10...
01...
24.
Hey.
Goodness, Sofia.
I could've had a heart attack!
Please don't.
How did you get here?
Penny said you'd be here.
Wait, I need to write this down.
I saw you earlier.
- Saw me what?
- Punching in the passcode.
Why did you pick that date?
You assume it's a date.
Jefri, my love,
you use dates for all your passcodes.
Emails, safes, ATMs, doors at home.
They're all dates,
even the unpleasant ones.
Whoever did it,
they must've used this freight elevator.
This goes almost directly to the morgue.
It's made to ferry bodies. Come in.
Okay.
We've already figured out
the method and the access.
Now to find the culprit.
We're going to find out soon.
Okay.
Any leads who did it?
We just found footprints.
They seemingly wore running shoes.
They moved from the woods
through the vent to the control room.
What is your shoe size?
Forty-three.
Lio.
Monitor, monitor.
This is Lio with Mr. Arya in the elevator.
We suddenly stopped. What's going on?
Chief, a fire activated the fire alarm.
Okay, everyone, to the lobby!
Yes, Chief!
Gosh, shit.
- Hello, Sarah.
- Are you still there?
I can't speak right now.
- Where are you?
- Hospital parking lot.
I saw the calendar.
The date was changed
to the day we first met.
What calendar?
What's that got to do with us?
Jef?
Hello? Are you still there?
SARAH ARUDITA, FEMALE, 20
Did you kill me because of Sarah, Jef?
Jef.
My dear Jefri.
I can feel her presence.
Sofia is still alive.
Now she's messing with us.
You said you perfectly
carried out your plan.
I don't know
how she came back to life either!
How do you know she did?
"Every time I close my eyes,
all I see is you."
She knew you sent that message to me.
She checked your phone?
You didn't delete it?
Point is, if she knows you're involved,
you're in danger, Sarah!
And now
she made it as if I stole her body.
But is she really capable of doing that?
Not by herself.
Enough, Jef.
You better get out of there.
Let's run away together.
- Jefri?
- Sarah, Sarah.
I'll call you later. Love you.
Jef.
If I have to take a guess...
That must be your sister.
Yes.
Asked me to come home.
She's worried.
Your phone, please.
We got nothing
out of the phone, sir.
He deleted
all the incoming and outgoing calls.
We can't find out who his last call was.
We found this.
Any updates from the others?
K9 is still following the footprints
into the woods on the other side.
Forensic team found
a cigarette butt in the toilet.
Sloppily discarded,
resulting in triggering the fire alarm.
That's certainly his.
When I came to pick him up
in the toilet, I smelled cigarette.
And now the floor in every room
is drenched.
This will make tracing impossible.
That bastard!
He's trying to wipe up evidence.
I received a report from the lab.
The T-800 serum is some sort of poison
that induces cardiac arrest.
Concocted from the venom
of various reptiles.
It dissolves in blood,
stops the heart within eight hours, and...
leaves no trace.
Get the custody van ready.
I'm transferring him to headquarters.
Yes, Chief.
I want him confined and heavily guarded.
- Lio.
- Yes.
- Confiscate his cigarettes.
- Got it.
Is it locked?
All done.
Where would he run off to?
Next door is the morgue anyway.
Who's Sarah, Jef?
Can you come pick me up, Jef?
Honey.
We'll be together forever, right?
Sofia?
Hello?
DANI AGUSTINUS, 50, MALE
Who's that?
Nobody.
A nobody that came here just for you?
Okay, if you must know,
he's my lawyer.
For what?
To review the clauses in our prenup.
Are they legally binding?
Which clause?
Asset distribution.
In case of infidelity or divorce.
Why are you overthinking?
It's like you're accusing me.
It's not an accusation if I have proof.
It's up to you to admit it or not.
Why the serious face? I was joking.
I wish I recorded your face.
It's not funny, Sof.
If he's not a lawyer, then who is he?
Dr. Dani Agustinus, a psychiatrist.
I didn't know
you're seeing a psychiatrist.
I've only had a few sessions.
I want to take care
of my mental health too.
Sofia?
This isn't Sofia.
But her phone is here.
When will she get it?
- Get it where?
- Monomono restaurant.
How did my wife's phone end up there?
No clue, sir.
It was found in the restroom
by the cleaners. Maybe Mrs. Sofia
was in a rush and forgot it.
My wife is dead.
Someone must've put it there on purpose.
But...
It's possible my wife
was at your restaurant last night
and intentionally left her phone there.
Wait, what?
I thought you said she's dead.
Well, she could still be alive.
Sir, I'm so sorry.
I'd rather stay out of
your personal matters.
Again, if you want to collect
Mrs. Sofia's phone,
please come to Monomono Restaurant.
Thank you.
Hello?
Babe, it's me.
The cops took my phone.
I'm stuck in the autopsy room,
and I found this phone.
I think someone did this on purpose.
Did what on purpose?
The only number
saved in this phone
is Sofia's.
- So whose phone is this?
- Dani Agustinus'.
I met him a few weeks ago
before Sofia went to Berlin.
Sofia said Dani Agustinus
was her psychiatrist, but I doubt it.
I'm sure she lied.
I need your help.
Find out who this Agustinus really is.
Where did you get this phone?
At...
the morgue.
Dani Agustinus...
is dead.
Sir.
I found an interesting clause
in the prenup.
Please.
Thanks.
Why am I still being detained?
I believe
you killed your wife with the T-800 serum
and stole her body to avoid an autopsy.
What's that suspicion based on?
Your behavior over the last few hours.
The bottle of the serum
found in your pocket.
That's not mine.
Your company made it.
So I'm a suspect because
my company made it and I'm the director?
The serum was produced by the largest
pharmaceutical factory
with high-tech equipment,
and it can cause a cardiac arrest.
You're not just the director,
you're also a chemist.
And your wife died of cardiac arrest.
You take me for a fool?
I didn't kill my wife!
Even if I did kill her,
I'd be an idiot to bring that here.
Why would anyone kill
or poison someone with T-800
and then steal the body
just to avoid an autopsy?
T-800 dissolves in the blood.
Impossible to detect in an autopsy.
Interesting how well you know
about the serum now
when you said
you knew nothing about it before.
Well... I was panicking earlier.
You kept pressuring me.
Rather than accusing me
with your nonsense,
think about what I just said.
See if it makes sense.
Make excuses all you want.
I just need to prove that you
have a reason to steal that body.
I didn't steal it!
How many times do I have to say it?
You're supposed to locate my wife's body!
Okay.
Do you mind telling us...
how you met your wife?
How's that relevant?
I was just wondering.
Since you two are so different.
- Different?
- Age gap.
Social status, and more.
Go on.
Feel free to go into detail.
We met in Bandung by chance.
By chance?
My motorcycle broke down, she passed by
in her car, offered me a ride.
We talked,
grew closer, and fell in love.
Pretty much it.
Can coincidences like that really happen?
Like something out of a soap opera.
NATIONAL PHARMACY SEMINAR
Please welcome our speaker,
Ms. Sofia Arini, CEO of Hexa Medica.
We met in Bandung
at a pharmaceutical conference.
She was a speaker,
I was a participant.
Did you go there of your own accord?
I was representing the campus
where I teach.
I had just got my bachelor's degree
and wanted to pursue a master's.
During that conference,
you tried to get close to her?
No.
I just watched from a distance.
Then how did you become close?
One day I was visiting Pangalengan.
My rental motorcycle broke down.
There was no reception,
I couldn't call the rental place
or a workshop.
Then Sofia's car passed by.
Did you break down?
You were at the conference, right?
I was surprised she recognized me.
Yes.
Even though I didn't stand out at all.
I'm an introvert,
but Sofia is very sociable.
She can make conversations
feel comfortable.
Back then, I was burnt out
from campus life,
and Sofia was still grieving her parents.
We grew close during the three days
of the conference.
What did she see in you?
No idea.
She said she needed young minds
to grow the company.
I told her I was young
and I specialized in pharmacy.
We're working on a new product right now.
And I think...
you can help me, Jef.
Okay?
If you trust me,
I'm up for it.
At that time, were you aware
that she inherited one of the biggest
pharmaceutical companies in the country?
I knew once she told me.
And that made you want to
marry her even more,
despite her being 15 years older?
We were in love.
Love knows no age.
Just like
a Shakespearean love story.
How beautiful.
Until death do us part.
I was just lucky.
Luck can happen by accident,
but some requires real effort.
I love my wife.
Really?
Can you tell me about
the moment you reported your wife's death?
I've submitted the report.
I want to hear it from you.
You can read it.
I want to hear it straight from you.
After coming back from work,
I saw my wife lying on the sofa.
Sof?
The music was on,
so I thought she was asleep.
But when I checked,
she was already gone.
Love?
I don't sense any grief
in the way you're telling your story.
Because you're making me upset.
I explained everything to the officers
who came to my house!
But you keep asking about it!
Reading a written story
and hearing it in person are not the same.
No wonder your wife grew suspicious.
What do you mean?
She hired a private investigator.
She suspected you were having an affair.
This is a copy of your prenup.
PRENUPTIAL AGREEMENT
One clause states that
if you have an affair,
your wife will divorce you,
and you won't get a penny from her assets,
including...
your contributions to the family business.
Isn't that what you were afraid of?
That's why you considered
killing your wife
once she caught you cheating?
Ridiculous.
That's ridiculous!
We're about to prove it.
My team
is on the way
to Dani Agustinus' place to verify.
Who?
Dani Agustinus.
The private investigator.
He...
He's dead.
Here, take a look.
This is his body.
Yunus Sasmita?
This guy?
YUNUS SASMITA, 50, MALE
Wait.
BURHANNUDIN, 35, MALE
DJUNAEDI KOZANO, 75, MALE
- Yes, Julie?
- Chief.
We're at the investigator's office,
but it's empty.
Dani Agustinus is missing,
and so are his investigation files.
Looks like his computer's hard disk
is stolen.
There are traces of forced removal.
Search Sofia Arini's home as well.
She might have kept some reports.
I'll arrange for a search warrant.
Yes, Chief.
- Lio.
- Sir.
Where's the custody van?
One moment, let me check.
- Hello?
- Sir.
Where's the custody van?
The road is jammed due to a fallen tree.
We're stuck here.
You two, over here!
Yes, sir.
Hello, Sarah.
Dani Agustinus is a private investigator.
Yeah, I know.
How did you find out?
When I got back home,
there was an envelope under the door.
From whom?
The investigator?
No sender's name, just a flash drive.
I checked, and it had a folder
with the investigator's name.
What folder?
It's full of photos.
I'll send them to you.
They must have followed us.
Not only that,
I'm sending an audio file as well.
Listen to it.
Oh, God. What now?
Don't worry, Sofia is scared of flying.
If she suffers cardiac arrest,
they will think it's due to the stress
of a long flight.
Sarah.
Sofia knew everything.
If she was able to send this
to your address,
it means she knows you and can hurt you!
You should leave now,
I'll catch up with you later.
Promise me you'll be there?
Yes, I promise.
Sarah?
Sarah.
Sarah, hello?
I think I'm being followed.
Jef. I'm scared.
Where did you park your car?
Jefri.
Jefri!
Sarah.
Sarah? Hello?
Sarah!
Fuck.
Where are you going?
I have to go.
I'm the one who gives orders here.
Let me go!
With all the evidence,
you'll be detained soon.
I have to go, someone needs my help!
Who?
You all have no idea who I am.
I can sue you all if you try to stop me!
Hey.
- Let me go! I must help Sarah!
- Calm down.
Settle down!
Please, help Sarah.
Are you two in cahoots?
No, sir.
She's innocent,
she's not involved in this.
I swear.
Who is she to you?
Here.
Your so-called "sister"?
I know she's not.
Yes, she's not my sister.
I lied, I'm sorry.
Please help Sarah.
If you don't hurry, she could die.
On one condition.
Tell me everything.
From the beginning.
Check this address.
Yes, sir.
No lies this time.
Her name is Sarah Arudita.
We met eight months ago.
Despite being the director
of the company,
I still make time
to teach one course at my alma mater.
Sorry for being late.
Sarah arrived late that day.
Come in.
Her face was innocent and intelligent,
she captivated me.
I want you guys to find
the endpoint of this chemical reaction.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah?
Did I miss a lot of the lesson?
You did.
I said she missed
a lot of important things,
which was a lie.
If you like, I can explain it again
at the library.
To get her to depend on me.
So, an example of an organic compound is
aliphatic hydrocarbon
like gasoline, paraffin, methane gas,
acetylene gas, and so on...
I offered her special tutoring sessions
in the library after the class.
You're amazing, sir.
Huh?
I'm serious.
You explain chemistry
as easily as breathing.
So effortless.
I was always belittled at home.
But with Sarah,
I felt like a hero.
Always praised and admired.
Respected.
Yes, go ahead.
It started as a study session together,
but over time, we were looking forward
to seeing each other every day.
I was upfront with Sarah
about being married
and she also told me she had a boyfriend.
My wife grew suspicious.
I tried to stop contacting
and seeing Sarah,
but it was hard.
I felt guilty,
but Sarah gave me comfort
that Sofia didn't.
Eventually...
the guilt faded away.
Replaced by a sense of conviction
that what I was doing with Sarah
wasn't wrong.
I started to open up to Sarah.
I told her everything.
Even my secrets that I never shared
with anyone else.
Because we promised
to have no secrets or lies between us.
I didn't want to betray my wife.
However,
I had already fallen for Sarah.
Sarah broke up with her boyfriend
to be with me.
But I was not ready to leave Sofia.
Sarah had grown tired of waiting.
She waited for a long time.
She got mad and refused to see me.
Sarah!
I don't understand.
You cried and got upset for what?
Sarah disappeared for a while.
I tried reaching out
and searching for her.
I got nothing.
Sarah.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I choose you.
But ever since Sofia suspected something,
she kept a close watch on me.
Always.
I knew it would end in divorce.
And Sofia would destroy me,
my career, my life.
Is this Dani Agustinus?
I need your help.
I'm tired of this, Jef.
Let's break up.
Hey...
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Actually,
I've figured out a way to separate
from Sofia without a divorce.
And we would get everything.
Thank you, darling.
Where's yours?
It's too early for me.
But I have one question.
If you planned such a meticulous murder
using the T-800 serum,
why didn't she die
and instead disappeared?
What went wrong?
You saw her drink that wine.
How did she escape death?
See you.
Maybe she switched her glass?
After that, then what?
Maybe she took neuroleptic drugs
that could induce catalepsy.
These drugs dissolve in the blood,
slow down the respiratory system,
and... stop the heart for a moment.
After a while, the metabolism returns,
her body could return to normal.
Like suspended animation.
Wouldn't that be
too complex and dangerous?
Not for Sofia.
She likes a challenge.
She hates losing.
I told you everything. Please help Sarah.
Hurry up and help her!
Sir.
Wait. We're not done here.
Sir!
- Help Sarah!
- Who is it?
Julie found something.
- Yes?
- Sir.
We found the blueprint
of the forensic lab building
complete with alternative exit routes.
There's also a manual for the building's
electrical system and cameras.
This person knew the building inside out.
Any leads on the missing body?
Not yet.
But we found a shovel
and shoes in the car trunk.
The size matches the footprints
behind the building.
Anything else?
We found black clothing
in the pile of dirty laundry.
The outfit he used to sneak inside?
Ma'am.
Updates from the hospital?
Yes, Ma'am.
Report to the chief.
Sir.
The guard is awake
and he told me what happened.
- Tell me.
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
Help me!
Okay.
We found some clothes,
a mask, and black gloves.
They match
the security guard's description.
We also found a pair of shoes
that leaves footprints just like the ones
behind this building.
And tools capable of dismantling
iron bars.
Can you guess where we found them?
At your house!
Along with the building blueprint
and the electrical system manual.
I've never had the items you mentioned.
They must be Sofia's.
She's dead!
You killed her.
You can't even prove it.
Her body is still missing right now.
Because you hid it.
Because she's still alive!
Wait!
Wait. Let me explain.
The most plausible explanation
why Sofia is behind all this.
She's not alone.
Someone helped her.
She faked her death.
After that,
she planned to come back
at the right moment.
You stole the body.
You created confusion
as if she came back to life,
distracting the security guard that night.
You should check the private investigator.
Dani Agustinus.
Sofia must've paid him
to help her pull off this madness.
Her plan is flawless.
Making me the scapegoat.
Sarah.
Find Sarah,
she'll vouch for me.
Please find her.
Please.
Yes, Julie.
Chief.
Did you find the apartment?
There's no one here, Chief.
Any signs of violence?
He said she was threatened.
Nothing.
She ran away?
More than that.
It looks like this place has been vacant
for some time.
Okay.
Call the entire forensics team.
Yes. Secure every road
in a one-kilometer radius.
Chief.
K9 scoured the forest all night,
and we've located the body
deep in the forest.
The address you gave us,
Sarah Arudita's place?
It's unoccupied.
It's an empty apartment.
No one in the neighborhood
recognizes the name Sarah Arudita.
We also checked the hospital
where you said she interned,
but there's no record of her.
Now I'm starting to think
you're making up stories.
You created a fictional character
named Sarah Arudita in your head
to give yourself the courage
and motivation to kill your wife.
Take the body back.
Lio.
Remove the barricade.
Yes, sir.
We've created an unnecessary traffic jam.
Julie. Make a report.
The investigation is over.
We have enough evidence
to charge with multiple counts.
Yes, Chief.
Get up.
Wait, wait.
That bastard!
Where are you going?
Now I see how hard it is to pretend.
What's wrong with my body?
Why do I feel paralyzed?
We've been stuck in that forensic building
for almost eight hours.
You must be exhausted.
Please help me.
Take me to a hospital.
Help.
Would you take someone in pain
to a hospital
if the someone wasn't yourself?
I can't help but think of my late wife.
She passed away ten years ago.
Are you tired?
Close your eyes.
Thank you for the ride.
Enough.
- It's green.
- Yeah.
The official records say
she died in an accident.
But truth is,
she was murdered.
My daughter was also in that car.
Lidya!
Are you okay, Sweetie?
Dad.
It hurts.
Mira, wake up.
Mira.
Taking her to the hospital
or providing first aid
could have saved my wife.
But the car that hit us...
just drove away,
as if nothing happened.
Help!
Mira!
An hour passed
before help arrived.
Mira.
Mira!
My wife died in my arms.
I tried to remember
the car's license plate.
But nothing came up.
But one day my daughter remembered.
You're okay.
Take a break, Sweetie.
I'm okay, Dad.
You sure?
There was another clue.
A ten year old's drawing,
even though it wasn't precise.
But the logo was familiar.
I had plenty of time to investigate.
I contacted all my friends
in the police force,
collected every bit of information.
And in the end,
I found you.
- Jef!
- They have a kid, Sof.
- Jefri!
- Sof!
Go.
How can you live all these years
carrying the weight of such a crime?
Okay.
Let me make you understand.
This is my daughter.
Her name is Lidya.
- Hello?
- Good evening.
I'm Arya Pradana, from the police.
Sir! Send help!
We found a shovel
and shoes in the car trunk.
The size matches the footprints
behind the building.
Dad. I've left the phone
at the restaurant.
She approached you at the campus
without me knowing.
To make sure she didn't get
the wrong person.
Promise me you'll be there?
Yes, I promise.
Please be careful. Okay?
Jefri!
But no.
For herself,
she had to make you willingly confess
the worst things you ever did.
And she did it.
She made you confess everything,
all in the name of love.
There were three people in that car.
A man, a woman and...
A little girl.
I didn't know what to do.
I wanted to help them back then,
but Sofia asked me to flee the scene.
Sarah, what's wrong with you?
He confessed, Dad.
He's the culprit.
We'll finish it, dear.
We'll finish it.
That confession was all we needed
to hunt you down.
The T-800 serum is formulated
from various reptilian venoms.
It dissolves in blood,
stops the heart within eight hours,
and leaves no trace.
This serum also induces hallucinations.
Panic and fear will take over,
before eventually death.
Dad, I'm at the airport.
No one knows I'm here,
no one's following me.
I've emptied out the apartment.
I'm going back to Malaysia.
Look.
Take a look.
You'll soon be with your wife again.
You bastard.
So smug.
Arrogant.
Your tears mean nothing.
Three.
Two.
One.